<topics task="2021 TREC Clinical Trials"><topic number="1">Patient is a 45-year-old male. He has a cancerous mass in the lower part of his spine (T-L spine) called anaplastic astrocytoma. The meatball has left her legs very weak and she has trouble urinating. He's been given a Foley catheter. He's also on high doses of steroids, chronic pain and high blood pressure. The fleshy part cannot be removed surgically. He's already had radiation instead of the meat dish. Over time, his legs became weak and he had difficulty urinating First, weakness in his right leg, a broken knee while walking, and a decline in the front of his right thigh. MRI shows a flesh-pimple in the conus area of the spine. Biopsy confirmed it as an anaplastic astrocytoma. He was treated with radiation to the T10L1 area, followed by 11 cycles of temozolomide (lasting 7 days, 7 days off). He was then given CPT-11 four times a week and Avastin Q2 two weeks apart. Then the cycle was repeated for two weeks.</topic><topic number="2">Patient is a 48-year-old male with a prior history of hypertension, hypercholesterolemia, bicuspid aortic valve and long-term damage from smoking. He showed up at his cardiologist on 2148-10-1 with increasing respiratory distress and swelling in both legs. TTE indicates severe aortic stenosis and progressive decline in the function of the left ventricle. EF was 25%. RV pressure was 41 millimeters of mercury and two atria were large. Aortic insufficiency of 2+ and mild MR are also noted. He was sent home from the Cardiology Clinic with Lasix and BB, but he couldn't tolerate BB Her breathing and leg swelling continued to worsen and she was eventually admitted for evaluation. Critical aortic stenosis was confirmed at this admission re-echo, with significant left ventricular hypertrophy, cavity dilation and severe global hypokinesis, severe aortic valve stenosis (bicuspid aortic valve with a history of disease), dilated ascending aorta and mild pulmonary artery sytolic hypertension. The patient was assessed pre-operatively as part of a valve replacement plan, including pre-op chest CT and carotid US, where moderate heterogenic plaque and ICA 1.39% contraction on both sides were found. He performs right heart cath to assess pulmonary artery pressure, including cardiac catheterization. It shows that there's no flow-limiting disease in his heart artery.</topic><topic number="3">A 32-year-old woman came in with a sudden onset of very severe headaches. She and her husband said that the day before she was in the kitchen and hit her head on the corner of a cabinet while standing. The next morning, he suddenly had a very severe headache. He came to the hospital, where a head CT scan showed a significant amount of blood clots in his right ventricle. The NSGY team assessed him as a spontaneous intraventricular hemorrhage and suspected an underlying vascular malformation. Cerebral angiogram, showing abnormal blood vessels with a draining vein, which is penetrating deep into the white matter from the left temporal lobe, and is consistent with AVM The patient's headache was persistent, but the painkillers were slowly improving. The patient refused to undergo physical therapy, but was able to walk freely without any difficulty. She was discharged from the hospital and allowed to go home with her husband on [2155-12-6]</topic><topic number="4">This is a 44-year-old woman with a history of PCOS, obesity and high blood pressure. He is presently presenting with symptoms of cholecystitis. During the evaluation, he was accidentally diagnosed with a large pericardial effusion. Pericardiocentesis was then performed and the collected fluid was found to be consistent with Burkitt's lymphoma. Kappa light chain restricted CD10 positive monotypic B cells were found in pericardial fluid, which were expressing FMC-7, CD19, CD20 and myc rearrangement. These are consistent with Burkitt's Lymphoma No association was found in subsequent lumbar puncture and bone marrow biopsy, leading to a diagnosis of primary cardiac lymphoma. Cardiac MRI shows a flesh pimple adjacent to the AV junction in the lateral wall of the right atrium, measuring 3 cm &#215; 1 cm Previous history of illness: Rare migraines hypertension Obesity PCOS/infertility Viral encephalitis/meningitis &#8594; ICH &#8594; seizure/stroke ([2137])  due to severe sinus infxn; which has resulted in mild non-focal residual deficits meningitis with CSF leak; lumbar drain placement followed by right leg DVT; IVC filter placement followed by knee surgery</topic><topic number="5">This is a 74-year-old male with a history of previous CAD and subsequent CABG, EF 60%, previous CVA (no residual deficits), hypertension, HL, DMII and Moderate to Severe PVD He was referred to the cardiology department for evaluation of PVD. Physical examination of the patient revealed a carotid bruit. In a detailed review of symptoms, the patient reported occasional dizziness; but never before sudden unconsciousness; occasional HA; chest pain/refusal of breath No sensory or motor defects found He recalls that he had a stroke probably 10-15 years ago, but there was no residual deficit. He just had excessive sweating before the CABG. System review may include chest pain, respiratory distress, sudden sleeplessness with respiratory distress at night, sleepy breathing, chest palpitations, sudden fainting or absence of prior fainting The patient's carotid U/S is performed, which detects significant bilateral carotid stenosis, with a greater amount of left side than right side Angiography shows 80% stenosis in the right ICA and 90% stenosis in the left ICA Cerebral angiography also shows that the right ACA and MCA are normally open, as well as the left ACA and left MCA are normally open. Previous history: CAD and subsequent CABG performed in [2154] ([Hospital1 112]) Previous CVA Bilateral carotid artery disease Anemia PVD Hypertension Diabetes and its complications as retinopathy and peripheral neuropathy Cataracts and subsequent surgery Thyroid nodule Colon polyps and subsequent surgery Intermittent lower back pain Proteinuria Arthritis with fracture of the right elbow bone in childhood</topic><topic number="6">Patient is a 55-year-old female with a history of ESRD and is on HD and peritoneal dialysis. He appeared to have watery, non-bloody diarrhea and weakness Patient has a history of 2 previous C. diff infections, the last of which was just 1 month ago Last time she was in the hospital, she took antibiotics last month. The patient was also treated with po Vanco for 14 days for C. diff. Patient initially admitted to ICU and was in septic condition on pressors (Levophed) until [8-26] where leukocytosis was present but fever was absent C. diff assay was positive at admission, and the patient's leukocytosis was consistent with C. diff The patient is initially placed on Vanco po, Flagyl IV and Flagyl po When the patient's condition improves, he is switched to Vanco oral and Flagyl oral in [8-29] Due to recurrent C. diff, the patient was treated with a long course of Vanco, totaling 6 weeks. The patient is advised to take probiotics and clean his house with bleach during the discharge.</topic><topic number="7">Patient is a 60-year-old male with a history of HCV cirrhosis, NSAID-induced gastritis, grade II esophageal varices and recent admission for UGIB on [2-9] Referred for admission due to new slurred speech and tangential thought process through the emergency department from the Hepatology clinic Patient reports new balance loss, which caused him to fall and possibly suffer head injury According to the latest liver clinic note, he has been leaving ETOH for a year (confirmed with the patient) No alcohol found in Utox. CT scan was normal, and neurological review indicates it's not an ischemic infarct. Patient initially diagnosed with hepatic encephalopathy and initiated to lactulose therapy Liver function tests showed significant increases in total and direct bilirubin. Another worrying feature is the increase in the patient's AFP. This could indicate progression of cirrhosis, as she's had no effect from the previous two doses of interferon. He will be followed up as an outpatient for further evaluation. Previous history of disease: HCV Cirrhosis (2 treatments with interferon, no effect) Portal Gastropathy Grade II Esophageal varices Recent admission of hypertension [4-/2150]: UGIB [2-9], non-steroidal induced gastritis</topic><topic number="8">Patient is a 57-year-old male with CLL and large cell transformation. He presented with the disease on [10/2119]- where both his white count and LDH were elevated. At that time he had no splenomegaly or cytopenia, but some bulky lymphadenopathy was noted. He later completed four cycles of FCR therapy, which ended on 09/2119 He responded very well to the therapy and was followed for almost two years without treatment. [7-/2122]-date he reappeared, where white count increased, lymphocyte was about 50%, and LDH was slightly increased Some lymphadenopathy is also observed, which is mildly degenerative and palpable. The patient then received four rounds of PCR therapy, but there was no significant response. His treatment was later changed to R-CVP, of which he received two cycles. There was no significant response, although his performance status remained excellent. He later moved to Campath therapy. After Campath therapy, his lymphocytosis decreased and his white count decreased nicely, but there was no effect on reducing bulky lymphadenopathy. She later suffered from left cervical node enlargement, which was biopsied and revealed Richter's transformation.</topic><topic number="9">Patient is a 41-year-old male with a prior history of severe intellectual disability, CHF and epilepsy. He arrived at NH with muscle spasms on the right side of his face and a whole body cough, which required 20 mg of Valium to stop seizure activity. According to the external medical report, the patient has been diagnosed with secondary generalization including focal epilepsy, which is probably due to anoxic brain injury at birth and related to atrophic changes seen on MRI, especially in the left temporal lobe. The patient first had a seizure at the age of 13, when family members noticed a whole body spasm. The second squeeze occurs two years after the first. Then she was put on Dilantin and phenobarbital. The patient hadn't had another contraction for almost 20 years. Recently Dilantin has been slowly reduced, and it was thought that perhaps this drug was necessary to keep him free of the ticks The patient did not have any more seizures during the hospital stay and was back to normal by the time he left the hospital. Full EEG report, pending at the time of dictation Previous history of the disease: Epilepsy (as described above) CHF depression</topic><topic number="10">Patient is a 22-year-old female, generally healthy, with a 5-year history of systemic mastocytosis. Its flare usually occurs three times a year He's currently presenting with flushing and tachycardia, which are possible symptoms of another flare. This is the patient's third flare in two months, which occurred during steroid tapering and is new to her. Patient responds well to his ongoing home regimen with 125 mg IV steroid (every 8 hours) and IV diphenhydramine CBC was consistent with his baseline, and differential was normal. Serum tryptase was high, 84 Patient failed due to adverse reaction to aspirin challenge Patient stabilized with IV steroids and IV Benadryl and then transferred back to the medical floor. He kept his home histamine receptor blockers on and switched from IV to PO steroids and Benadryl. After an overnight observation, he was discharged, with the following medications: home medications, prednisone taper, PPI including GI prophylaxis, Calcium and vitamin D, and SS Bactrim for PCP.</topic><topic number="11">The patient is a 75-year-old male with metastatic papillary thyroid cancer who has previously received 19 sessions of XRT. He has been presenting with increasing difficulty swallowing solid food for the past 2 days, decreased oral food intake, a weight loss of about 20 pounds in the last several weeks and some lethargy. Papillary thyroid cancer is first diagnosed by a muscle test in the right side of the throat. He had a neck mass resection; however, a thyroidectomy was not possible. This was due to the high risk of bleeding, the proximity of the trachea and recurrent laryngeal nerve, and the large size of the muscle. The patient then received XRT in the throat and RAI ablation was performed. The cancer has spread to the lymph nodes and adrenal glands. History of previous surgery: &#8226; Hernia repair &#8226; Tonsillectomy</topic><topic number="12">Patient is a 34-year-old female with Marfan's syndrome and a history of mitral regurgitation with severe mitral valve prolapse. He had earlier planned to have his mitral valve (MV) repaired but did not show up for the next follow-up. He is currently in a symptomatic condition and is being prepared for mitral valve repair or replacement surgery. His ejection fraction (EF) was found to be 65% on Transthoracic echocardiography (TTE). Previous history of illness: &#8226; Marfans syndrome &#8226; Severe mitral regurgitation including mitral valve prolapse (MVP) &#8226; Gastric reflux disease &#8226; History of gestational diabetes mellitus &#8226; Pregnancy-related hypertension &#8226; Obesity Previous history of surgery: &#8226; Two Cesarean sections &#8226; Laser eye surgery &#8226; Cataract surgery &#8226; Foot surgery (bone length shortening)</topic><topic number="13">Patient is a 62-year-old male with a previous history of CVA He has a neurogenic bladder and an indwelling suprapubic catheter implanted. He has been hospitalized several times in the past due to UTI, altered mental status and urosepsis. He is currently in hospital with urosepsis, which is currently under control after treatment with vanc/meropenem. CT scan shows a non-obstructing stone in the left ureter and no evidence of urethral stricture Significant leakage was observed around the site of the suprapubic catheter. Patient initially started on Ditropan, later changed to Detrol The urologist is not particularly concerned about the leakage and plans to follow up with the patient next week. Previous history of disease: &#8226; After CVA &#8226; After neurogenic bladder, after insertion of suprapubic catheter &#8226; Recurrent UTI (caused by Klebsiella / Pseudomonas) &#8226; Non-Hodgkin' s Marginal Zone Lymphoma (Left Oxygote), Dx 03  s/p R-CHOP &#215; 6 cycles &#8226; Bell' s palsy &#8226; BPH &#8226; Hypertension &#8226; Partial bowel obstruction, followed by colostomy &#8226; Hepatitis C &#8226; Cryoglobulinemia &#8226; Transverse myelitis, including SLE, with anti-dsDNA positive &#8226; Insulin-dependent diabetes mellitus &#8226; Fungal eshagophagitis (Stage IV?) &#8226; Recurrent urinary tract infections (caused by Pseudomonas and Enterococcus) &#8226; Infection of the urinary tract (including the urethra) with a blood clot or a blood clot in the urethra</topic><topic number="14">Patient is a 70-year-old man with COPD and baseline O2 requirement of 2.5 to 3.5 liters He has obstructive sleep apnea (OSA), obesity hypoventilation syndrome and diastolic CHF (dCHF) He was previously discharged from the hospital on [2132-8-24] He is currently re-hospitalized with agitation and altered mental status, and hypoxia is also noted; despite being given 5 liters of O2 with BiPAP, his O2 saturation was in the 70s. Initially, the patient was very agitated, then he became somnolent. The patient's daughter reported that the patient's agitation and altered mental status had increased over the past 23 days and his O2 saturation was between 60 and 70 during his stay at home. He also noticed that the patient's feet were swollen and gained weight, which led to contact with the patient's PCP. In this context, the dose of Lasix was increased from 80 mg to 100 mg daily, which resulted in a slight improvement in folia. Patient has decreased appetite, reduced mouth intake and energy levels and difficulty performing daily activities at home No recent fever, cough, chills, production of a cough, chest pain, stomach pain or other new symptoms; however, chronic pain in right thigh for the past 12 months The patient's daughter also reported that the patient was taking medication regularly and using BiPAP correctly at night. Previous history of disease: &#8226; CAD; followed by 4-vessel CABG in [2119] &#8226; CHF; EF 55%, mild AS &#8226; Obesity hypoventilation syndrome &#8226; Obstructive sleep apnea &#8226; DM2 &#8226; Ventricular tachycardia; followed by ICD in [2127] &#8226; Hypothyroidism &#8226; Schizophrenia &#8226; COPD &#8226; Pneumonia; treated at [Hospital1] on [47]</topic><topic number="15">Patient is a 70-year-old female with a previous history of CAD Recently, a flesh-puddle was found in his stomach. He arrived at the hospital with fever/shaking and bandemia For several weeks before admission, he had been experiencing pain in the middle of his abdomen, which was spreading to his left flank. Pain is present throughout the day, does not increase with eating, but is accompanied by vomiting and coughing [4-20]-date CT abdomen without contrast, showing a heterogeneous flesh pool of 9.5 x 7.5 x 6.0 cm in size in the left upper abdomen Patient biopsy with EUS Biopsy results indicate pancreatic adenocarcinoma, which is located at the head of the pancreas CT also shows a flesh pimple on the splenic flexure/pancreatic tail, which is likely a diverticular abscess, as the patient may have a recent history of diverticulitis It is diagnosed as an infected fluid buildup or abscess Patient is treated with IV antibiotics (Zosyn, followed by ceftriaxone and Flagyl) and continues to receive these medications until outpatient review of ID is completed. Previous history of disease: Coronary artery disease; angioplasty performed in the last year [State 108] Mitral valve prolapse Atrial fibrillation Hyperlipemia Hypertension Chronic kidney disease (SCr 2.1, [3-17]) Hypothyroidism (TSH 10, [3-17]) Anemia (HCT 30.7, [3-17]) The following are the most common causes of hypertension in the United States:</topic><topic number="16">Patient is a 79-year-old female with multifactorial chronic hypoxemia and dyspnea. It was diagnosed as a cause of diastolic CHF. He suffers from pulmonary hypertension, which is thought to be caused by chronic ASD and COPD. The patient uses 5 liters of oxygen at home and is currently hospitalized with increasing respiratory problems. Cardiology recommended right heart catheterization to evaluate response to sildenafil, but the patient was reluctant to do so. As recommended by Pulmonary, a compassionate, empiric sildenafil trial is given to patients with severe dyspnea that affects outpatient quality of life. In the inpatient trial, the patient was able to tolerate it and no hypotension was observed. Since prior authorisation has been obtained, the patient will undergo outpatient follow-up with pulmonology, to allow for the long-term initiation of sildenafil Previous history of disease: Atrial septal defect repair ([6-17]), which is complicated by sinus arrest and is established by PPM Diastolic CHF, estimated dry weight 94 kg Pulmonary hypertension (RSVP 75, [11-24]), chronic ASD-related COPD, O2 at home 5L NC, baseline saturation OSA below 90 from late 80s, CPAP not used appropriately Mild mitral regurgitation Microcytic anemia Hypothyroidism Appendectomy and Cholecystectomy have been performed previously ([33]) Gallstone pancreatitis, ERCP and sphincterotomy have been performed subsequently Elevated alkaline phosphatase, amiodarone</topic><topic number="17">The patient is a 64-year-old woman with multiple myeloma. He's had previous allogeneic transplants and the disease has returned He also has systemic amyloidosis, which has affected his lungs, tongue, bladder, and heart. Patient is currently on hemodialysis due to ESRD and arrived at hospital with 2 days of malaise, weakness, and generalized body aching. Last week he was hospitalized for hypercalcemia and treated with pamidronate 30 mg, calcitonin, and dialysis. The patient is initially treated with melphalan and prednisone, followed by a VAD regimen and an autologous stem cell transplant. After his myeloma returned, he received treatment with thalidomide and velcade, which was later suspended due to swelling and worsening kidney function.</topic><topic number="18">This is a 78-year-old male with a history of BPH and has undergone multiple urological procedures, including a suprapubic prostatectomy. Patient had low urine output and a bladder scan showed a residual of 360 cc. Staff were unable to insert the foley catheter. Urology was consulted and they performed a flexible cystoscopy in the ICU. There they found a severe 2 cm bulbar urethral stricture. They were able to insert a small catheter and put it in. The patient has a leak around the catheter, then the catheter finally comes out. But afterwards, the patient's urine output was good. Post-void bladder scans are done every 4 hours to ensure that residual volume is not increased. Urology recommends that when the patient is stable, he be taken to the OR and his stricture fixed with surgery.</topic><topic number="19">Patient is a 65-year-old male with a prior history of CAD, prior MI, HLD, hypertension, ventricular tachycardia, and unconsciousness He was admitted this morning for fainting and evaluation of ventricular arrhythmias. After a series of unconsciousness tests, he was discharged from the hospital. A cardiac monitoring device has also been installed. The monitor was tested at OSH and reported that yesterday's monitor showed: 40 seconds of VT, followed by bradycardia at a rate of 39, which is consistent with the patient's symptoms. Patient was on telemetry at night and went into monomorphic VT. Patient found unconscious; pulse not clear CPR is initiated and within a minute the patient is back in sinus rhythm. The patient reported no symptoms prior to this incident. The patient is currently experiencing symptoms of fainting and nausea, but denies chest pain. Patient will be transferred to CCU for catheterization and EPS</topic><topic number="20">Patient is a 35-year-old female with a previous history of acne and mild hirsutism. Initial assessment of testosterone levels is elevated Recently she has noticed the growth of her arms and legs and feels that her finger rings are getting smaller Her menstrual cycle is a little irregular and there's some nipple discharge. Patient has a positive history for snoring and headache Physical examination may detect subtle features of the face of acromegaly and prognathism Normal according to visual fields confrontation Hirsutism, thickening of soft tissue and diaphoresis of the hands and feet may be observed IGF-1 at 968 ng/mL and random GH at 19.7 ng/mL in laboratory evaluation (fasting state) MRI shows a macroadenoma, not an invasion. The patient has been on a stable dose of octreotide LAR since diagnosis was confirmed. She is married and a mother of two children Currently using an IUD for birth control</topic><topic number="21">Patient is a 57-year-old male who has been reported with stomach pain and vomiting. Gradual onset of pain, which is in the epigastric and periumbilical areas and spreads to the back, approximately 20 hours prior He drinks about 60 units of alcohol a week and smokes about 22 cigarettes a day. He's generally healthy and has no history of medication or allergies. Family history of type 2 diabetes (his father and sister) He lives alone and has no children. Physical examination found the abdomen soft but painful to the touch. Bowel sounds are normal. His heart rate is 115 beats per minute and his blood pressure is 110/75 mm Hg. Laboratory tests found significantly higher leukocytosis (WBC 19.5), urea 8.5, CRP (145) and amylase (1200) and blood sugar levels of 15. Cross-sectional imaging found no evidence of obstructive pancreatitis</topic><topic number="22">Patient is a 31-year-old female who came in with abdominal pain. The pain started last night, as a disturbance in the abdomen. He had a hunger and a general weakness. The pain intensifies in the morning and becomes sharp At the same time, the pain is concentrated in the right lower abdomen. Patient's temperature is normal and vital signs are fine. Palpation of the right lower abdomen on physical examination can detect pain and guarding in the area. Palpation of the left abdomen causes pain in the right side Laboratory tests have found significant leukocytosis. CT abdomen with contrast showing distended appendix, with wall thickened; however, no evidence of perforation, abscess or gangrene Patient is a candidate for laparoscopic appendectomy under general anesthesia</topic><topic number="23">The patient is a 39-year-old male who came to the clinic with cough and shortness of breath, which was not relieved by his inhaler. These symptoms have been present for 5 days in the last 2 weeks Last week he doubled his dosage of oral corticosteroids. The patient is a chef and has a three-year history of asthma. He often feels coughing, wheezing, shortness of breath and tightness in the chest These symptoms become more uncomfortable within 12 hours of starting work each day and increase throughout the week. Symptoms resolve in 12 hours when off duty Spirometry shows that the forced expiratory volume (FEV1) in the first second is 63% of the predicted value. The patient's previous history of seasonal allergic rhinitis during the summer is significant He does not smoke or use illegal drugs. His father and sister have a family history of asthma. Currently he is using inhaled corticosteroid (ICS) and fluticasone 500 mcg/salmeterol 50 mcg, one puff twice a day</topic><topic number="24">Patient is a 55-year-old male who presented to his primary care physician with lower urinary tract symptoms, including frequency, urgency, weak stream, incomplete urination and intermittent flow. These symptoms have been going on for the last nine months. The subsequent evaluation found: IPSS score: 15 Post-void residual: 70 mL Prostate volume (TRUS): 60 mL Prostate-specific antigen (PSA) level: 3.2 ng/mL Maximum flow rate: 10 mL/sec when urine volume was 130 mL He is generally healthy and only taking Vit D 1000 units daily Recent (3 days ago) blood test results were normal: Hgb: 13.5 g/dl WBC: 135,000 /mm3 Plt: 350,000 /ml PT: 11 seconds PTT: 35 seconds INR: 0.9 Creatinine: 0.5 mg/dl BUN: 10 mg/dl Urine test (U/A) found: Color: Yellow state: pH in solution: 5.3 Specific gravity: 1.010 Sugars: 100 Nitrite: absent Ketone: absent Leukocyte esterase: absent RBC: absent WBC: 2 WBCs/hpf Urine biota test (U/C): biota is not found</topic><topic number="25">The patient is a 42-year-old postmenopausal woman who underwent a screening sonogram, where an abnormality was detected in her right breast. Breast examination found no tangible tissue A subsequent core biopsy was performed to diagnose infiltrating ductal breast carcinoma 1.8 cm in size in the upper outer quadrant of the left breast. Then a lumpectomy was performed and no cancer cells were found in the surgical margins. The tumor was HER2-positive and ER/PR-negative Axillary sampling detects cancer cells in 1 out of 12 lymph nodes Chest X-ray was normal. The patient is currently taking a daily well women multivitamin and is not taking any other medications. He smokes regularly and drinks alcohol occasionally. He is in a relationship with only one partner She has a history of three pregnancies and live births and has breastfed all three of her children.</topic><topic number="26">The patient is a 45-year-old woman who was referred to the emergency department with a history of stomach pain, nausea and vomiting for about 4 days and 2 vomiting episodes. The pain is confined to the epigastric region and is spreading to the right upper abdomen. The pain increases after eating fatty foods He's experienced the same pain twice in the past year. Patient has a history of prior illness with hypercholesterolemia and two C-sections She has two children and is menopausal. He doesn't smoke, drink alcohol, or use any illegal drugs. He has a slight fever on physical examination. His vital signs are: &#8226; Blood pressure: 150/85 mmHg &#8226; Heart rate: 115/min &#8226; Breathing rate: 15/min &#8226; Temperature: 38.2&#176;C &#8226; SpO2: 98% (room air) Abdominal palpation shows tenderness in the epigastric region and upper right side, but no rebound tenderness Bowel sounds are normal. Laboratory tests found increased ESR and leukocytosis with left shift Ultrasound detects multiple gallstones and biliary sludge; the largest gallstone is 0.7 cm (0.4 in) in size. Elective cholecystectomy is recommended for the patient as per the surgical consultation.</topic><topic number="27">Patient is a 53-year-old male who has been suffering from chronic HCV infection for the past 2 years. His previous medical history includes significant inguinal hernia surgery at only 20 years old. For the past 9 months, he has been receiving a combination of IFN (100 mg/week) and RBV (400 mg/day) Six months ago, direct-acting antiviral drugs were added to his treatment. Patient's medical records include information of previous multiple HCV RNA positive and evidence of enzyme immunoassay positive for anti-HCV antibody Recent liver biopsy tests found no evidence of hepatocellular carcinoma and noted chronic inflammation consistent with chronic viral hepatitis. There was no evidence of alcoholic liver disease, bleeding from esophageal varices, hemochromatosis, autoimmune hepatitis or any metabolic liver disease. Physical examination shows the patient is awake and not showing any signs of serious illness. His vital signs are: &#8226; Blood pressure: 130/75 mmHg &#8226; Heart rate: 90/min &#8226; BMI: 27 abdomen is soft and there is no ascites or tenderness Lower extremities (legs) normal and no swelling observed</topic><topic number="28">The patient is a 60-year-old Spanish man who has been in the hospital for almost a day with breathing difficulties. Symptoms started suddenly and have gradually increased He's had COPD for the last two years. Spirometry test found 60% of the predicted value of post-bronchodilator FEV1/FVC He smokes 20 cigarettes a day. The patient has a history of previous disease with significant BPH and is using Flomax for it Her brother has a family history of high blood pressure. His list of medications includes Duo-Neb inhaled, as needed and every 4 hours, Vit D3 1000 units daily and Flomax for BPH. The patient is paralyzed and seriously ill, but alert and aware of his surroundings. Vital signs are as follows: &#8226; Blood pressure: 135/80 mmHg &#8226; Breathing rate: 25/minute &#8226; Heart rate: 75/minute &#8226; BMI: 40 &#8226; Oxygen saturation (O2sat): 90%</topic><topic number="29">The patient is a 24-year-old male who has been suffering from type 1 diabetes for 11 years. He arrived at the emergency department with symptoms of hyperglycaemia and possible diabetic ketoacidosis, as he had not taken insulin for three days. The patient said that he is currently homeless and has lost his insulin, needles, glucometer and blood glucose testing equipment. The patient stated that at the time of initial diagnosis of type 1 diabetes, her blood sugar level was &gt;1000 mg/dL and she was suffering from polyuria, polydipsia and polyphagia. He said he has been taking insulin since then and has never been prescribed oral medication for diabetes. He is currently taking insulin glargine 55 units once daily and insulin aspart three times daily according to the sliding scale. The patient has had several previous cases of diabetic ketoacidosis, for which he was hospitalized. In this hyperglycemia, he does not feel any nausea, vomiting or abdominal discomfort and does not appear to be sick at all The results of the laboratory tests on the patient are as follows: &#8226; A1c: 11.3% &#8226; Creatinine: 0.9 mg/dL, eGFR &gt;60 mL/min &#8226; Aspartate aminotransferase (AST): 17 U/L &#8226; Alanine aminotransferase (ALT): 14 U/L &#8226; Beta-hydroxybutyrate: 0.1 mmol/L &#8226; Bicarbonate: 25 mEq/L &#8226; Anion Gap: 14 mEq/L</topic><topic number="30">Patient is a 33-year-old female who has presented with fatigue, weight gain and irregular bleeding during menstruation. There's no sign of hirsutism or nipple discharge. His BMI is 34. Laboratory tests found high levels of TSH (13 mU/L) and low levels of free T4 (0.2 ng/dl) The anti-TPO level is very high (120 IU/ml) His condition was diagnosed as Hashimoto's thyroiditis. His PC, brother and mother all have the same disease. After starting Levothyroxine 250 mcg daily, the patient's symptoms improved significantly and her menstrual periods returned to normal. She's still overweight, BMI is 31. All results except for anti-TPO are within normal range according to his latest thyroid profile: &#8226; TSH: 2.35 mU/L &#8226; Free T4: 2.7 ng/dl &#8226; Anti-TPO: 75 IU/ml</topic><topic number="31">The patient is a 37-year-old woman who came to the clinic for a Pap smear as part of a routine health check-up. The test revealed that she had stage 1B cervical cancer. Her HPV test was positive for HPV type 16. The patient's sexual history indicates that he has had three sexual partners and has four children. He's done tubal ligation before He smoked for a long time and drank frequently In other ways, he is fine. As a treatment, she was offered a radical hysterectomy.</topic><topic number="32">The patient is a 17-year-old boy who has been complaining of vomiting, bloodless diarrhea, stomach pain, fever, chills and hunger pangs for the past 3 days. He had eaten a salad in a restaurant before the diarrhea started Physical examination of the patient may show pale skin, jaundice and abdominal pain Laboratory test results are as follows: &#8226; Hemoglobin: 9.7 g/dL &#8226; Platelet: 110,000 /cu.mm &#8226; Creatinine: 3.6 mg/dL &#8226; Blood urea nitrogen (BUN): 73 mg/dL &#8226; Direct bilirubin: 2.4 mg/dL &#8226; Lactate dehydrogenase (LDH): 881 IU/L (normal: 110265 IU/L) Medium number of schistocytes and helmet cells were found in the peripheral blood smear Shiga-like toxin-producing E. coli (STEC) stx1/stx2 was detected in the faeces. The patient has no other underlying medical conditions and is not currently taking any medications.</topic><topic number="33">The patient is a 42-year-old healthy woman who came to the clinic for a flu shot in early October. He works at a rehab center and has no underlying medical condition. This year, he is getting his first vaccine. She has been married for 5 years and uses barrier methods for birth control. Her menstrual cycle is irregular He does not smoke and is not currently taking any medication. He exercises regularly - at least 30 minutes a day, at least 5 days a week He has no history of allergies to food or medication. His previous surgical history includes tonsillectomy. In other ways, he's perfectly healthy.</topic><topic number="34">The patient is a 47-year-old Asian woman who reports experiencing chronic depression. He lost interest in activities that once gave him pleasure He said that his mood has been depressed for the last three weeks. He is also suffering from malnutrition, which has resulted in a weight loss of about 5 kg. She says that she feels powerless and worthless almost every day. He doesn't use drugs, smokes or drinks alcohol. He used to exercise at least 30 minutes a day, but he has not been able to do so for the last three weeks due to lack of energy. He's also been having some digestive problems lately. She is married, has 4 children and is menopausal. Her husband has recently been diagnosed with colon cancer and is about to start chemotherapy. The patient has no significant prior medical history and her medical history only includes Vit D3 1000 units daily intake. No family history of mental illness. Patient's HAM-D score is 20.</topic><topic number="35">Patient is a 15-year-old girl with a history of frequent headaches on both sides of her head. Headaches occur twice or more a week and last for about a day or less each time The pain is of a pulsating nature and intensity, which is interfering with his daily activities. Headache with nausea and light discomfort She recently noticed that headaches during menstruation are increasing. She has been diagnosed with migraine headaches and is being treated. He is a high school student and lives with both parents. He loves to read and spends his free time in a public library near his home. She is also interested in writing stories and has written many short stories in English. He rarely exercises. Her BMI is 21 and her blood pressure is 100/60 mmHg. Physical examination found no significant abnormalities</topic><topic number="36">Patient is a 32-year-old obese woman who came to the clinic with weight concerns. He is 5'5" tall and weighs 113 pounds. He mainly talks about sleep apnea, PCO and dissatisfaction with his body shape. She is a high school teacher and has been married for 5 years She has not used any contraceptive for the past 4 months and has no previous pregnancy history He doesn't smoke or use drugs. She is interested in dieting and exercise to lose weight He completed the four square step test in 14 seconds. His physical condition: blood pressure 130/80 mmHg, heart rate 195/min and BMI 41.54 Blood test results: &#8226; FBS: 98 mg/dl &#8226; TG: 150 mg/dl &#8226; Cholesterol: 180 mg/dl &#8226; LDL: 90 mg/dl &#8226; HDL: 35 mg/dl Her heart rate is normal, and her osteoarthritis and ROM are within the normal range</topic><topic number="37">Patient is a 20-year-old Caucasian female who has been in clinic for one day with loss of vision on one side, facial weakness, slurred speech and facial numbness. He went to his PCP and had an MRI of his brain, which showed a plaque on his brain stem. After a few months he felt weakness in his lower leg, which caused problems with his balance. The second MRI showed another lesion in the left cerebral hemisphere. Diagnosis of relapsing remitting multiple sclerosis (RRMS) confirmed after a second MRI Her history of surgery is notable, two years ago, C-section, and she has a child. She's divorced and currently has no sexual relationship. He smoked 10 cigarettes a day and drank alcohol occasionally. She works as an editor at a publishing house and is happy to work from home most of the time. He's been in treatment for RRMS for seven months.</topic><topic number="38">Patient is a 35-year-old female with myasthenia gravis, class IIa. He complains of diplopia, fatigue and weakness, which mainly affects his upper extremities. His anti-AChR antibody test was positive and single fiber electromyography (SFEMG) also came out positive. He's on pyridostigmine 60 mg three times a day. However, there are still some symptoms that are interfering with his professional work. He's a research coordinator and has three children. Her 70-year-old father has high blood pressure. He does not smoke or use illegal drugs. He occasionally drinks alcohol at social events. His physical and laboratory tests found no other significant abnormalities. The following are the physical and laboratory test values: &#8226; Blood pressure: 110/75 mmHg &#8226; Hgb: 11 g/dl &#8226; WBC: 8,000/mm3 &#8226; Plt: 300,000/ml &#8226; Creatinine: 0.5 mg/dl &#8226; BUN: 10 mg/dl &#8226; Beta hCG: Negative for pregnancy</topic><topic number="39">Patient is a 3-day-old Asian female who has been present with jaundice that started the day before. She was born at 38 weeks and 3 days of uncomplicated pregnancy. Family history is not important The baby is breast-feeding Vital signs: lower abdominal temperature: 36.3&#176;C Heart rate: 154 beats/min Breathing rate: 37 breaths/min Blood pressure: 65/33 mm Mercury body measurements: Weight: 3.2 kg Height: 53 cm Head circumference: 36 cm Physical examination: The whites of the eyes are yellow and the inner membrane of the heart and lungs auscultation found no murmurs or other abnormalities Normal laboratory test results on mechanical and pleural palpation: total bilirubin: 212 mg/dL Direct bilirubin: 140.4 mg/dL AST: 37 ALT: 20 ULT: 20 ULT: 74 GGT: 75 UL Alkaline: 51 UL L Eq: 35 mg/dL CR: 45 mg/dL Neonatal blood count: 2 UQ: 35 kL Neonatal count: 2 kL Neonatal count: 4 kL Neonatal count: 3 kL Neonatal count: 4 kL Neonatal count: 3 kL</topic><topic number="40">The patient is a 60-year-old male who has complained of recurrent headaches, generalized bone pain, and difficulty chewing that started six years ago, and they're increasing. Physical examination revealed swelling around the molar region on both sides of the face. Folic acid levels have been rising since his last test. There are also multiple extraoral lesions on the head and face. The swollen areas are not sensitive and are attached to the bone Subsequent evaluation has shown an increase in radioactive substance uptake and an increase in urinary pyridinoline. His serum alkaline phosphatase is 300 IU/L, which is much higher than the normal limit (44 &#215; 147 IU/L). The only notable family history is her mother's high blood pressure and her father's type 2 diabetes mellitus. He has been diagnosed with Paget's Disease of Bone and will be started on Bisphosphonate as the first course of treatment.</topic><topic number="41">Patient is a 57-year-old farmer who was diagnosed with Parkinson's disease a year ago. He feels the slow movement and the trembling His previous medical history includes high blood pressure and hypercholesterolemia. He lives with his wife. They have three children. Before his diagnosis, he was active in farm work, such as farming and taking care of livestock. Patient complains of tremors and slow movement He had trouble getting through a door, because his body suddenly became stiff and he needed help getting through the door. His handwriting is getting smaller. He's currently on Levodopa and Trihexyphenidyl. He says the medication has helped improve his tremors and slowness of movement. But he still has difficulty starting to move, muscle stiffness and general slowness. He is a vigilant and cooperative individual, with no signs of dementia. He does not smoke or use illegal drugs.</topic><topic number="42">Patient is a 19-year-old pregnant Hispanic female, G1P1, who is 32 weeks and 6 days pregnant. He has been presenting at OB clinic for regular health check up with mild headache and swollen feet. Preliminary assessment found his blood pressure was 146/99 mmHg and urine dipstick was 3+ protein. His blood pressure and U/A were normal in previous health tests. A few hours later, his blood pressure was re-evaluated to 150/100 mmHg. Laboratory tests showed normal hematocrit, platelet count, and liver transaminase. He is feeling tired, but no fever or cold. He mentions headaches, but no change in vision. No signs of breathing, cough, chest pain, sleep apnea, chest tightness or skin rash Physical examination showed no abdominal pain, change in bowel habits, nausea or vomiting, pain during urination, frequent urination, blood or foamy urine Swelling in the foot noted, but no joint pain or back pain. She has no prior history of any significant illness and is taking only prenatal vitamins. Family history of DM type 2 and hypertension He drinks socially, but has no history of smoking or drug use. She has had only one partner in the past two years and has not used any form of birth control. At the first visit, when she was six weeks pregnant, her BMI was 24. She gained weight naturally throughout her pregnancy.</topic><topic number="43">Patient is a 60-year-old woman who was admitted to the stroke department. He recently took a second course of intravenous antibiotics for aspiration pneumonia. She has a fever and she mentions abdominal pain and diarrhea (ejaculating 8 times in 3 hours, each time with a lot of acid, liquid stool) Patient's entire abdomen is tender and swollen, with hyperactive bowel sounds. He has a fever (38.4&#176;C), tachycardic (113/minute) and hypotensive (80/40 mmHg) Clostridium difficile toxin was found in the stool.</topic><topic number="44">Patient is a 14-year-old boy who complains of scoliosis and back pain. He has no other medical problems. He used to be able to play regular sports, like basketball and soccer, but recently he's had trouble doing those. Pain is in the legs and back and increases with physical activity He likes to lie down most of the time. He is unhappy with his posture and mentions the unevenness of his shoulders and the tilting of his head to the right. The patient is a well-groomed, well-groomed teenager who is alert and cooperative. Left shoulder slightly higher than right shoulder His scoliotic curve is measured at 45 degrees. Patient is a candidate for surgery for scoliosis according to perioperative MEP monitoring</topic><topic number="45">Patient is a 34-year-old African American male with a history of sickle cell disease who came to the clinic with severe bone pain. The patient had severe lower back pain, which extended to both sides of the thigh, and the pain level was 9/10. Patient has a history of sickle cell crises since childhood Also, he's been experiencing similar symptoms for the past two weeks, which have not been helped by treatment with oxycodone. His PCP sent him to the emergency room, so he could take intravenous pain medication. Patient has no fever and blood pressure is normal. Physical examination found no splenomegaly He has no history of drug allergy. He does not smoke or use illegal drugs. The results of the laboratory tests are as follows: Hgb: 8 g/dl WBC: 10,000 /mm3 Plt: 300,000 /ml MCV: 106 fL Hemoglobin electrophoresis: 91% HbS, 6% HbF, 3% HbA2 AST: 22 U/L ALT: 43 U/L Alk P: 53 U/L Ferritin: 1200 ng/ml The following is the list of the laboratory tests performed:</topic><topic number="46">Patient A is a 30-year-old male who was admitted to hospital with 10 days of coughing, excessive night sweats and malnutrition. He had travelled to India a month ago and has no history of getting a TB vaccine. He used to be healthy and worked as an engineer in a high-tech company He does not smoke or use illegal drugs. Physical examination showed he had a fever (38&#176;C), a heart rate of 115 beats/minute, a respiratory rate of 22, a blood pressure of 125/75 mmHg, and a blood O2 level of 97%. Chest X-ray shows a 1.8 cm diameter infiltrate in the middle of the left lung, with signs of cavitation The sputum smear found Mycobacterium tuberculosis in his saliva, which is sensitive to the first-line TB drugs (isoniazid, streptomycin, rifampicin and ethambutol). The results of the laboratory tests are as follows: &#8226; Hgb: 13 g/dl &#8226; WBC: 14,000 /mm3 &#8226; Plt: 300,000 /ml &#8226; AST: 13 U/L &#8226; ALT: 15 U/L &#8226; Alk P: 53 U/L &#8226; Total bilirubin: 0.6 mg/dl &#8226; Na: 137 mEq/l &#8226; K: 4 mEq/l &#8226; Creatinine: 0.5 mg/dl &#8226; BUN: 10 mg/dl &#8226; ESR: 120 mm/hr &#8226; The test was performed on a sample of blood taken from a patient with a blood clot in the colon.</topic><topic number="47">Patient is a 62-year-old African-American male who presents with weakness in the left arm and leg, black eye in the right eye, loss of sensation in the right side of the face, relaxation of facial muscles, and speech indistinctness. He did not report any history of breathing, headache, irregular heartbeat, chest pain, fever, dizziness, difficulty controlling stool or urine, or unconsciousness. He has a history of high blood pressure, hyperlipidemia and hypothyroidism. He has been smoking a pack of cigarettes a day for the past 40 years and drinking 56 beers a week He is unaware of his family's history of the disease. He is currently taking Levothyroxine, Atorvastatin and HTCZ His vital signs were stable at initial assessment. Physical examination has shown relaxation of the left facial muscle, dysarthria and left hemiplegia His National Institutes of Health Stroke Scale (NIHSS) score was 7. No acute intracranial finding on primary CT angiogram of head and neck Patient has been administered intravenous recombinant tissue plasminogen activator (t-PA) and started high-dose statin therapy He was then placed in the ICU for 24 hours of observation. Head MRI detected an acute infarct measuring 1.7 cm in size in the right periventricular white matter and posterior basal ganglia</topic><topic number="48">Fernandez is a 41-year-old man who is a professional soccer player. He came to the clinic with itchy feet. Physical examination revealed scaling and maceration between the third and fourth toes of his right foot. The area is red and painful, with a slight fissuring. But the upper and lower parts of the foot are intact. No scabs or tearing found at the affected site He didn't apply any ointment to the wound and has no history of any previous medical conditions such as DM. He smokes 15 cigarettes a day and drinks a beer a day Her family history includes hyperlipidemia in her mother and MI in her father. He has multiple partners and uses condoms during sexual intercourse His physical and laboratory tests were normal in other respects. Microscopic KOH wet mount tests showed segmented fungal hyphae and confirmed Tinea pedis infection</topic><topic number="49">A 12-year-old girl comes to the clinic with her mother complaining of short stature, delayed puberty and developmental delay. His karyotype study found 45X, which confirmed the diagnosis of Turner syndrome. She has been on GH for the past 6 months; however, estrogen therapy was not given to delay menarche and achieve ideal height. Physical examination revealed her as obese and mentally retarded. Her breasts are in the early stages of development and there is no thick hair on the genitals or buttocks. His last lab test was TSH 3 and FBS 75 mg/dl.</topic><topic number="50">A 5-month-old boy was brought to the pediatric surgery clinic with a hollow on the right side of his ankle. The baby is the first of the family to be born from a healthy mother's womb at 38 weeks via NVD. Mother's pregnancy was normal without any complications At birth, the baby weighs 3,200 grams and is 50 centimeters long. He is currently breastfeeding, and weighs 6.5 kg and is 62 cm tall. Physical evaluation showed no developmental delay. Physical examination found a testicle in the left atrium, but no testicle in the right atrium. His penis is normal in shape and size, and he's not circumcised. Diagnostic laparoscopy has identified an abdominal undescended testis</topic><topic number="51">Patient is a 25-year-old G1P1 pregnant female, 24 weeks and 3 days pregnant. She came to the clinic with a sudden onset of fever and cold, accompanied by nausea and vomiting. He also complains of pain during urination, urge to urinate and frequent urination. He also has severe pain in the abdominal area. Vital signs: Temperature: 39.7oC Heart rate: 117/min Breathing rate: 20/min Blood pressure: 113/74 mmHg Physical examination: Sensitivity was noted at both costovertebral angles No history of recurrent UTI or other illness prior to conception Tests for the presence of bacteria in urine found Gram-negative rod-shaped bacterial cells, leukocytes and leukocyte casts No germs found in the blood. Blood test results: Hb: 12.9 g/dL Hct: 39% MCV: 76 fL WBC count: 14,120/&#956;L The following is a list of the most commonly used drugs in the United States.</topic><topic number="52">The patient is a 34-year-old male who has been in the clinic since yesterday with dizziness and severe diarrhea. He returned from an international trip a few days ago and spent a month in a camp in Sudan. Initially, he experienced abdominal pain, but then he started to have bloating, nausea and soft stools. Soon, his large amount of water causes odorless diarrhea. The stool is watery and white, but the patient has no fever. Vital signs: &#8226; Blood pressure: 95/62 mm Hg when lying down &#8226; Blood pressure: 75/40 mm Hg when standing &#8226; Heart rate: 110/min Physical examination: &#8226; Patient appears ill, facial mucosa is dry &#8226; Skin elasticity is reduced in fecal examination: &#8226; V. cholerae detected in dark-field microscopy of a sample of freshly discarded feces Laboratory test results: &#8226; Sodium: 137 meq/L &#8226; Potassium: 2 meq/L &#8226; Chloride: 94 meq/L &#8226; CO2: 15 meq/L &#8226; Fecal leukocytes: not seen &#8226; Fecal occult blood: not found</topic><topic number="53">The patient is a 34-year-old woman from Jordan who came to the clinic with complaints of general and unspecified pain in her bones and joints. He is married and has three children. No previous medical history or medication. Physical measurements: &#8226; BMI: 23 &#8226; Blood pressure: 120/75 mmHg &#8226; Heart rate: 75/min Laboratory test results: &#8226; Vitamin D: 14 ng/ml &#8226; Other tests are normal: o Calcium: 9.2 mg/dl o Phosphorus: 3.2 mg/dl o PTH: 28 pg/ml The following are the most commonly reported:</topic><topic number="54">Patient is a 57-year-old male who was admitted to the clinic with 4 months of weight loss and chronic dry cough. Computed tomography of the chest shows multiple infiltrates in both upper lobes of the lungs and thickening of the bronchial walls. His medical records list the serum as MPO-ANCA positive. Transbronchial biopsy found necrotic granulomas and multinucleated giant cells, and therefore her disease was diagnosed as Wegener's granulomatosis. He's been on corticosteroids and cyclophosphamide for the past four months. His Birmingham Vasculitis Activity Score (BVAS) has been above 4 since the onset of the disease. He had a physical and a lab test yesterday. The results are as follows: &#8226; A healthy, well-nourished, non-icteric, cooperative and alert individual &#8226; Weight: 73 kg &#8226; Height: 177 cm &#8226; Blood pressure: 120/80 mmHg &#8226; Heart rate: 90 /min &#8226; Breathing rate: 22 /min Laboratory test results: &#8226; Hgb: 13 g/dl &#8226; WBC: 8000 /mm3 (Neutrophil: 2700 /mm3) &#8226; Plt: 300,000 /ml &#8226; AST: 40 U/L &#8226; ALT: 56 U/L &#8226; Alk P: 147 U/L &#8226; Total bilirubin: 1.2 mg/dl &#8226; ESR: 1/20 mmHg &#8226; MPO-ANCA: 15 EU3</topic><topic number="55">A 22-year-old Caucasian male came to the clinic complaining of hand tremors for over a year. The tremor first appeared in his right hand, when he was holding an object. The tremor then becomes permanent and spreads to both arms and legs, even during rest. The Kayser-Fleischer ring was found in the eye examination. Physical examination has shown jaundice, hepatosplenomegaly and hypotonia in the upper limbs. Despite his constant smile, he was described by his parents as aggressive. Laboratory tests found significantly lower serum caeruloplasmin (0.05 g/l) and increased copper excretion in 24-hour urine (120 &#956;g/24 h). His disease was confirmed as Wilson disease by high liver copper concentration (305 &#956;g/g dry weight of liver).</topic><topic number="56">Patient is a 41-year-old male who has acromegaly and underwent transsphenoidal surgery 4 months ago. He's been in the clinic for regular lab tests since his original surgery. Lab tests found her IGF-1 level at 4.5 for both sex and age, which is the highest value in the normal range. His random GH level is 4 &#956;g/L. Recent MRI of the brain confirmed the presence of residual tumors in the pituitary. Previous medical history only pituitary adenoma-related acromegaly and recent surgery are notable After the surgery, he's only taking vitamin D and multivitamins.</topic><topic number="57">The patient is a 41-year-old obese woman who was brought to the emergency room with complaints of abdominal pain and vomiting. The pain started gradually from yesterday and is localized to the epigastric and periumbilical regions, which are spreading to the back. He regularly drinks alcohol and does not smoke She has no history of allergies and she only takes multivitamins every day. Family history of illness Her mother has high blood pressure She lives with her husband and has three children. Physical examination of the abdomen is tender and soft, and bowel sounds are normal. His heart rate is 115 beats per minute and his blood pressure is 110/75 mm Hg. Notable results in laboratory tests: &#8226; Leucocytosis: 19.5 &#8226; Urea: 8.5 &#8226; CRP: 145 (high) &#8226; Amylase: 1200 (high) &#8226; Glucose: 15 A CT scan of the abdomen showed acute edematous interstitial pancreatitis including enlarged common bile duct and intrahepatic duct, which confirms gallstone pancreatitis Her pregnancy test is negative and she's not breastfeeding.</topic><topic number="58">The patient is a 17-year-old boy who has been coming to the clinic for four days with severe pain in the right lower abdomen. The pain is suddenly shifting from one place to another, and is accompanied by nausea and vomiting Physical examination showed he had fever and palpation of the abdomen showed tenderness, rebound tenderness and guarding. Laboratory tests showed an increase in WBC, with a predominance of neutrophils. CT scan found evidence of acute perforated appendicitis and free fluid in the pelvis. Diagnostic laparoscopy showed phlegmon, but no other abdominal abnormalities were found. He is currently a candidate for emergent laparoscopic appendectomy under general anesthesia.</topic><topic number="59">The patient is a 15-year-old boy who was diagnosed with asthma a year ago. He has come in complaining of shortness of breath, chest tightness and coughing. According to his mother, the patient had no effect from his usual corticosteroid inhaler. Patient admitted to emergency department for severe asthma exacerbation. He's a candidate for general corticosteroid therapy Spirometry shows 60% of his forced expiratory volume (FEV1) in the first second. His previous medical history is not significant. Family history includes his mother and uncle with asthma. He had previously been treated with a combination of inhaled corticosteroids and Zafirlukast.</topic><topic number="60">The patient is a 63-year-old male who has been in the emergency department for the past two days with a sudden inability to urinate. Abdominopelvic CT scan shows an enlarged prostate and a bladder full of urine. He's a candidate for urethral catheterization and TURP. Results of subsequent evaluation: &#8226; Post-void residual: 71 mL &#8226; Prostate volume (TRUS): 63 mL &#8226; Prostate-specific antigen (PSA) level: 3.5 ng/mL Recent blood test results (three days ago) were normal: &#8226; Hgb: 13.6 g/dl &#8226; WBC: 13300 /mm3 &#8226; Plt: 370,000 /ml &#8226; PT: 12 sec &#8226; PTT: 34 sec &#8226; INR: 0.9 &#8226; Creatinine: 0.5 mg/dl &#8226; BUN: 10 mg/dl Urine test results: &#8226; Color: yellow &#8226; Condition: rounded &#8226; pH: 5.3 &#8226; Specific gravity: 1.0 &#8226; Glc: 100 &#8226; Nitrite: &#8226; Ketone: no &#8226; Leukocyte ester: no &#8226; RBC: no &#8226; WBC: no RBC: no. 2 &#8226; WBC: no. 3 &#8226; WBC: no. 2 &#8226; WBC: no. 3 &#8226; WBC: no. 3 &#8226; WBC: no. 4 &#8226; WBC: no. 4 &#8226; WBC: no. 5 &#8226; WBC: no. 2 &#8226; WBC: no. 3 &#8226; WBC: no. 4 &#8226; WBC: no. 5 &#8226; WBC: no. 2</topic><topic number="61">Patient is a 45-year-old postmenopausal woman with cytologically confirmed breast cancer. Core biopsy found 3 cm invasive ductal breast carcinoma in the upper and outer region of the left breast The tumor is HER2-positive and ER/PR-negative Axillary sampling has detected 5 positive lymph nodes. Metastatic lesions were detected on his chest X-ray. Patient is currently taking multivitamins and iron supplements He doesn't smoke or drink alcohol. He is not sexually active and has no children. He's a candidate for tumor surgery and is willing to do it before chemotherapy.</topic><topic number="62">Patient is a 46-year-old male who has presented with dizziness and frequent headaches. He has a family history of CAD, but no other cardiovascular risk factors such as smoking, high blood pressure or diabetes mellitus, and is physically active. The patient's LDL-C and HDL-C levels were 545 and 53 mg/dL, respectively Her fasting glucose and triglyceride levels were 85 and 158 mg/dL, respectively, which are within normal limits. The patient is not taking any lipid-lowering medication. Neck auscultation detected a systolic murmur 3+/6+, which is spreading to the skull. Ultrasonography of the carotid arteries showed severe stenosis in the left internal carotid artery (LICA) and moderate stenosis in the right internal carotid artery (RICA), which was estimated to be 40%-50% The peak-systolic velocity (PSV) and end-diastolic velocity (EDV) for LICA are 208.5 cm/s and 54.5 cm/s respectively; the PSV for RICA is 91.72 cm/s and the EDV is 37.37 cm/s Plaque is seen on the anterior and posterior walls of the internal carotid artery and common carotid artery These are characterized as bulky plates, extending to the middle third of the internal coronary arteries (ICAs) and are mainly echogenic and hyperechoic, with less than 50% of the area being echolucent and the surface asymmetric.</topic><topic number="63">A 54-year-old obese woman was admitted to the emergency department with nausea and vomiting along with stomach pain that had started 4 days earlier. Epigastric pain spreads to the upper right abdomen and is aggravated after eating fatty foods He has experienced the same pain twice in the past year His previous medical history includes hypercholesterolemia and 2 NVDs. She has two children and is in menopause. He doesn't smoke, drink alcohol, or use any illegal drugs. She has a slight fever. His vital signs are: blood pressure 150/85 mmHg, heart rate 115/min, respiratory rate 15 times/min, temperature 38.2&#176;C, and blood oxygen level 98% (at room air) The patient is in a coma, but not in any serious discomfort. Palpation with epigastric area and right upper abdominal area tender, but no rebound tenderness Bowel sounds are normal. Lab tests found high ESR and leukocytosis with left shift. Ultrasound detected multiple gallstones, biliary sludge and common bile duct (CBD) stones The smallest stone is 14 mm.</topic><topic number="64">Patient is a 55-year-old male, who was diagnosed with HCV 2 years ago and has recently been diagnosed with co-infection with HBV His previous medical history is not significant. He has been taking IFN (Interferon), RBV (Ribavirin) and direct-acting antiviral drugs for the last 6 months He's not taking any other medication. His medical records indicate that he has previously tested positive for HCV RNA multiple times and tested positive for anti-HCV antibody enzyme immunoassay. Recent liver biopsy found no evidence of hepatocellular carcinoma; however, long-term inflammation was noted, which is consistent with chronic viral hepatitis There was no evidence of alcoholic liver disease, bleeding from esophageal varices, hemochromatosis, autoimmune hepatitis or metabolic liver disease. The patient is currently conscious and not experiencing any severe discomfort. His vital signs are: blood pressure 130/75 mmHg, heart rate 90 beats per minute and BMI 27. Abdominal examination found the abdomen to be soft; no ascites or any tenderness Lower extremities normal and no swelling noted</topic><topic number="65">The patient is a 25-year-old male, whose type 1 diabetes was confirmed by molecular analysis seven years ago. He has come to the clinic complaining of shortness of breath and fatigue during physical exertion. According to him, he had a slight shortness of breath after climbing the stairs to the third floor, but no shortness of breath at rest and no chest pain, which is consistent with the New York Heart Association (NYHA) class II. He's been diagnosed with cardiomyopathy, with plans to start treatment with ACE inhibitors and beta blockers. He is currently taking 70/30 insulin and vitamin D supplements No other significant pre-existing medical conditions Her family history includes her uncle and grandfather with type 1 DM The results of his laboratory tests are as follows: &#8226; FBS: 100 mg/dl &#8226; HbA1c: 6.5% &#8226; Cholesterol: 190 mg/dl &#8226; Triglycerides (TG): 140 mg/dl &#8226; LDL: 125 mg/dl &#8226; HDL: 40 mg/dl</topic><topic number="66">A 16-year-old girl comes to the clinic complaining of weight gain and irregular menstrual cycles Her BMI was 24, but she's gained five kilos in the last few weeks. She feels more tired than before and is not able to go dancing with her friends His laboratory tests showed significantly elevated TSH levels (15 mU/L) and low free T4 levels (0.18 ng/dl). The anti-TPO levels are also very high (136 IU/ml) Based on these results, he was diagnosed with Hashimoto's disease. He doesn't smoke and is not sexually active.</topic><topic number="67">A 54-year-old woman has an abnormal cervical squamous intraepithelial/glandular lesion on her Pap smear He tested positive for HPV 16. She is sexually active with her husband and has 4 children She's menopausal and doesn't use any contraception. He smokes and drinks alcohol regularly Otherwise, he is fine. He was advised to conization</topic><topic number="68">The patient is a 23-year-old male who was admitted to hospital with symptoms of high blood pressure (175/95 mmHg) and septicaemia. He's had respiratory failure and renal failure, so he's been put on mechanical ventilation and haemodialysis, respectively. His blood smear showed microangiopathic haemolytic anemia and thrombocytopenia. Blood test results showed high levels of lactate dehydrogenase and low levels of human complement C3, but the coagulation profile was normal. His condition has been diagnosed as atypical haemolytic uremic syndrome. He's been treated with plasma exchange and corticosteroids. He had previously received meningococcal group ACWY conjugate vaccine and meningococcal group B vaccine His genetic survey found ADAMTS13 &gt;10%</topic><topic number="69">The patient is a healthy 67-year-old woman who came to the clinic to get her flu shot in early October. He works at a rehab center and has no underlying medical conditions. This is his first shot this year. She's menopausal and has four children. He doesn't smoke. He takes multivitamins and anti-hypertensive medication every day. Exercise regularly for at least 30 minutes a day, five days a week He has no food or drug allergies.</topic><topic number="70">Patient is a 46-year-old Asian woman with MDD. He complains of chronic mood swings and lack of interest in daily activities. According to him, most days his mood is still depressed. He complains almost daily of weakness and feelings of worthlessness He's been taking anti-depressants for the past six months, but the symptoms are still present. He doesn't drink alcohol or smoke. He used to exercise at least 30 minutes a day, but he has not been able to do so for the last three weeks because he lacks enough energy. He's also recently developed some digestive issues. He is married and has four children. She is menopausal Her husband was diagnosed with colon cancer a year ago and is currently undergoing chemotherapy. His previous medical history is not significant. No family history of mental illness. His HAM-D score is 20.</topic><topic number="71">Patient is a 34-year-old obese woman who has come to the clinic because of concerns about her weight. She is 165 cm tall and weighs 113 kg (BMI: 41.5). In the past, he's used anti-obesity agents and appetite suppressants, but without success. He expresses dissatisfaction with sleep apnea, PCO and body shape She's a high school teacher. He's been married for five years. She has not used any contraceptive method for the past 4 months and has not been pregnant before He has little exercise and finds it difficult to move He couldn't complete the four-square-step test in less than 15 seconds. He does not smoke or use drugs. His vital signs: blood pressure 130/80 mmHg, heart rate 195/min and BMI: 41.54 Laboratory test results: &#8226; FBS: 98 mg/dl &#8226; Triglycerides (TG): 150 mg/dl &#8226; Cholesterol: 180 mg/dl &#8226; LDL: 90 mg/dl &#8226; HDL: 35 mg/dl He is considering laparoscopic gastric bypass surgery to treat his stomach ulcer and to treat his stomach ulcer.</topic><topic number="72">Patient is a 16-year-old girl who has recently been diagnosed with Myasthenia Gravis (class IIa). He's complaining of diplopia and weakness in his upper extremities. His anti-AChR antibody test was positive and single fiber electromyography (SFEMG) test was also positive. He is currently being treated with immunosuppressants with acetylcholinesterase inhibitor, but still has some symptoms. He does not smoke or use illegal drugs. She is not sexually active and her period is regular Physical examination and laboratory tests found no other significant abnormalities. Vital signs and laboratory test results: &#8226; Blood pressure: 110/75 mmHg &#8226; Hgb: 11 g/dl &#8226; WBC: 8000/mm3 &#8226; Plt: 300,000/ml &#8226; Creatinine: 0.5 mg/dl &#8226; BUN: 10 mg/dl &#8226; Beta hCG: negative for pregnancy &#8226; The following are the most commonly reported symptoms of the disease:</topic><topic number="73">Patient is a 3-day-old female who has been present with jaundice that started the day before. She was born at 34 weeks and was placed in an incubator because of a shorter gestation period. Vital signs reported: core temperature: 36.3&#176;C, heart rate: 154 beats/min, respiratory rate: 37 beats/min, and blood pressure: 65/33 mmHg. It weighs 2.1 kg, is 45 cm tall, and has a head circumference of 32 cm. He appears with yellow eyes and a yellow body. His liver and pancreas are normal at palpation. Laboratory test results: &#8226; Serum total bilirubin: 21.02 mg/dL &#8226; Direct bilirubin: 2.04 mg/dL &#8226; AST: 37 U/L &#8226; ALT: 20 U/L &#8226; GGT: 745 U/L &#8226; Alkaline phosphatase: 531 U/L &#8226; Creatinine: 0.3 mg/dL &#8226; Urea: 29 mg/dL &#8226; Na: 147 mEq/L &#8226; K: 4.5 mEq/L &#8226; CRP: 3 mg/L &#8226; Complete blood cell count within normal limits She has neonatal jaundice and may require phototherapy</topic><topic number="74">Patient is a 53-year-old male who complained of frequent headaches, general bone pain and difficulty chewing. These symptoms started six years ago and have been getting worse. The tests showed swelling around the molars on both sides of his face. Swelling has increased since the last examination. Multiple extraoral lesions have also been identified on the head and face. The spots are non-sensitive and attached to the bone Subsequent evaluation showed increased uptake of radioactive material and increased levels of pyridinoline in urine. Serum alkaline phosphatase 300 IU/L (normal range is 44-147 IU/L) The patient's sister had the same problem. Her sister was diagnosed with Paget's disease of bone at the age of 52. Patient has been diagnosed with Paget's Disease of Bone and plans to start Bisphosphonate as the primary treatment.</topic><topic number="75">The patient is a 55-year-old male who was recently diagnosed with Parkinson's disease. He complains of slow movement and tremors His condition is mild and has been diagnosed as Hoehn-Yahr Stage I. His previous medical history includes high blood pressure and hypercholesterolemia. He lives with his wife. They have three children. Before Parkinson's disease, he was active in physical activities such as gardening He feels his hands shaking and his movements slowing down. He had trouble getting through a door, because his body suddenly became stiff and he needed help getting through the door. His handwriting is getting smaller. He was offered treatment with Levodopa and Trihexyphenidyl. He's alert and cooperative and shows no signs of dementia. He does not smoke or use illegal drugs.</topic></topics>