<topics task="2021 TREC Clinical Trials"><topic number="1">Patient is a 45-year-old male with a history of spinal proliferative astrocytoma accompanied by severe lower limb weakness and urinary retention/concentration, post-Foley catheter insertion, high dose steroids, hypertension and chronic pain. The tumor is located between the thoracic and lumbar spine, with non-surgical, post-radiation, regenerative astrocytoma. accompanied by progressive weakness of the lower extremities and retention/accumulation of urine. The patient initially presented with right lower extremity weakness, where his right knee was bent, with difficulty walking and numbness in the right anterior thigh. The MRI showed a mass in the spinal cord cone, which was biopsied and found to be a regenerative astrocytoma. Treatment included radiation between TH10-O1 followed by 11 temozolomide cycles 7 days on and 7 days off. Irinotecan was followed by Avastin (bevacizumab) every 2 weeks with 2 weeks off and the cycle repeated.</topic><topic number="2">48-year-old male with a history of hypertension, hyperlipidaemia, aortic valve dialysis, and smoking came to his cardiologist on [**2148-10-1**] with progressive dyspnea and swelling of lower extremities. Transverse thoracic ultrasound revealed severe aortic stenosis with impaired left ventricular function. The ejection fraction was 25%. Right ventricular pressure was 41 and he was divalent. She was found to have a grade 2+ aortic insufficiency with mild mitochondrial insufficiency. He was sent home from the cardiology clinic with Lasix and beta-blockers (which he couldn't tolerate), continued to have worsening shortness of breath and swelling of the lower extremities, and finally presented here for evaluation. During this admission, repeated echocardiography confirmed critical aortic stenosis presenting left ventricular hypertrophy with cavity dilation and severe total hypoglycaemia, severe aortic valve stenosis with underlying bilateral aortic valve, dilated anus aorta, or systolic pulmonary artery hypertension. The patient underwent preoperative valve replacement screening with preoperative chest CT and carotid ultrasound (which showed moderate heterogeneous plaques with bilateral narrowing of the internal carotid artery) ICA 1-39%). He also underwent cardiac catheterization with right cardiac catheterization to assess his pulmonary artery pressures, which did not show angiographically evident coronary artery disease restricting flow.</topic><topic number="3">A 32-year-old woman comes in after a severe "explosive" headache. She and her husband report that yesterday she was in the kitchen, got up and hit her head on the corner of a cupboard. The next morning, she had a sudden "explosive" headache. She went to the hospital where the head CT showed a significant amount of blood in her right abdomen. The neurosurgery department examined her for spontaneous intravascular bleeding with concern for underlying vascular dysplasia. A cerebral angiogram was performed which showed abnormal vascularization with a drainage vein from the left temporal lobe penetrating deep into the white matter, consistent with arteriovenous dysplasia. The patient continued to have headaches, but they were getting better with painkillers. The patient refused physical therapy evaluation, but was walking independently without difficulty. She was discharged to the house with her husband on [**2155-12-6**].</topic><topic number="4">This is a 44-year-old female with a history of Polycystic Ovarian Syndrome, Obesity, Hypertension, who presented with symptoms of cholecystitis and was found to have a large pericardial collection. Pericardiocentesis was performed and the fluid analysis was consistent with Burkitt's lymphoma. The pericardial fluid contained monotypic, light chain-confined, CD10-positive B lymphocytes expressing FMC-7, CD19, CD20 and myc rearrangement compatible with Burkitt lymphoma. The subsequent lumbar puncture and bone marrow biopsy were negative for any involvement, making this lymphoma a primary cardiac lymphoma. The heart MRI showed a 3cm x 1cm mass on the lateral wall of the right ventricle next to the ventricular septum. If you have any of the following: Rare migraines 2. hypertension 3. increased blood pressure 3. Obesity 4. The use of the product in combination with other medicinal products may be considered as a means of preventing the development of ovarian cysts. Intracranial bleeding - Seizure/stroke ([**2137**]) = - from severe sinusitis, which caused mild non-focal residual defects 6. Leakage of ENS with meningitis after insertion of lumbar drainage 7. Deep vein thrombosis of the right lower extremity after insertion of a filter into the inferior vena cava 8. Surgery on the knee</topic><topic number="5">74-year-old male with a history of coronary artery disease following aortic bypass graft, 60% ejection fraction with prior vascular stroke (no residual deficits), hypertension, hyperlipidaemia, type 2 diabetes, moderate to severe peripheral vascular disease, was referred to a cardiologist for evaluation of peripheral vascular disease and on examination the patient was found to have coronary fibrosis. After further review of symptoms, the patient reports + Occasional dizziness, without previous seizure, occasional headaches, denied precardial pain/diphtheria. There are no sensory or motor defects. He remembers that he may have had a stroke 10-15 years ago with no residual deficit. Before the aortic bypass, she was just sweating. Further review of the systems is notable for the absence of pre-cardiac pain, exercise dyspnea, parasystemic nocturnal dyspnea, orthopnea, palpitations, syncope or apoplexy. He underwent a carotid ultrasound which showed significant bilateral stenosis, A&gt;D. The angiography revealed 80% narrowing of the right carotid and 90% narrowing of the left carotid. Cerebral angiography revealed further open right anterior and middle cerebral arteries and open left anterior and middle cerebral arteries. History of memory: coronary artery disease after aortic bypass [**2154**] ([**Hospital 1 112**]) Previous stroke Ambulatory Carotid disease Anaemia Peripheral vascular disease Hypertension Diabetes with complicated retinal and peripheral neuropathy Cataract treated by surgery Thyroid obstruction Multiple colon treated by dissection Other pain in the spine Proterozoic fracture of the right atrium as a child Arthritis</topic><topic number="6">Patient is a 55-year-old female with a history of end-stage renal disease in hemodialysis and peritoneal dialysis and presenting with fluid, bloodless diarrhea and weakness. He has a history of 2 previous C diff (clostridium) infections, the most recent just over a month ago. Recent use of antibiotics in the last month on previous intake. He had also been treated for Cdiff at the time for 14 days of oral vancomycin. Patient initially admitted to intensive care and was septic on vasopressors (levophed=norepinephrine) until morning of [**8-26**] with leukocytosis but no fever. The C diff test was positive at baseline and the patient had C diff compatible leukocytosis. The patient was initially placed on oral vancomycin, intravenous Flagyl and oral Flagyl, and when the patient improved, was switched to oral vancomycin and oral Flagyl on [**8-29**]. The patient was treated with vancomycin for 6 weeks of prolonged treatment due to recurrent C diff. The patient was also encouraged to take probiotics and to bleach the house when discharged.</topic><topic number="7">60-year-old male with cirrhosis of the liver, second-degree esophageal cirrhosis, recent admission for upper gastrointestinal bleeding, gastritis from nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory drugs, referred for admission through the emergency department of the hepatology clinic for new sticky speech and inconsistent thinking. The patient also describes a new imbalance that led to a fall in which he may have hit his head. According to the last note from the liver clinic, he's been off ethanol for a year (confirmed by the patient), urine toxicity test was negative for alcohol. The CT scan was within normal limits and the neurological evaluation found that it wasn't an ischemic heart attack. The patient was given a possible diagnosis of hepatic encephalopathy and started lactulose. Liver function tests showed a dramatic increase in total and direct cholerythrin since the last visit. Another worrying feature was the increase in the patient' s AFP (a-fetoprotein). This could be a cirrhosis progression, as he failed twice on interferon therapy. He'll be monitored as an outpatient to investigate this. The following are the most commonly reported adverse reactions: &#8226; Hepatitis C cirrhosis (interferon x2 therapy unresponsive) &#8226; Gastropathy &#8226; Grade II esophageal cancer &#8226; Hypertension &#8226; Recent admission [**4-/2150**]: &#8226; Upper respiratory gastritis haemorrhage caused by nonsteroidal agents [**2-9**]</topic><topic number="8">This is a 57-year-old man with chronic lymphocytic leukemia (CLL) and a large cell metastasis. He presented with the disease on [**10/2119**] with elevated white blood cell count and LDH. He didn't have splenomegaly or cell death at the time. He had some kind of lymphadenopathy. He then completed four cycles of FCR treatment, which he completed on [09/2119**]. She had an excellent response to the treatment and was followed off-treatment for about two years. Then [**7-/2122**] showed an increased white blood cell count, about 50% lymphocytes and slightly increased LDH. She also had some mild exacerbation of palpable lymphadenopathy. He then received four cycles of PCR but had little response and his regimen was changed to R-CVP, of which he received two cycles. Again, she had no significant response, although she continued to have excellent functional status and eventually switched to Campath therapy. His lymphocytosis decreased and his white blood cell count decreased markedly, but there was not much of a response in terms of reducing the lymphadenopathy. Eventually, he developed an enlarged left cervical lymph node, which was biopsied and found to have a Richter transformation.</topic><topic number="9">41-year-old male with a history of severe intellectual disability, congestive heart failure (CHF), epilepsy, which was accompanied by right-sided facial spasms and generalized tremor at the point of hospitalization, which required 20 mg of Valium to stop the seizure activity. Outpatiently, the patient was considered to have focal epilepsy with secondary generalisation, possibly due to anoxic brain injury at birth, and possibly related to atrophic changes observed on MRI, particularly in the left temporal lobe. The patient first experienced seizures at the age of 13, which were identified by the family as having generalized convulsions. He had a second seizure two years after his first episode. He was continuing with Dilantin and phenobarbital. The patient went 20 years without another seizure. Recently, Dilantin has been gradually reduced and it was considered that perhaps this medicine was necessary to keep him free of seizures. The patient had no further events during hospitalization and returned to baseline at the time of discharge. Full EEG reports are pending at the time of dictation. Individual reminder: Epilepsy as above, congestive heart failure, depression</topic><topic number="10">Patient is a 22-year-old otherwise healthy female with a five-year history of systemic mastocytosis, with a normal three-year outbreak, presenting with a flare and tachycardia and concerned about another flare. This is the patient's third flare-up in two months, and she's still on a gradual decrease in steroids that are new to her. She responded well to 125mg of intravenous steroids every 8 hours and intravenous diphenhydramine in addition to the treatment she continues at home. The general blood work was at her reference points. The serum penetration revealed a high value at 84</topic><topic number="11">A 75-year-old man with metastatic thyroid cancer, having completed 19 sessions of radiation therapy, who has had worsening dyspepsia for the past two days for solids, poor oral absorption, a 20-pound weight loss in the last few weeks, and lethargy. Thyroid cancer diagnosed with a mass in the right cervix-- undergoing a cervical mass resection, inability to perform a thyroidectomy. --high risk of bleeding, proximity to the trachea and the palindromic laryngeal nerve and large tumor size. --completed radiation therapy to the cervix--completed radioiodine therapy--metastatic to lymph nodes and adrenal glands. * you are having a hernia repaired. * you have a tonsillectomy.</topic><topic number="12">34-year-old woman with Marfan syndrome and known severe mitral valve prolapse with insufficiency who was scheduled for mitral valve repair but missed from follow-up. She remains symptomatic and is now ready to undergo surgery to repair/replace a mitral valve. Expulsion gap of 65% on transurethral ultrasound. Individual reminder: Marfan syndrome Mitral valve event with severe insufficiency Gastric reflux History of gestational diabetes Hypertension during pregnancy Obesity Caesarean section x 2 Laser eye surgery cataract surgery foot surgery (slowing down the length of the bone)</topic><topic number="13">62-year-old male with a history of vascular stroke, neurogenic bladder with permanent ultrasound catheter, multiple prior admissions for urinary tract infections, altered level of consciousness and urethritis presents to hospital with urethritis now resolved after treatment with vanc/meropenem ((vancomycin/meropenem). According to the CT scan, there's a non-obstructive stone in the left ureter, no signs of urethral strictures. Significant leakage around the superior catheterization site. Started with oxybutynin and switched to tolterodine. The urologist is not concerned about leakage and will monitor him the next week. has had a vascular stroke Neurogenic bladder performed hyperbaric catheterization recurrent urological infections with Klebsiella/ Pseudomonas Non-Hodgkins lymphoma Left eyelid marginal zone Dx at 03 (subjected to R-CHOP x 6 cycles) Bells infection Benign prostatic hyperplasia Hypertension Partial bowel obstruction Subjected to colostomy Hepatitis C C Cystic fibrosis Myeloid leukemia with anti-HIV, Abnormal DNA+ Diabetic Diabetes Mellitus and Neuroblastoma Stage IV?</topic><topic number="14">70 years old with COPD at 2.5 to 3.5 L O2 at baseline, obstructive sleep apnea and obese hypoxia, dysregulated congestive heart failure, discharge [**2132-8-24**] now exhibiting arousal and altered level of consciousness with hypoxia and O2 saturation around 70% at BipAp at 5 L. The patient was agitated and then lethargic at baseline. The daughter reported increased arousal and altered consciousness levels for 2-3 days with O2 saturation at 60-70% at home. The daughter has also noticed increased swelling of the lower limbs and weight gain, which led to a phone call with her doctor and an increase in the lasix dose from 80 mg daily to 100 mg daily with some mild improvement in swelling. She's exhibited decreased appetite, decreased oral absorption, decreased energy levels at home with difficulty with daily activities. No recent history of fever, cough, chills, sputum production, pre-cardiac pain, abdominal pain or other complaints except chronic pain in the right thigh for the last 1-2 months. The daughter also reports adherence to medication and adherence to BiPap at night. Individual MEMORY:- coronary heart disease; underwent aortic-stereoscopic bypass of 4 vessels [**2119**] - congestive heart failure; ejection fracture (EF) 55%, mild AORS (aortic stenosis) - obese hyperactivity syndrome - obstructive sleep apnea - Type 2 diabetes mellitus - abdominal tachycardia; underwent ICD (injected defibrillator of the heart) ** [2127**] - hypothyroidism - schizophrenia - HAP - Pneumonia treated at [N4**-7] [**1**] in hospital ** 1</topic><topic number="15">A 70-year-old woman with a history of coronary artery disease (CAD) recently noticed an abdominal mass, which appeared with fever/ chills and an increased number of blood cells in the aorta. In the last weeks before her admission, she had pain in the middle of her abdomen, which was reflected on her left side. It lasts all day, does not increase with food, although there is associated vomiting and is aggravated by coughing. A CT scan of the abdomen without a scan line was then carried out on [**4-20**] which showed a large heterogeneous left abdominal mass measuring 9,5 x 7,5 x 6,0 cm. The patient underwent an endoscopic ultrasound with biopsy. The biopsy results were consistent with pancreatic adenocarcinoma in the head of the pancreas. A mass was also observed on CT scan in the splenic curve and the tail of the pancreas, possibly an ectopic apstasis, given the recent probable history of the patient's ectopic dermatitis, which was considered to be an infected fluid collection or apstasis. He was treated with intravenous antibiotics (Zosyn, then ceftriaxone and flagyl) and will continue to receive them until examined by infectious disease specialists as an outpatient. Stefania disease with a history of angioplasty in [**State 108**] one year ago 2. The mitral valve is affected 3. Vaginal pain 4. Hyperlipidaemia 5. is the Blood pressure 6. Chronic renal disease (SCr 2.1 to [**3-17**]) 7. Hypothyroidism (TSH 10 to [**3-17**]) 8. The following table summarises the data for the following categories of patients:</topic><topic number="16">C. 79 years old with multifactorial chronic hypoxaemia and dyspnea believed to be due to diastolic congestive heart failure, pulmonary hypertension believed to be due to chronic interstitial communication and chronic obstructive pulmonary disease, on 5L oxygen at home, admitted with complaints of worsening dyspnea. The cardiologist recommended right-sided cardiac catheterization to assess the response to sildenafil, but the patient refused. The pulmonologist recommended an empirical, compassionate sildenafil test due to severe dyspnotic symptoms preventing an outpatient stay, and the patient tolerated an inpatient test without hypotension. The patient had to undergo a pulmonary operation to initiate chronic sildenafil as an outpatient, subject to prior approval. Previous medical history:- Correction of atrial septal defect [**6-17**] complicated by atrial blockage with PPM placement. - Diastolic congestive heart failure, estimated dry weight 94kg - Pulmonary hypertension (right systolic joint pressure 75 to [**11-24**]) considered secondary to long-term autistic disorder - COPD with home oxygenation (5L NC) with a reference saturation of 80 to 90 in this treatment. - Obstructive sleep apnea (OSA), not compatible with CPAP - Mild mitochondrial insufficiency - Microcytic anaemia - Hypothyroidism - S/p APPY, s/p CCY ('[**33**]) - Pancreatitis from gallstone s/p ERCP, sphincterotomy - Increased alkaline phosphate secondary in amidone</topic><topic number="17">64 year old female with multiple myeloma, underwent allogeneic transplantation with relapsed disease and systemic amyloidosis (blocked lungs, tongue, bladder, heart), on dialysis for ESRD end stage renal disease representing malaise, weakness and generalized body pain x 2 days. She was admitted last week with hypercalcemia and has been given 30 mg of pamidronate, calcitonin and dialysis. The patient initially received melphalan and prednisone, followed by a VAD regimen and autologous stem cell transplantation. With a recurrence of myeloma, he received thalidomide velcade and thalidomide, which were eventually also discontinued due to worsening of oedema and renal function.</topic><topic number="18">This is a 78-year-old male with a history of benign prostatic hyperplasia who underwent multiple urological procedures, including a prostatectomy. It was noted that he had low urine output and a bladder scan showed residual 360cc. It was impossible for the staff to pass a foley. Urology was consulted, a flexible cysteoscopy was performed in the ICU, and a severe 2 cm pelvic urethral stricture was found. They were able to put a small catheter through it and leave it in place. The patient leaked urine around the catheter, the catheter eventually came out but continued to have good urine production, and bladder scans were done after urination every 4 hours to make sure that he didn't have a high residual volume. The urologist suggested that when the patient is stable he should be taken to the operating room to surgically correct the narrowing.</topic><topic number="19">A 65-year-old male with a history of coronary artery disease and a history of myocardial infarction (MI), hyperlipidaemia, abdominal tachycardia and congestion was admitted earlier today for evaluation of congestion and abdominal arrhythmias. He was recently discharged after testing negative for a heart attack, which included the implantation of a heart monitoring device. He was examined in the Occupational Safety and Health department and, according to the report, the monitor showed from yesterday: 40 seconds of abdominal tachycardia and then bradycardia at a rate of 39 bpm a little later corresponding to his symptoms. During the night, the patient entered a monomorphic abdominal tachycardia on telemetry. The patient was found to be unresponsive. He started CPR, but it's unclear if the patient had a pulse. Within a minute, the patient was back to a venous rhythm. The patient reports no symptoms prior to this episode. At present, the patient is experiencing numbness and nausea, but is denying chest pain. The patient is to be transferred to the coronary unit for catheterization and electrophysiology.</topic><topic number="20">A 35-year-old female presented with a history of acne and mild hypertrichosis. The initial evaluation revealed elevated levels of testosterone. Recently she noticed a gradual swelling of her hands and feet and recognized that her ring was getting too small for her finger. There's some abnormality in her menstrual cycle, as well as some secretion from her nipples. He also has a positive history of snoring and headaches. Clinical examination revealed subtle signs of acromegaly and pregnatism. Visual fields are normal by comparison. Hypertrichosis, thickening of the soft tissues and sweating of the hands and feet are observed. The fasted state laboratory evaluation reveals IGF-1 968 ng/mL and the random growth hormone is 19.7 ng/mL. The MRI shows a macrophage without filtration. She's been on steady doses of long-acting octreotide since her diagnosis was confirmed. She's married with two kids. She uses an intrauterine device as a method of contraception.</topic><topic number="21">Patient is a 57-year-old male with abdominal pain and vomiting. The pain started gradually about 20 hours ago in the epidural and pariemphal area, reflecting off his back. He drinks about 60 units of alcohol a week and smokes 22 cigarettes a day. He's healthy, no history of allergies or medication use. His family history is positive for type 2 diabetes (his father and sister). He lives alone and has no children. The abdomen is delicate and soft. His bowel sounds are normal. His heart rate is 115/min and his blood pressure is 110/75 mmHg. Laboratory results are notable for leukocytosis (19.5), urea 8.5, high CRP (145), high amylase (1200) and glucosylated cholesterol level 15. The CT scan was negative for obstructive pancreatitis.</topic><topic number="22">Patient is a 31-year-old woman who complains of abdominal pain. The pain started last night as diffuse abdominal discomfort. She had a decreased appetite as well as a bad mood. The pain got worse and worse and acute in the morning. The pain was detected in the right lower quadrant this morning. Temperature is within normal limits with normal vital signs. Focal sensitivity and protective feeling were observed in palpation of the right lower quadrant. Palpating the left lower quadrant causes pain in the right. Her lab work is notable for leukocytosis. Abdominal CT scan with a scan shows the presence of an enlarged appendix with thickening of the wall of the appendix without perforation, abscess or gangrene. She's a candidate for laparoscopic appendicectomy under general anesthesia.</topic><topic number="23">A 39-year-old man arrived at the clinic with cough and shortness of breath, which were not relieved by his inhaler. He's had these symptoms for five days in the last two weeks. He doubled his oral corticosteroids in the last week. He's a chef with a history of asthma for three years, suffering from frequent coughing, wheezing, shortness of breath and tightness in the chest. Symptoms become more bothersome within 1 to 2 hours of starting work each day and worsen throughout the working week. His symptoms improve within 1 to 2 hours of being out of the workplace. A spirometry was performed which revealed a forced expiratory volume of air at the first second (FEV1) 63% of the predicted. His previous medical history is important for seasonal allergic rhinitis in the summer. He doesn't smoke or use illegal drugs. His family history is important for asthma in his father and sister. She's currently using inhaled corticosteroids (ICS) and fluticasone 500 mcg/salmeterol 50 mcg, one inhalation twice a day.</topic><topic number="24">The patient is a 55-year-old male who has been seeing his doctor for symptoms of the lower urinary tract, including frequent urination, urgency, weak flow, incomplete emptying and intermittent flow for the past 9 months. Further evaluation revealed: IPSS score: 15 Urinary Residue after urination: 70 mL Prostate tumor (TRUS): 60 mL Level of Protective Specific Antigen (PSA): 3.2 ng/mL 10 mL/sec maximum flow rate when the volume of urine was 130 mL Otherwise healthy using only 1000 units of vitamin D daily. The most recent biochemical blood test (previously 3 days) was normal: Hgb: 13.5 g/dl WBC: 135000 /mm3 Plt: 350000 /ml PT: 11 seconds PTT: 35 seconds INR: 0.9 Creatinine: 0.5 mg/dl BUN: 10 mg/dl U/A: Colour: yellow Appearance: hazy PH: 5.3 Specific weight: 1.010 Glc: 100 Nitrates: negative Ketone: no Leukocyte retention: negative RBC: negative WBC: 2 WBCs/h Upf/C: negative</topic><topic number="25">Patient is a 42-year-old postmenopausal woman who underwent a preventive ultrasound which revealed an abnormality in her right breast. She didn't have any palpable lumps on her breast exam. She had a core biopsy and revealed a penetrating, progressive breast cancer 1.8 cm in the left upper quadrant. He had an oncoctomy and the surgical boundaries were clear. The tumor was HER2-positive and ER/PR negative. The armpit sampling revealed 1 positive lymph node from the 12 sampled. The chest X-ray was not remarkable. She uses multivitamins every day and no other medication. He smokes a lot and drinks alcohol occasionally. She's only in a relationship with one partner and has a history of three pregnancies and live births. She breastfed all three children.</topic><topic number="26">A 45-year-old woman was referred to the emergency department with abdominal pain that lasted about 4 days, accompanied by nausea and 2 episodes of vomiting. The pain is localized to the epigastric region and reflects in the right upper quadrant. The pain gets worse after eating fatty foods. The patient has experienced similar pain twice in the last year. Her history is notable for hypercholesterolaemia and two caesarean sections. She has two children and is in menopause. He doesn't smoke, he doesn't drink, and he doesn't use illegal drugs. He has a mild fever. Her blood pressure is 150/85, her heart rate (HR) is 115, her heart rate (RR) is 15, her angiotensin converting enzyme (AEC) is 38.2, her SpO2 is 98% in rheumatoid arthritis. When palpated, she exhibits epigastric tenderness and tenderness in the right upper quadrant with no recovery. His bowel sounds are normal. The laboratory analysis is notable for increased TKD and leukocytosis with left shift. The ultrasound revealed several gallstones and bile mud. The largest gallstone is 0.7 cm. Surgical consultant recommends a scheduled holocyst.</topic><topic number="27">A 53-year-old male has had chronic HCV infection for the past 2 years. His history is only relevant for a groin surgery when he was 20. She's been on combination therapy with IFN (100 mg/week) and RBV (400 mg/day) for the last 9 months. Direct antiviral drugs were added to his treatment six months ago. His medical history shows previous positive HCV RNA tests as well as positive enzyme immunoassay for antibodies against HCV. The recent biopsy was negative for hepatocellular carcinoma and was only notable for chronic inflammation consistent with chronic viral hepatitis. There is no evidence of alcoholic liver disease, oesophageal variceal bleeding, hemochromatosis, autoimmune hepatitis or metabolic liver disease. He's a man on alert with no acute discomfort. His blood pressure is 130 over 75, heart rate is 90 over a minute, and his BMI is 27. His abdomen is soft with no ascites or tenderness. Lower extremities are normal with no swelling.</topic><topic number="28">The patient is a 60-year-old Spanish male who arrived with shortness of breath about a day ago. The symptoms started acutely and got progressively worse. It's a known COPD incident from two years ago. Spirometry revealed FEV1/FVC after bronchodilator = 60% of the predicted values. He smokes 20 cigarettes a day. His prior medical history is notable for benign prostatic hyperplasia and he uses Flomax for it. His family history is positive for hypertension in his brother. His medication includes Duo-Neb inhaled every 4 hours as needed, vitamin D3 1000 units a day and Flomax for his PBH. He's an obese man who's acutely ill but he's oriented and he's conscious. The vital signs are as follows: Blood pressure: 135/80 Frequency: 25/min Frequencies: 75 bpm Body mass index: 40 O2 saturation: 90%</topic><topic number="29">The patient is a 24-year-old man who has had type 1 diabetes for 11 years. He's coming into the ER with hyperglycemia and concern about possible diabetic ketoacidosis after not taking his insulin for 3 days. The patient reports being homeless and having lost his supply of insulin, syringes, glucometer and glucose-measuring equipment. Patient reports that at the time of initial diagnosis of type 1 diabetes, he was hospitalized with a glucose value &gt; 1000 mg/dL. At the time, she was showing signs of polyuria, polydipsia and polyphagia. He states that he has been taking insulin since the time of his diagnosis and has never been prescribed oral medication for the management of diabetes. More recently, she uses insulin glargine 55 units once a day and insulin aspart sliding scale 3 times a day. The patient had previous episodes of diabetic ketoacidosis for which he was hospitalized. With this hyperglycemic episode, she's not experiencing nausea, vomiting or abdominal discomfort and she looks fine. Laboratory studies of the drug showed: A1c: 11.3% Creatinine: 0.9 mg/dL with eGFR &gt; 60 mL/min Aspartate aminotransferase (AST): 17 U/L Alanine aminotransferase (ALT): 14 U/L Beta-hydroxybutyric acid: 0.1 mmol/L Carbohydrate: 25 mEq/L Anion gap: 14 mEq/L The drug was first reported in the United States in the 1970s.</topic><topic number="30">The patient is a 33-year-old woman who's been complaining of fatigue, weight gain, and irregular bleeding between periods. No excess hair or nipple discharge was detected. Her BMI was 34. Laboratory test results were notable for high TSH (13 mU/ L) and low free T4 (0.2 ng/ dl). Her anti-TPO levels were extremely high (120 IU/ml). He was diagnosed with Hashimoto's thyroiditis. Her aunt, brother and mother have the same disease. After starting 250 mcg of levothyroxine a day, her symptoms improved significantly and her period is normal. She's still overweight with BMI 31. Her most recent thyroid profile revealed all results except anti-TPO within the normal range: TSH: 2.35 mU/ L Free T4: 2.7 ng/ dl Anti-TPO: 75 IU/ ml The most recent thyroid profile revealed all results except anti-TPO within the normal range: TSH: 2.35 mU/ L Free T4: 2.7 ng/ dl Anti-TPO: 75 IU/ ml</topic><topic number="31">The patient is a 37-year-old woman who came to the clinic for a routine Pap smear. The test revealed stage 1B cervical cancer. The patient tested positive for HPV 16. She has three sexual partners and four children. He's been stripped of his salpicins. He smokes 30 packs a year and drinks a lot. Otherwise, he's healthy. She was offered a radical hysterectomy.</topic><topic number="32">A 17-year-old boy complains of vomiting, bloodless diarrhea, abdominal pain, fever, chills and loss of appetite for the past 3 days. He ate a salad at a restaurant before the diarrhea started. The clinical examination was notable for pallor, jaundice and diffuse abdominal tenderness. The laboratory results were as follows: Hb: 9.7 g/dL Platelets: 110,000 /cu.mm3 Creatinine: 3.6 mg/dL Blood urea nitrogen (BUN): 73 mg/dL Direct cholelithium: 2.4 mg/dL Lactic dehydrogenase (LDH): 881 IU/L (normal: 110-265 IU/L) The peripheral blood smear showed a moderate number of both schistocytes and skull cells. E. coli (STEC) stx1/stx2 producing Shiga toxin were found in the faeces. She has no other underlying disease and is not on any medication.</topic><topic number="33">A 42-year-old healthy woman came to the clinic to get her flu shot in early October. She works at a halfway house and has no underlying medical condition. It's the first time he's had the vaccine this year. She's been married for five years and uses barrier methods of contraception. The cycle of menstruation is irregular. He doesn't smoke. He's not on any medication. Exercise regularly for 30 minutes a day, at least 5 days a week. He has no history of allergies to any food or medication. Her prior surgical history is important for tonsillectomy and she's otherwise healthy.</topic><topic number="34">The patient is a 47-year-old Asian woman who complains of persistent feelings of sadness. She has lost interest in activities that she once enjoyed. She states that her mood has been mostly depressed for the past three weeks. She also lost her appetite, which led to a weight loss of about 15 pounds [5 kg]. He complains of loss of energy and feelings of worthlessness almost every day. He doesn't use drugs and he doesn't smoke. He doesn't drink alcohol. He used to work out every day for at least 30 minutes. But he hasn't had enough energy to do that for the last three weeks. He 's also recently had some digestive problems . She's married with four kids. She's in menopause. Her husband has recently been diagnosed with colon cancer and is beginning chemotherapy. There's nothing remarkable in her previous medical history and her drug history is only positive for 1,000 units of vitamin D3 a day. Her family history is negative for any psychological problems. Her HAM-D score is 20.</topic><topic number="35">Patient is a 15-year-old girl with a history of recurrent bilateral headaches. The seizures occur 2 or more times a week and each episode lasts about a day and a half. The pain is throbbing in quality and severe in intensity, causing problems with her daily physical activity. The seizures are associated with nausea and photophobia. She recently noticed that there are more seizures around her menstrual period. She's been diagnosed with a migraine and is undergoing treatment. She's a high school student and lives with both her parents. She is a book lover and spends her free time in a public library near her home. She is also interested in writing stories and has several short stories in English. He rarely exercises. Her BMI is 21 with a blood pressure of 100/60. There's nothing remarkable in her clinical examination.</topic><topic number="36">The patient is a 32-year-old obese woman who came to the clinic with concerns about her weight. He is 5'9" tall. and weighs in at 113 pounds. She complains of sleep apnea, polycystic ovarian syndrome and dissatisfaction with her body shape. She's a high school teacher, married for five years. She hasn't used any contraceptive methods in the last four months and she's had no previous pregnancies. He doesn't smoke or use drugs. She likes to try diets and exercise to lose weight. He completed the four-block test in 14 seconds. Her blood pressure is 130/80, her heart rate is 195 beats per minute, and her BMI is 41.54. Her lab tests are FBS: 98 mg/dl TG: 150 mg/dl Cholesterol: 180 mg/dl LDL: 90 mg/dl HDL: 35 mg/dl Her cardiac evaluation is normal. She has a high blood pressure. Her joints and fetal capacity are within normal limits.</topic><topic number="37">Patient is a 20-year-old Caucasian female who comes to the clinic with one-sided vision loss and facial weakness, dysfunction and numbness lasting 1 day. She visited her family doctor and underwent an MRI scan of her brain, which revealed a single plaque in the brain stem. After a few months, she developed weakness in her lower extremities that led to balance problems. The second MRI revealed another damage to the left cerebral hemisphere. The diagnosis of relapsing remitting multiple sclerosis (RRMS) is confirmed after the second MRI scan. Her surgical history is significant, due to a caesarean two years ago and she has a child. She's divorced and has no sexual relationship. He smokes 10 cigarettes a day and drinks alcohol occasionally. She works as an editor at a publishing house and is happy to be able to work from home most of the time. He's been on treatment for RRMS for the past seven months.</topic><topic number="38">Patient is a 35-year-old female with grade IIa gravis muscle disease. She complains of drooping, fatigue and weakness affecting mainly her upper extremities. He had a positive AChR antibody test and a single-fiber electromyogram (SFEMG) was positive. He takes 60 mg of pyridostigmine three times a day. But she still has some symptoms that are affecting her work. She's a research coordinator and she has three kids. Her 70-year-old father has high blood pressure. He doesn't smoke or use illegal drugs. He drinks alcohol occasionally at social events. Clinical examination and laboratory tests were not significant for other abnormalities. The following table shows the number of samples of the test chemical in the sample:</topic><topic number="39">A three-day-old female infant of Asian descent has jaundice that started a day ago. He was born at 38 weeks and 3 days, after a pregnancy without complications. Family history is normal. The baby is breast-feeding. The vital signs are listed as: arm temperature: 36.3&#176;C, heart rate: 154 beats/minute, respiratory rate: 37 breaths/minute and blood pressure: 65/33 mm Hg. Its weight is 3.2 kg, its length is 53 cm and the circumference of its head is 36 cm. Her hard robe is yellow and her body is yellowish. No whispers or other abnormalities in heart and lung listening are detected. Her liver and spleen are normal at the time of palpation. The laboratory results are as follows: Total serum cholerythrin: 21,02 mg/dL Direct cholerythrin: 2,04 mg/dL AST: 37 U/L ALT: 20 U/L GGT: 745 U/L Alkaline phosphate: 531 U/L Creatinine: 0.3 mg/dL Urea: 29 mg/dL Na: 147 mEq/L K: 4.5 mEq/L CRP: 3 mg/L Total haemoglobin within the normal range. She was diagnosed with uncomplicated neonatal jaundice that may require phototherapy.</topic><topic number="40">Patient is a 60-year-old male who complains of frequent headaches, generalized bone pain and difficulty chewing, which began 6 years ago and is worsening. Examination shows bilateral swelling around the groin. The swelling's increased since his last examination. Several extraoral lesions are detected on the head and face. The swelling is not painful and it's attached to the underlying bone. Further evaluation indicates increased intake of radioactive material as well as increased pyridinoline in the urine. The serum alkaline phosphatase is 300 IU/L (the normal range is 44-147 IU/L). His family history is only relevant for hypertension in his mother and type 2 diabetes in his father. The diagnosis of Paget' s disease of the bone was confirmed and the administration of bisphosphonates as first-line treatment will be initiated.</topic><topic number="41">A 57-year-old farmer was diagnosed with Parkinson's disease a year ago. He's showing signs of slow movement and terror. His medical history is important for hypertension and hypercholesterolemia. He lives with his wife. They have three kids. Before his diagnosis, he was actively involved in planting and caring for farm animals. Patient complains of tremors and slow movement. He had difficulty getting through a door, being cold and needing guidance to get inside. His handwriting is getting smaller. He's on levodopa and trihexyphenidyl. He said his medication helps with the tremor and the slow movement. But he's still having trouble initiating movements, stiffness and slowness in general. He's a man of alertness and cooperation who has no signs of dementia. He doesn't smoke or use illegal drugs.</topic><topic number="42">19-year-old Hispanic female, gestational number G1P1, 32+6 weeks pregnant, came to the maternity clinic for regular follow-up complaining of mild headache and swollen legs. Initial evaluation revealed a blood pressure of 146/99 and a urine sample with 3+ proteins. Blood pressure and hyperglycaemia (U/A) were normal at the previous visit. The repeated blood pressure a few hours later is 150/100 mmHg. Lab tests showed normal blood count, platelet count and liver transaminase levels. He complains of fatigue but not fever or chills. He also suffers from headaches without any changes in vision. No shortness of breath, cough, chest pain, orthopenia and palpitations or skin rash were observed. Clinical examination was negative for abdominal pain, change in bowel habits, nausea, vomiting, dysuria, frequency, bleeding or foamy urine. Swelling of the legs was observed without joint pain or back pain. She has no specific medical history and uses only prenatal vitamins. Her family history is positive for type 2 diabetes and hypertension. She's a social drinker with a negative history of smoking or drug use. She's only had one partner in the last two years and hasn't used any contraceptive methods since two years ago. Her BMI was 24 at the first visit when she was 6 weeks pregnant. She gains weight normally during her pregnancy.</topic><topic number="43">Patient is a 60-year-old female admitted to the stroke ward with a recent history of secondary intravenous antibiotics for absorption pneumonia. She has a fever and complains of abdominal pain and diarrhea (eight bowel movements in 3 hours, large amounts of green, liquid stool each time). The patient's abdomen is generally tender and swollen with hyperactive bowel sounds. He has a fever of 38.4 degrees, a rapid heartbeat of 113 beats per minute, and hypotension of 80/40 mmHg. The faecal samples must have tested positive for Clostridium difficile toxin.</topic><topic number="44">The patient is a 14-year-old boy who complains of scoliosis and back pain. He has no other medical condition. He used to be able to participate in everyday activities like basketball and soccer, however, recently he has been having difficulty doing them. The pain is in his leg and back, and it's aggravated by physical activity. He prefers to be lying down most of the time. He is not happy with his body movement and complains of shoulder imbalance and head shift to the right. The patient is a well-dressed and well-fed teenager who is alert and cooperative. The left shoulder is slightly higher than the right shoulder. The scoliosis curve is measured at 45 degrees. The patient is a candidate for scoliosis surgery according to the perioperative monitoring (motionally induced potentials) MEP.</topic><topic number="45">The patient, a 34-year-old African-American male with a known history of sickle cell anemia, arrives at the clinic with severe bone pain. The patient had severe lower back pain that was reflected in both thighs, a score of 9 out of 10. The patient had a positive history of sickle cell seizures from childhood. He also had the same symptoms for the last two weeks, taking oxycodone therapy, which was not beneficial for his pain. His family doctor sent him to the emergency room to receive intravenous pain relievers. The patient is nowhere within normal blood pressure. No splenomegaly was detected during the clinical examination. He has no positive history of drug allergy. He doesn't smoke or use illegal drugs. The laboratory study is as follows: Hgb: 8 g/dl WBC: 10000 /mm3 Plt: 300000 /ml MCV: 106 fL Haemoglobin electrolyte: 91% HbS 6% HbF 3% HbA2 AST: 22 U/L ALT: 43 U/L Alk P: 53 U/L Ferritin: 1200 ng/ml The mean value of the test chemical is the following:</topic><topic number="46">Patient A is a 30-year-old male who was admitted to the hospital after 10 days of coughing, intense night sweats and loss of appetite. He traveled to India a month ago and has no history of positive TB vaccination. He is a previously healthy man who works as an engineer for a high-tech company. He doesn't smoke or use illegal drugs. He had a fever (38 degrees Celsius) with a heart rate of 115 b/min, respiratory rate of 22, blood pressure 125/75 mmHg and oxygen saturation of 97%. Chest X-ray showed a leak in the middle of the left lung, 1.8 cm in diameter with cavitation marks. The smear on the sputum revealed a positive sputum culture for Mycobacterium tuberculosis, which is sensitive to first-line drugs for tuberculosis (isoniazid, streptomycin, rifampicin and ethambutol). The laboratory study is referred to as follows: Hgb: 13 g/dl WBC: 14000 /mm3 Plt: 300000 /ml AST: 13 U/L ALT: 15 U/L Alk P: 53 U/L Total Bill: 0.6 mg/dl Na: 137 mEq/l K: 4 mEq/l Creatinine: 0.5 mg/dl BUN: 10 mg/dl TKE: 120 mm/hr The following is the laboratory study:</topic><topic number="47">A 62-year-old African-American male presented with weakness in the left upper and lower extremities, associated with dark optic spot in the right eye, numbness in the right cheek, facial drooping and slurred speech. He refused shortness of breath, headache, palpitations, chest pain, fever, dizziness, bowel or urinary incontinence, loss of consciousness. His medical history was significant for hypertension, hyperlipidemia and hypothyroidism. He's smoked a pack of cigarettes a day for 40 years and consumes five to six beers a week. He doesn't know his family history. He uses levothyroxine, atorvastatin and HTCZ. His vitals were stable at the primary evaluation. Facial droop on the left side, dysarthria and left-sided hemiplegia were observed during clinical examination. His score on the National Institutes of Health Stroke Scale (NIHSS) was estimated at 7. The initial head and neck CT scan did not report eight intracranial findings. Intravenous recombinant plasminogen activator (t-PA) was administered as well as high dose statin therapy. The patient was admitted to the intensive care unit for 24 hours follow-up. Head CT revealed a 1.7 cm acute infarction of the right ventricular white matter and the posterior right basal ganglia.</topic><topic number="48">Fernandez is a 41-year-old man who is a professional soccer player. He came to the clinic with an itchy foot. Clinical examination revealed localized peeling and indentation between the third and fourth toes of the right foot. It became inflamed and painful, with mild stretch marks. The spine and the sole of the foot were unaffected. There's no pus or tear in the affected area. He didn't use topical ointment for the damage and he doesn't have a positive history of any underlying disease, like diabetes (DM). He smokes 15 cigarettes a day and drinks one beer a day. His family history is positive for hyperlipidaemia in her mother and myocardial infarction in her father. He has several partners and uses a condom during sex. Clinical and laboratory tests were otherwise normal. Tinea pedis infection was confirmed as a diagnosis by observation of segmented fungal tissues during a liquid-based KOH microscopy.</topic><topic number="49">A 12-year-old girl came to the clinic with her mother, complaining of short stature, delayed puberty and developmental delay. The karyotype test revealed 45X and confirmed the diagnosis of Turner syndrome. She's been on growth hormone (GH) for six months without estrogen therapy to avoid menstruation and reach her ideal height. On clinical examination, she is an obese, mentally retarded girl. Her breast bulbs were stage 1 with no hair in the pubic or armpit area. Her Thyroid-type hormone (TSH) was 3 and her Fasting Blood Sugar (FBS) was 75 in the last laboratory study.</topic><topic number="50">A five-month-old boy came to the pediatric surgery clinic complaining of a hollow scrotum on his right side. The boy is the first child born at 38 weeks with NVD from a healthy mother. The mother had a normal pregnancy with no complications. The boy weighed in at three and a half pounds and was fifty centimeters tall. She's breast-feeding and now weighs 11 pounds, 20 ounces, and is 20 feet tall. He's not developmentally delayed in the clinical evaluation. There's a palpable testicle on the left scrotum and an unpalpable testicle on the right scrotum. The penis is normal in shape and size and has not been circumcised. The diagnostic laparoscopy showed an abdominal non-descending testicle.</topic><topic number="51">Patient is a 25-year-old pregnant woman G1 P1, age 24 years and 3 days of gestation, who developed a sudden onset of fever and chills, accompanied by nausea and vomiting. She also complains of dysuria, urgency and frequency of urination. He also reports severe pain in the ribs. Its vital points are: T = 39.7oC, P = 117, R = 20 and AP = 113/74 mm Hg. Clinical examination reveals palpable tenderness of both sides of the spine. She has no history of recurrent UTIs before her pregnancy or any other underlying disease. Urine culture showed Gram-negative rod-shaped bacterial cells, white blood cells and leukocytes. The blood culture is negative. The general examination shows Hb 12.9 g/dL, Hct 39%, MCV 76 fL, white count 14.120/mL.</topic><topic number="52">A 34-year-old male comes into the clinic complaining of dizziness and severe diarrhea since yesterday. He returned from an international trip a few days ago and lived in a camp in Sudan for a month. She developed abdominal pain followed by bloating and nausea, as well as loose stools. Soon he had a strong watery diarrhea without smell. The stool is moist and white, but the patient has no fever. Blood pressure is 95/62 when lying down and drops to 75/40 when standing up. The skin's asparagus has decreased. Heart rate is 110 and he looks sick with dry mucus. V. cholerae was observed in dark field microscopy of a fresh stool sample. The laboratory test is as follows: Sodium 137 meq/L Potassium 2 meq/L Chloride 94meq/L CO2 15 meq/L Faecal white blood cells No faeces with occult bleeding Negative</topic><topic number="53">The patient is a 34-year-old woman from Jordan who comes to the clinic with some general and non-specific bone and joint pain. She's married with three kids. Her prior medical and pharmaceutical history is unremarkable. Her BMI is 23, her blood pressure is 120/75, her heart rate is 75 beats per minute. Her lab test is remarkable for vitamin D: 14ng/ml and otherwise healthy. The test chemical is a solvent and the test chemical is a carrier of the test chemical.</topic><topic number="54">A 57-year-old male was admitted to the clinic for weight loss and persistent dry cough four months ago. Chest CT showed bilateral multiple infiltrations in the upper lobes and thickening of the bronchial walls. There's a documented positive MPO-ANCA serum in his medical history. Trans-bronchial biopsy revealed necrotic redness with poly-nucleated giant cells and diagnosed Wegener's erythema. He's been on corticosteroids and cyclophosphamides for the past four months. His Birmingham vasculitis activity score (BVAS) has been over 4 since the onset of his disease. The latest clinical and laboratory examination was performed yesterday and showed the following results: A healthy, well-nourished male, non-jaundiced, cooperative and alert Weight: 73 kg Height: 177 Blood pressure: 120/80 Heart rate: 90/minute Frequency: 22/minute Blood moisture: 13 g/dl White blood cells: 8000 /mm3 (Neutrophils: 2700/mm3)</topic><topic number="55">A 22-year-old Caucasian male came to the clinic with a history of terror from a year ago. The terror was originally in his right hand while holding something. Later the tremor became continuous and extended to both arms and legs, even to the stillness. The Kayser-Fleischer ring was detected during the ophthalmic examination. Clinical examination revealed jaundice, hepatosplenomegaly and hypotension of the upper extremities. He had a constant smile on his face, however, according to his parents' explanation, he has aggressive behavior. Its laboratory analysis was significant for low serum seroplasmin (0.05 g/ l) and increased 24-hour urine copper excretion (120 &#956;g/24 h). Wilson' s disease was confirmed by high liver copper concentration (305 &#956;g/ g dry weight liver).</topic><topic number="56">Patient is a 41-year-old male, known case of acromegaly, who underwent sphincter surgery four months ago. He came to the clinic for follow-up lab tests after his first major surgery. His lab test shows IGF-1 level 4.5 ULN, adjusted for gender and age. The random level of growth hormone (GH) is 4 &#956;g/L. Recent brain MRI confirmed the residual pituitary tumor. His history is only relevant for acromegaly due to pituitary gland tumor and recent surgery. After the surgery, she's only on vitamin D and multivitamins.</topic><topic number="57">Patient is a 41-year-old obese woman who's been admitted to the emergency room with abdominal pain and vomiting. The pain that started gradually yesterday is localized to the epidural and pariemphal area, reflecting off her back. He drinks alcohol frequently and doesn't smoke. She has no history of allergies and uses only multivitamins daily. Her family history is positive for hypertension (her mother). She lives with her husband and has three children. The abdomen is delicate and soft. Her bowel sounds are normal. Her heart rate is 115/min and her blood pressure is 110/75 mmHg. Laboratory tests are noteworthy for leukocytosis (19.5), urea 8.5, high CRP (145), high amylase (1200) and glucose level 15. Abdominal CT revealed acute oedematous intermediate pancreatitis with enlargement of the common bile duct and the intrahepatic duct, confirming the presence of a gallstone. Her pregnancy test is negative and she's not breastfeeding.</topic><topic number="58">The patient is a 17-year-old boy who complains of severe migraine pain in the right lower quadrant of his abdomen, which started four days ago. The pain is accompanied by nausea and vomiting. He was feverish with tenderness, tenderness from the recovery and a cautiousness in palpation. His white blood cells were elevated with dominant neutrophils. CT showed signs of acute perforated appendicitis with free fluid in the spleen. Diagnostic laparoscopy revealed a phlegm with no other abdominal abnormalities. He's now a candidate for emergency laparoscopic appendicectomy under general anesthesia.</topic><topic number="59">The patient is a 15-year-old boy with asthma who was diagnosed a year ago. She's exhibiting shortness of breath, chest tightness and coughing. According to his mother, he didn't respond to the usual inhaled corticosteroid regimen. He was admitted to the emergency room with a diagnosis of severe asthma exacerbation. He's a candidate for general corticosteroid therapy. Spirometry revealed a forced expiratory volume in the first second (FEV1) of 60% of the predicted. His previous medical history is not relevant. His family history is important for asthma in his mother and uncle. He was previously treated with a combination of inhaled corticosteroids and Zafirlucaste.</topic><topic number="60">Patient is a 63-year-old male who was admitted to the emergency department with a history of acute urinary retention in the last two days. The abdominal CT scan revealed a large prostate and a bladder filled with urine. He's a candidate for catheterization and a transurethral resection of the prostate (TURP). Further evaluation revealed: Residue after urination: 71 mL Prostate tumor (TRUS): 63 mL Level of prostate specific antigen (PSA): 3.5 ng/mL Recent biochemical blood test (before 3 days) was normal: Hgb: 13.6 g/dl WBC: 133000 /mm3 Plt: 370000 /ml PT: 12 seconds PTT: 34 seconds INR: 0.9 Creatinine: 0.5 mg/dl BUN: 10 mg/dl U/A: Colour: yellowish Appearance: cloudy: PH: 5.3 Specific base: 1.010 Glc: 100 Nitrogen: negative: none Protein: negative WBCs: negative RBCs: negative WBCs: negative U/C: 2</topic><topic number="61">The patient is a 45-year-old postmenopausal woman with cell-confirmed breast cancer. A nucleus biopsy revealed a penetrating advanced breast cancer 3 cm in the left upper quadrant. The tumor is HER2-positive and ER/PR negative. The armpit swab revealed five positive lymph nodes. The chest X-ray was remarkable for metastatic lesions. The patient is using multivitamins and iron supplements. He doesn't smoke or drink. She's not sexually active and she doesn't have any children. She's a candidate for a tumor resection, and she's agreed to do it before the chemo.</topic><topic number="62">A 46-year-old man is experiencing dizziness and frequent headaches. He has a family history of coronary artery disease, but he has no other cardiovascular risk factors like smoking, high blood pressure and diabetes, and he's physically active. The patient' s LDL-C and HDL-C levels were 545 and 53 mg/ dL, respectively. Fasting glucose and triglyceride levels (85 and 158 mg/ dL, respectively) were within normal limits. The patient did not report any use of lipid-lowering drugs. The cervical audit revealed a 3+/6+ systolic burst in the cervix, which was reflected in the skull. Ultrasound of the carotid arteries revealed severe narrowing of the left internal carotid artery (LICA) as well as moderate narrowing of the right internal carotid artery (RICA) estimated to be between 40% and 50%. For LICA, the cut-off values of the maximum systolic (PSV) and the end diastolic velocity (EDV) were 208.5 cm/ s and 54.5 cm/ s, respectively. The RICA PSV was 91,72 cm/s and the RICA EDV was 37,37 cm/s. Plaques were observed on the anterior and posterior walls of the internal carotid artery and common carotid artery, which were characterised as bulky plaques extending to the middle third of the internal coronary arteries (ICA) and as predominantly acoustic and ultrasonic, with less than 50% of the area being acoustically insulated with abnormal surfaces.</topic><topic number="63">A 54-year-old obese woman was admitted to the emergency room with abdominal pain that started four days ago with nausea and vomiting. The epigastric pain radiates to the right upper quadrant, worsening after eating fatty foods. The patient has experienced similar pain twice in the last year. Her prior medical history is notable for hypercholesterolaemia and 2 non-alcoholic liver infections (NVD). She has two children and is in menopause. He doesn't smoke, he doesn't drink, and he doesn't use illegal drugs. He has a mild fever. Her blood pressure is 150/85, her heart rate (HR) is 115, her heart rate (RR) is 15, her blood rate (T) is 38.2, her SpO2 is 98% in rheumatoid arthritis. She's a fat woman with no acute discomfort. When palpated, she exhibits epigastric tenderness and tenderness in the right upper quadrant with no recovery. His bowel sounds are normal. The laboratory analysis is notable for increased TKD and leukocytosis with left shift. Ultrasound revealed several gallstones, bile sludge and stones (common bile sources) of CBD. The smallest stone is 14 mm.</topic><topic number="64">The patient is a 55-year-old male who was diagnosed with HCV 2 years ago and had a recent co-infection with HBV. His previous medical history is not relevant. She's been on IFN, RBV, and direct antiviral drugs for the last six months. The patient is not taking any other medication. His medical records show previous positive HCV RNA tests and positive enzyme immunoassay for antibodies against HCV. The recent biopsy was negative for hepatocellular carcinoma and was only notable for chronic inflammation consistent with chronic viral hepatitis. There is no evidence of alcoholic liver disease, oesophageal variceal bleeding, hemochromatosis, autoimmune hepatitis or metabolic liver disease. He's a man on alert with no acute discomfort. His blood pressure is 130 over 75, heart rate is 90 over a minute, and his BMI is 27. His abdomen is soft with no ascites or tenderness. Lower extremities are normal with no swelling.</topic><topic number="65">The patient is a 25-year-old male with type 1 diabetes, which was confirmed by molecular analysis seven years ago. He shows up at the clinic with shortness of breath and fatigue during activities. He claims mild shortness of breath after ascending 3 floors, no shortness of breath at rest and no chest pain (Category 2 according to New York Heart Association). He's been diagnosed with myocardial infarction, which will be treated with ACE inhibitors and beta-blockers. He's on insulin 70/30 and vitamin D supplements. His previous medical history is not relevant to other medical problems. His family history is positive for type 1 diabetes in his uncle and grandfather. The laboratory test is as follows: FBS: 100 mg/dl HbA1c: 6.5% Cholesterol: 190 mg/dl TG: 140 mg/dl LDL: 125 mg/dl HDL: 40 mg/dl</topic><topic number="66">A 16-year-old girl came to the clinic complaining of weight gain and abnormal menstrual cycles. Her BMI was 24, but in the last few weeks, she's gained five kilos. She gets tired more often and doesn't have the energy to go dancing with her friends. Laboratory test results were notable for high TSH levels (15 mU/ L) and low free T4 levels (0.18 ng/ dl). The anti-TPO levels were extremely high (136 IU/ ml). He was diagnosed with Hashimoto's disease. She doesn't smoke and she's not sexually active.</topic><topic number="67">A Pap test on a 54-year-old woman revealed an abnormal plaque-like intraepithelial/adenoidal lesion in the cervix. She tested positive for HPV 16. She's sexually active with her husband and has four children. She's in menopause and not using birth control. He smokes and drinks alcohol frequently. Otherwise, he's healthy. She was offered a conical surgery.</topic><topic number="68">The patient is a 23-year-old male who was admitted to hospital with high blood pressure (175/95 mmHg) and signs of sepsis. He developed respiratory failure requiring mechanical ventilation and renal failure requiring hemodialysis. His blood work showed microangiopathic hemolytic anemia and thrombocytopenia. His blood work revealed elevated lactic dehydrogenase and decreased levels of human C3 supplement with a normal clotting profile. He was diagnosed with atypical hemolytic uremic syndrome. He was on plasmapheresis and corticosteroids. You have previously been vaccinated with a combined meningococcal vaccine ACWY and meningococcal vaccine B. The genetic test revealed ADAMTS13 was &gt;10%.</topic><topic number="69">A healthy 67-year-old woman came to the clinic to get her flu shot in early October. She works at a halfway house and has no underlying medical condition. It's the first vaccination of the year. She's in menopause and has four kids. It's not working at all. She's on a daily regimen of multivitamins and antihypertensive medication. Exercise regularly for 30 minutes a day, at least 5 days a week. He's not allergic to any food or medication.</topic><topic number="70">A 46-year-old Asian woman with Major Depressive Disorder (MDD) complains of persistent feelings of sadness and loss of interest in daily activities. She states that her mood is still depressed most days. He complains of loss of energy and feelings of worthlessness almost every day. She's been on antidepressants for the last six months, but the symptoms are still there. He doesn't drink or smoke. He used to work out every day for at least 30 minutes, but he hasn't had enough energy to do it for the last three weeks. He's also had some digestive problems recently. She's married with four kids. She's in menopause. Her husband was diagnosed with colon cancer a year ago and is undergoing chemotherapy. Her previous medical history is unremarkable. Her family history is negative for any psychological problems. Her HAM-D score is 20.</topic><topic number="71">The patient is a 34-year-old obese woman who comes to the clinic with concerns about her weight. He is 5'9" tall. and weight 113 kg (BMI: 41.5). In the past, he's been unsuccessfully using anti-obesity and appetite suppressants. She complains of sleep apnea, polycystic ovarian syndrome and dissatisfaction with her body shape. She's a high school teacher. She's been married for five years. She hasn't used any contraceptive method in the last four months and she's had no previous pregnancies. She rarely exercises and seems to have difficulty moving. He's not able to complete the four-square test in less than 15 seconds. He doesn't smoke or use drugs. Her blood pressure is 130/80, her heart rate is 195 beats per minute, and her BMI is 41.54. Her lab results are FBS: 98 mg/dl TG: 150 mg/dl Cholesterol: 180 mg/dl LDL: 90 mg/dl HDL: 35 mg/dl She's thinking of having a laparoscopic gastric bypass, but she's not sure.</topic><topic number="72">The patient is a 16-year-old girl who was recently diagnosed with myasthenia gravis, grade IIa. She complains of a bending and weakness affecting her upper extremities. He had a positive AChR antibody test and a single-fiber electromyogram (SFEMG) was positive. He is being treated with acetylcholinesterase inhibitors in combination with immunosuppressants. But he's still showing some symptoms. He doesn't smoke or use illegal drugs. She's not sexually active and her menstrual periods are regular. Clinical examination and laboratory tests are not significant for other abnormalities. Blood pressure: 110/75 Hgb: 11 g/dl White blood cells: 8000 /mm3 Plt: 300000 /ml Creatinine: 0.5 mg/dl BUN: 10 mg/dl Beta hcg: negative for pregnancy The following are the most commonly reported cases of hypoglycaemia:</topic><topic number="73">Patient is a female infant 3 days with jaundice that started a day ago. She was born at 34 weeks and is being kept in a warm room because of her gestational age. The vital signs reported were: arm temperature: 36.3&#176;C, heart rate: 154 beats/ minute, respiratory rate: 37 breaths/ minute and blood pressure: 65/33 mm Hg. Its weight is 2.1 kg, its length is 45 cm and the circumference of its head is 32 cm. It has a yellow hard coat and a yellowish body. Her liver and spleen are normal in palpation. The laboratory results are as follows: Total serum cholerythrin: 21,02 mg/dL Direct cholerythrin: 2,04 mg/dL AST: 37 U/L ALT: 20 U/L GGT: 745 U/L Alkaline phosphate: 531 U/L Creatinine: 0.3 mg/dL Urea: 29 mg/dL Na: 147 mEq/L K: 4.5 mEq/L CRP: 3 mg/L Complete haemoglobin count was within the normal range. She was diagnosed with neonatal jaundice that may require phototherapy.</topic><topic number="74">Patient is a 53-year-old male who complains of frequent headaches, generalized bone pain and difficulty chewing, which began 6 years ago and is worsening. Examination shows bilateral swelling around the groin. The swelling's increased since his last examination. Several extraoral lesions of the head and face are detected. The edema is not sensitive and it's attached to the underlying bone. Further evaluation indicates increased intake of radioactive material as well as increased pyridinoline in the urine. The serum alkaline phosphatase is 300 IU/L (the normal range is 44-147 IU/L). The patient's sister had the same problems. She was diagnosed with Paget's disease of the bone when she was 52. Diagnosis of Paget' s disease of the bone is confirmed and bisphosphonates will be started as first-line treatment.</topic><topic number="75">The patient is a 55-year-old male who was recently diagnosed with Parkinson's disease. He complains of sluggishness and terror. His disease is classified as mild, stage I under Hoehn-Yahr. His history is important for hypertension and hypercholesterolemia. He lives with his wife. They have three kids. He was actively involved in gardening before his diagnosis. He complains of tremors and slow motion. He had difficulty getting through a door, being cold and needing guidance to get inside. His handwriting is getting smaller. He's offered levodopa and trihexyphenidyl. He's a very alert and cooperative man who has no signs of dementia. He doesn't smoke or use illegal drugs.</topic></topics>