<topics task="2021 TREC Clinical Trials"><topic number="1">The patient is a 45-year-old male with a history of anaplastic spinal astrocytoma, aggravated by severe weakness of the lower extremities, urine congestion with Foley catheter, high doses of steroids, hypertension and chronic pain. The tumor is localized in the T-L section of the spine, an inoperable anaplastic astrocytoma after radiation treatment. Complicated by progressive weakness of the lower limbs and retention of urine. The patient initially showed weakness of the MID (right lower limb), where the right knee gave way showing difficulty walking and stiffening of the right anterior thigh. MRI showed a mass in the spinal cord cone, and a biopsy revealed it was an anaplastic astrocytoma. The therapy included radiation therapy of the t10-l1 region, followed by 11 cycles of temozolomide, 7 days yes and 7 days no. This was followed by weekly CPT-11 for 4 weeks on Avastin every two weeks with a 2 week break and then repeating the cycle.</topic><topic number="2">A 48-year-old man with a history of arterial hypertension, hyperlipidemia, aortic valve bicuspid and severe tobaccoism, who went to his cardiologist [**2148-10-1**], with progressive dysnea and edema of the lower limbs. Transthoracic echocardiography (TET) showed severe aortic stenosis with worsening of left ventricular function (LVF). The ejection fraction was 25%. Her right ventricular (EsB) pressure was 41 and she had a bi-varicular dilation. Diagnosed with 2+ aortic insufficiency, with mild mitral insufficiency. Furosemide and BB (which she did not accept) were sent to her home from the cardiology clinic, dyspnea and lower limb edema continued to worsen, and she finally presented for evaluation. During this hospitalization, a repeated echocardiography confirmed critical aortic stenosis, showing left ventricular hypertrophy with dilation of the cavity and severe general hypocinesia, severe bicuspid aortic valve stenosis, dilated upper aorta, and mild systolic pulmonary hypertension. The patient was evaluated preoperatively with computed tomography of the chest and preoperative carotid ultrasound (which showed moderate heterogeneous plaque with bilateral stenosis of the internal carotid artery (ICA) in 1-39%). She also underwent a cardiac catheterization, with a right cardiac catheterization, to evaluate the pressures in the pulmonary arteries, which did not angiographically indicate any coronary artery disease limiting the flow.</topic><topic number="3">This is a 32-year-old woman who was reported missing after a mild headache. It is reported that she and her husband woke up in the kitchen yesterday and hit their heads with the corner of a cupboard. The next morning, he had a mild headache. He made it to the hospital, where a CT scan of the head showed a large amount of blood in the right ventricle. He was evaluated by the neurosurgeon for spontaneous internal ventricular bleeding, with concern for a lower vascular malformation. A cerebral angiography was performed, which revealed an abnormal vasculature with a drainage guard of the left temporal lobe that was inserted into the deep white substance consistent with arterio-oesophageal malformation (AOM). The patient continued to have migraines, but the painkillers were improving. The patient refused to undergo physiotherapy, but was able to walk independently without any difficulty. She was given leave to return home with her husband.</topic><topic number="4">This is a 44-year-old woman. She has Polycystic Ovarian Syndrome, obesity and hypertension. He had symptoms of cholecystitis and was accidentally diagnosed with a large pericardial effusion. A pericardiocentesis was performed and the pericardial fluid analysis was found to be compatible with Burkitt's lymphoma. The pericardial fluid contained positive monotypic CD10 cells with reduced light chain kappa, indicating FMC-7, CD19, CD20, and myc rearrangement, which were compatible with Burkitt's lymphoma. A lumbar puncture and a bone marrow biopsy were negative for any infection, which led to his identification as a primary cardiac lymphoma. A cardiac MRI showed a 3 cm x 1 cm mass on the lateral wall of the right atrium, next to the auriculobentrical (AB) junction. Medical history: one. Anomalous migraines in the second, hypertension in the third, obesity in the fourth. SOP/responsibility five. Viral encephalitis/meningitis -&gt; Intracranial hypertension (ICH) -&gt; convulsions/cerebrovascular accident (2137) = caused by a severe sinus infusion, caused by light non-focal sand deficits 6. leakage of liquid cephalorrhoidal (LZR) fluid, with secondary meningitis, when placing lumbar drainage. Seven, please. Deep Benign Thrombosis (DBT) in the lower limb, with the insertion of a Lower Caval Venous (LCV) filter 8. Knee surgery.</topic><topic number="5">A 74 year old male with a history of coronary artery disease/ischemic cardiopathy (CI), with a history of bypass surgery, 60% Ejection Fraction (FE% 60) Pre-Cerebrovascular Injury (CVI) (without residual deficiency), HTA, Dyslipidemia (DLP), DMII, EAP (peripheral artery disease) from moderate to severe. He was referred to cardiology for evaluation of PAE, and during the study, the patient presented carotid murmurs. After further review of the symptoms, the patient is diagnosed with occasional asynchronous dizziness and occasional migraine. It negates thoracic pain/dyspnea. Sensory failure, no motor signs, and no visual signs. He remembers a stroke he had 10 or 15 years ago without any residual. Before CABG, she had diaphoresis. In another review of the system, it is noted that there is no chest pain, exertion dysnea, paroxysmal nocturnal dysnea, orthopnea, palpitations, syncope or presyncope. He had a carotid ultrasound, which showed significant bilateral carotid stenosis. Angiography revealed a stenosis of 80% of the right carotid artery (ACD) and 90% of the left carotid artery (EKA-ACI). Brain angiography also showed the right anterior cerebral artery (AGA-ACA) and the middle cerebral artery (EGA-ACM) to be permeable, as well as an ACA and a left ACM permeable. Medical history: Ischemic cardiopathy (IC), previous history with coronary heart disease Coronary bypass surgery (BKK-CABG) [**2154**] (**Hospital1 112**) Previous IBD-ACV Secondary carotid artery disease Anemia eAP Hypertension Complicated diabetes, cataracts treated with retinopathy and peripheral neuropathy. Thyroid nodule Colon polyps with resection Periodic low back pain, unspecified Proteinuria History of a fracture of the right elbow Arthritis in childhood</topic><topic number="6">The patient is a 55-year-old woman with chronic end-stage renal disease, HD, and is on peritoneal dialysis. She suffered from dysentery and weakness. She's had two previous C. diff infections, the last one about a month ago. His previous hospitalization had involved antibiotics, and he was treated for C. diff with oral bancomycin for 14 days. The patient was initially admitted to the ICU and was septic with tube compressors (levophed, noradrenaline), with leukocytosis but without fever until the morning of [8-26]. The C. diff test was positive upon admission, and the patient was consistent with leukoplakia. She was initially given oral Vancomycin, Flagyl IV, and oral Flagyl, and upon seeing improvement, was retained on only oral Vancomycin and oral Flagyl in [8-29]. The patient was treated with oral Vancomycin for 6 weeks due to a recurrence of C. diff. Upon discharge, she was also encouraged to take probiotics and disinfect the house with bleach.</topic><topic number="7">The patient is a 60-year-old male with severe liver cirrhosis, caused by hepatitis C, and secondary hepatic cirrhosis. with varicose veins of the intestinal tract, recently admitted due to Upper Digestive Hemorrhage (HDA) [**2-9**], gastritis caused by NSAIDs. He was sent from the clinic of hepatology to the emergency room due to recurrence of sleep speech/dysarthria and tangential thinking. The patient also described a new instability, which could be triggered by a fall or a blow to the head. According to the last note from the hepatology office, he has been without alcohol for a year (confirmed with the patient), and the urine toxicity tests were negative for alcohol. Computed Tomography Axial (CT) provided the usual results, and neurological evaluation determined that there was no ischemic stroke. She was diagnosed with suspected hepatic encephalopathy and began treatment with lactulose. Functional tests of his liver showed a marked increase in total and direct bilirubin since the last visit. Another worrying aspect was the rise of the FA. This could indicate progression of cirrhosis, as the interferon was not responsive in both sessions. We will assess this situation and order an outpatient follow-up. Medical history: Cirrhosis caused by hepatitis C virus (CHB-VHC) (two treatments with interferon, no response) Portal gastropathy II. varices of the intestinal tract at the level of the arterial hypertension Last admission [4-/2150]: HDA [2-9], gastritis not caused by steroids</topic><topic number="8">The patient is a 57-year-old male with chronic lymphocytic leukemia (CLL) and a transformation to large cells. He presented with the disease on [**10/2119**] with a high white blood cell count and elevated LDH. She didn't have splenomegaly at the time, she didn't have cytopenias. She had severe lymphadenopathy. She completed four cycles of FCR therapy in [**09/2119**] and responded to the treatment excellently, with follow-up without treatment for the next two years. In [**7-/2122**], he again presented an increase in leukocytes, with about 50% of lymphocytes and a slight increase in LDH. He also presented with palpable lymphadenopathy, with a slight progressive deformity. She received four cycles of PCR, but the response was poor; therefore, the treatment regimen was changed to R-CVP, and she received two cycles of it. Again, she had no significant response, although she maintained an excellent functional condition, and was eventually switched to Campath therapy. The lymphocytosis disappeared and her white blood cell count decreased significantly, but little was accomplished in reducing the large lymphadenopathy. She then developed a swollen gongolia on her left neck, and after a biopsy a Richter transformation was detected.</topic><topic number="9">This is a 41-year-old male with severe intellectual disability, congestive heart failure, and epilepsy. He had epilepsy causing spasms on the right side of his face and was admitted to a nursing home with general tremor, requiring 20 mgs of Valium to stop the seizures. According to an external medical report, the patient was believed to have focal epilepsy with secondary spread, probably due to an anoxic brain lesion she had at birth and possibly related to atrophy changes seen on MRI, especially in the left temporal lobe. The patient had her first seizure at the age of 13. Her family noted a generalized seizure. The second seizure came two years later. She was given Dilantin (phenitoin) and phenobarbital. The patient had not had another seizure for 20 years. Recently, her dosage of Dilantin was being tapered, and it's possible that this medication may be necessary to be free of her seizures. The patient had no other incidents during his hospitalization and his baseline condition returned by the time he was discharged. The full EEG reports are still to come at the time of dictation. His medical history includes epilepsy, congestive heart failure and depression.</topic><topic number="10">This is a 22-year-old woman, otherwise healthy, but with a five-year history of systemic mast cell carcinosis, with rashes occurring three times a year. Now, she's presented with fever and tachycardia, raising suspicion of another outbreak. This is the patient's third outbreak in two months, while she continues to gradually taper off steroids, which is new to her. He responded well to 125 mg of the endobenosal steroid every 8 hours and endobenosal diphenhydramine, in addition to his home regimen. Full blood tests were in the basal range, showing a normal differential. His serum triptase level was as high as 84. The patient failed the aspirin provocation test because of an adverse reaction. She was stabilized with intravenous steroids and intravenous Benadryl (diphenhydramine), and was returned to medical service. The patient continued with her home histamine receptor blockers and switched from endovenous steroids to oral, as well as Benadryl to oral; she was observed overnight and discharged with her home medications: a gradual reduction in prednisone, gastrointestinal prophylaxis with IBP, calcium and vitamin D, and bactrim (cotrimoxazole) in the standard prophylactic dose of PCP.</topic><topic number="11">This is a 75-year-old male with metastatic papillary thyroid cancer, after 19 X-rays and radiotherapy. Her solids swallowing dysphagia worsened over two days, with poor oral ingestion, a weight loss of nine kg in the last weeks and a slight sleepiness appearing. Dx papillary thyroid cancer with right cervical mass -- after cervical mass was removed; inability to do thyroidectomy -- high risk of bleeding, proximity to the trachea and recurrent laryngeal nerve, and high tumor size -- after X-ray radiotherapy to the neck -- after radioactive iodine ablation -- metastatic to lymph nodes and kidney after repair of hernia *after amygdactomy *</topic><topic number="12">A 34-year-old woman with Marfan's syndrome, who has severe mitral valve prolapse with reflux, was scheduled for mitral valve repair, but follow-up was lost. It persists symptomatically, and you are ready to undergo surgery to repair/replace the mitral valve. 65% ejection fraction (EF) in transthoracic echocardiography (TET) is used. Medical history: Marfan's syndrome severe mitral valve prolapse, severe mitral regurgitation disease caused by gastric reflux history of gestational diabetes mellitus hypertension in pregnancy obesity Caesarean x 2 laser eye surgery cataract surgery surgery of the foot (reduction of bone length)</topic><topic number="13">62-year-old male, history of acute IBS, neurogenic bladder with permanent suprapub catheter, who has had multiple hospitalizations for urinary tract infections, altered mental status and urological sepsis. He went to the hospital with urological sepsis, which has been treated with vancomycin/meropenem. Computed Tomography (CT) showed non-obstructive calcium lesion in the left ureter, without urethral stenosis. Significant leaks were detected around the suprapubic catheter. They started it on Ditropan and then they changed it to Detrol (tolterodine). The urologist doesn't worry about leakage and will see the patient again next week. History of: Neurogenic cerebral vascular disorder (CVA-CVD), recurrent urinary infections with suprapubric probe, non-Hodgkin lymphoma of the left orbital marginal area caused by Klebsiella/Pseudomonas, diagnosed in 03 (after 6 cycles of R-CHOP) Bell's palsy HPB arterial hypertension partial bowel obstruction, hepatitis C with colostomy cryoglobulinemia LES, transverse myelitis, positive anti-ADND antibodies Insuulin-dependent diabetic Esophageitis IV. What's the phase? Infections by gernubids, including Pseudomonas and Enterococos</topic><topic number="14">Patient 70 years of age, EPOC (2.5 to 3.5 L O2 in basic), Sleep Apnea Blockers Syndrome (LABS-SAOS) and obesity-related hypoventilation syndrome, decompensated congestive heart failure (BGK-ICC) who was diagnosed with hypertension. He was discharged on [2132-8-24] and now presents with agitation and altered mental status, with hypoxia and O2 saturation around 70 with BiPap 5 L. The patient reported agitation and then drowsiness. Her daughter stated that in the last 2-3 days she had been experiencing agitation and mental state changes, with her O2 saturation at home in the 60-70 range. The daughter also noticed an increase in EDE edema and weight gain; this prompted her to make a phone call to the doctor and the day the FUROSEMIDAR dose was increased from 80 mg to 100 mg, with a slight improvement in edema. The patient experienced a decrease in appetite, oral intake and energy levels at home, with complications of AVD. She has had no recent fever, cough, chills, sputum production, chest pain, abdominal pain or any other complaint, except for chronic pain in the right thigh for the last 1-2 months. Her daughter also confessed that she's been filling her nipples with medication and BiPap at night. Medical history: - Coronary heart disease; treated with 4 cups of coronary artery bypass surgery [2119] - BGK-ICC; FE% 55, mild EA - obese hypo-ventilation syndrome - suppressor of sleep apnea - DM2 - ventricular tachycardia, with DAE [2127]</topic><topic number="15">A woman in her 70s, with a history of coronary heart disease, who recently has been diagnosed with a mass in the abdomen, which has presented with fever, tremors and increased neutrophils in the peripheral blood. In the last few weeks, she's had a central abdominal infarction, which was irradiated to the left side. The pain persisted throughout the day and was not aggravated by food, although it was associated with vomiting and aggravated by coughing. She underwent a contrastless OT-TC of the abdomen at [4-20], which showed a large heterogeneous mass of 9.5 x 7.5 x 6.0 cm in the upper left abdomen. They did an echoscopy, biopsy, and a biopsy. The biopsy results were found to be compatible with pancreatic head adenocarcinoma. OT-TC also showed a mass in the splenic flexure/pancreatic cavity, probably a diverticular abscess due to recent antecedents of diverticulitis; it was thought to be an accumulation of infected fluid or abscess. The patient received intravenous antibiotic treatment (Zosyn [piperacillin-tazobactham], then ceftriaxone and Flagyl) and will continue with them until an outpatient follow-up by an infectious disease specialist. Medical history: Coronary artery disease with a history of angioplasty, one year ago [108 state] Mitral valve prolapse atrial fibrillation hyperlipemia hypertension Chronic kidney disease (CrS 2.1 en [3-17]) Is there hypothyroidism? is there any other medical history of the disease? Anemia (HCT 30.7 in [3-17])</topic><topic number="16">A 79-year-old woman with chronic multi-factor hypoxemia and dyspnea, admitted for complaints of allegedly worsening dyspnea as a result of diastolic heart failure (ICK-ICC), pulmonary hypertension (probably secondary to chronic CIA) and 5-liter home EPOC. The cardiology consultation recommended direct cardiac catheterization to evaluate the response to sildenafil, but the patient refused. The Pneumology Consultation recommended an empirical and compassionate clinical trial with sildenafil due to severe dysnetic symptomatology that prevented ambulatory life, and the patient consented to a clinical trial without hypotension. The patient should be treated by pneumology, to start sildenafil chronically and ambulatory, provided prior approval is obtained. Medical history: - Fixed intra-earphone communication [6-17] complicated with sinus arrest, with permanent heart rate marker installed - Diastolic heart failure (DHI-ICC), estimated dry weight of 94 kg - Pulmonary hypertension (RSVP 75 [11-24]) long-term Aurikula Inter-Aural Communication (AAK-CIA) is considered secondary - EPO with Home O2 (5 L per nasal cannula), with a wild satisfaction of between 80% and 90% with this therapy. - SAOS, not compatible with CPAP - Mild mitral insufficiency - Microcytic anemia - Hypothyroidism - Appendicectomised and colectostomised - Cervical pancreatitis treated with CPRE and sphinterotomy - High alkaline phosphatase, secondary to amiodarone</topic><topic number="17">A 64-year-old woman with multiple myeloma and treated with secondary allogeneic transplantation, recurrent disease and systemic amyloidosis (implications in the lungs, spleen, bladder and heart), treated by hemodialysis for chronic end-stage renal disease. The patient has been experiencing general malaise, weakness and body pain for the past two days. She was admitted last week with hypercalcemia and received 30 mg pamidronate, calcitonin and dialysis. She was initially treated with melphalan and prednisone, then with a VAD regimen (vincristine, adriamycin, and dexamethasone) and stem cell auto-transplantation. Faced with a recurrence of myeloma, she was given thalidomide and velcade, but these were eventually discontinued due to edema and worsening kidney function.</topic><topic number="18">He's a 78-year-old male with a history of BPH who has undergone several urological procedures including a suprapubic prostatectomy. She was diagnosed with low diuresis, and a 360 cc of residues were found by means of a bladder ultrasound. The workers never got the Foley catheter in. The urology department was consulted, and a flexible cystoscopy was performed at the ICU, finding severe bulbar urethral stenosis of 2 cm. They were able to run a small catheter through it and just left it there. The patient had leaks around the catheter, and eventually the catheter was removed; however, she maintained good urine output and had ultrasound scans of her bladder every 4 hours after urination to ensure that there was no excessive sand volume. The urologist recommended that as soon as the patient is stabilized, that he be taken to the operating room to surgically correct the stenosis.</topic><topic number="19">A 65-year-old man with coronary artery disease and pre-myocardial infarction, Hodgkin's disease, hypertension, ventricular tachycardia, and syncope was admitted to the hospital this morning for evaluation of syncope and ventricular rhythms. He was recently discharged after a negative evaluation for synchrony. During this evaluation, a heart-monitoring device was used. An examination was made in another hospital and according to yesterday's monitor report, the following readings were given: ventricular tachycardia (TB) every 40 seconds followed by bradycardia with a frequency of 39 seconds, according to symptoms. At night, the patient was inserted into the monomorphic TB on the telemetry. The patient did not respond. Accelerated cardiac beating (BBB-RCP) was started, although it was not clear whether the patient had a pulse. After a minute, the patient was back in sinus rhythm. The patient has not reported any symptoms prior to this incident. The patient now experiences a feeling of presyncope and nausea, but denies chest pain. The patient will be transferred to the coronary care unit for catheterization and electrophysiological examination (AEF-EEF).</topic><topic number="20">I have a 35-year-old woman with a history of acne and mild hirsutism. The initial evaluation showed high testosterone levels. Recently, she noticed that her hands and feet were gradually becoming larger, and she noticed that her ring was becoming smaller and smaller. We have some irregularity in her menstrual cycle, and also a slight discharge from the nipple. She also has a rash and a headache. A physical examination revealed subtle facial features of acromegaly and prognatism. The visual fields are normal for the confrontation. It's characterized by hirsutism, thickening of soft tissue and diaphoresis of the hands and feet. The fasting lab's evaluation shows IGF-1 at 968 ng/mL and random GH at 19.7 ng/mL. MRI showed a non-invasive macroadenoma. She's been on a steady dose of long-release octreotide since her diagnosis was confirmed. He is married and has two children. She is using an intrauterine device (IUD) as a contraceptive.</topic><topic number="21">Patient is 57 years old and has abdominal pain and vomiting. The pain began gradually over about 20 hours in the epigastric and periunbilical regions, radiating down the back. She drinks about 60 units of alcohol a week and smokes 22 cigarettes a day. She is in good health with no history of allergies or medication. Family history is positive for type 2 diabetes. Father and sister. She lives alone and has no children. The abdomen is painful and soft. Your bowel movements are normal. His heart rate is 115/min and his arterial pressure is 110/75 mmHg. Laboratory results are notable for the level of leukocytosis (19.5), 8.5 urea, high PCR (145), high amylase (1200) and 15 Glc. The CT scan was negative for expansionary pancreatitis.</topic><topic number="22">Patient is a 31-year-old woman with severe abdominal pain. The pain started last night, a vague stomach ache. She had a bad appetite and was feeling unwell. The pain became more intense and more intense in the morning. The pain was detected in the lower right quadrant this morning. Temperature and vital signs are within normal limits. On dissection of the right lower quadrant, focal pain and defense were detected. Fractures in the lower left quadrant cause pain in the right quadrant. The lab tests show that she has leukoplakia. Contrasted CT scan of the abdomen shows an appendix with thickened appendicular wall, no perforations, abscesses, or gangrene. It is a candidate for laparoscopic appendicectomy under general anesthesia.</topic><topic number="23">A 39-year-old man with coughing and shortness of breath came to the clinic, unable to relax on the respirator. He had these symptoms five days a week for the past two weeks. Her oral corticosteroid dosage doubled in the last week. He's a chef with a history of asthma for three years, frequent coughing, whistling, shortness of breath, and chest tightness. Symptoms become bothersome between 1 and 2 hours after you start work each day, and they worsen during the work week. Symptoms usually improve within an hour or two of leaving the office. Spirometry was performed, revealing a forced breath volume of 63% of the predicted in the first second (FEV1). His medical history is significant because of his annual allergic rhinitis in the summer. She doesn't smoke or do illegal drugs. Family history includes both father and sister with asthma. Currently, she uses Oral Corticosteroids (AK-CI) and fluticasone 500 mcg/salmeterol 50 mcg, which is inhaled twice daily.</topic><topic number="24">The patient is a 55-year-old male who has been referred to his physician, and for the past nine months has been experiencing the symptoms of the lower urinary tract: frequent urination, urgency, weak urine output, incomplete defecation, and intermittent flow. The subsequent evaluation showed the following: IPSS score: 15 Post-mictation residues: 70 ml Prostate volume (direct ultrasound): 60 ml Prostate specific antigen (PSA): 3.2 ng/ml Maximum flow: 10 ml/s, when urine volume is 130 ml The rest, is healthy and takes only 1,000 units of vitamin D per day. Recent blood biochemistry (3 days ago) was normal: hb: 13.5 g/dL Leukocytes: 135000 /mm3 Platelets: 350000 /ml TP: 11 seconds TPT: 35 seconds INR: 0.9 Creatinine: 0.5 mg/dL BUN: 10 mg/dL Urianalysis: Color: yellow Appearance: brownish pH-5.3 Specific gravity: 1.010k Nitrite: negative Ceton: none Leukocyte esterase: negative Hematics: negative Leukocytes: 2 Leukocytes/high-concentration area UROCULTIBOA: negative</topic><topic number="25">The patient is a 42-year-old postmenopausal woman who underwent a seizure ultrasound which revealed an abnormality in the right breast. There was no noticeable mass in the chest examination. A thick-needle biopsy was done, revealing a 1.8 cm infiltrating ductal carcinoma of the breast in the upper left quadrant. She had a tumour-ectomy, and the surgical margins were clear. The tumor was HER2 positive and estrogen receptor/progesterone receptor negative. The axial sampling showed 1 out of 12 samples positive for lymph nodes. The chest x-ray showed no significant findings. She takes a daily multivitamin from the "healthy women" and no other medication. He smokes a lot and drinks alcohol occasionally. She has only one partner, and a history of three live pregnancies and births. She has breastfed all three of her children.</topic><topic number="26">A 45-year-old woman was referred to the emergency department after suffering from abdominal pain for approximately four days, vomiting and two vomiting episodes. The pain is localized to the epigastric region, and radiates into the upper right quadrant. The pain is usually worse after eating fatty foods. The patient had the same pain twice in the last year. His medical history features hypercholesterolemia and two cesarean sections. She's a mother of two and a menopausal. She doesn't smoke, drink or take illegal drugs. She has a slight fever. His blood pressure is 150 over 85, heart rate is 115, respiratory rate is 15, T 38.2, SpO2 in ambient air. When it breaks, it causes pain in the epigastric growth and in the upper right quadrant, without rebound. Your bowel movements are normal. The lab results indicate high VSG and unusually high white blood cell count. The ultrasound showed some calcareous lesions and some calcareous dirt. The largest hairball is a quarter of an inch. The surgical consultation recommends an optional cholecystectomy.</topic><topic number="27">A 53-year-old male has had chronic hepatitis C virus (CHB-VHC) infection for the past two years. His medical history is only relevant because of a single hip hernia surgery at age 20. She's been on combined IFN (100 mg/week) and RBV (400 mg/day) since 9 months. The direct antiviral drugs were added to the treatment six months ago. His medical history shows positive CHB-VHC RNA testing as well as positive enzymatic immunoassay for anti-CHB-VHC antibodies. His recent biopsy was negative for hepatocellular carcinoma, and was only notable for chronic swelling consistent with chronic viral hepatitis. There is no evidence of alcoholic liver disease, varicose veins, hemochromatosis, autoimmune hepatitis or metabolic liver disease, bleeding. He's very alert, with no obvious distractions. Blood pressure is 130 over 75. Heart rate is 90 per minute. BMI is 27. His stomach is soft, acidic and painless. Lower extremities are normal, no swelling.</topic><topic number="28">The patient is a 60-year-old Spanish man with dyspnea diagnosed the day before. The symptoms started in an abrupt fashion and gradually worsened. He's the guy who introduced the EPOC that we've been hearing about for a couple of years. Spirometry showed post-bronchodilatory FEV1/FVC at 60% of the predicted values. She smokes 20 cigarettes a day. Among his medical records, the presence of HBP is notable, in which case Flomax (tamsulosin) is used. In her family history, there is a brother who has hypertension. Her medication includes Duo-Neb (salbutamol and ipratropious), inhaled every 4 hours as needed, 1000 units of vitamin D3 daily and Flomax for HBP. He's a fat man, slightly ill, but oriented and conscious. Her vital constants are as follows: PA: 135/80 fR: 25 lpm FC: 75 lpm BMI: 40 Oxygen saturation: 90%</topic><topic number="29">The patient is 24 years old and has had type 1 diabetes for 11 years. She is expressing concern about hyperglycemia and possible diabetic ketoacidosis in the emergency room after not taking insulin for 3 days. The patient has reported that he is currently homeless and has lost his supply of insulin, syringes, a glucometer and a glucose test. The patient states that at the time of diagnosis of type 1 diabetes, he was hospitalized with a glucose value &gt; 1000 mg/dL. At this point, she had polyuria, polydipsia, and polyphagia. He revealed that he has been on insulin treatment since his diagnosis and has never been prescribed any oral agent for the management of diabetes. Recently, 55 glargine has used insulin once daily and aspart variable dose insulin 3 times daily. The patient had a prior diabetic ketoacidosis. She was hospitalized. With a mild hyperglycemic event, he has no feces, no vomiting, no abdominal disorders, and he is fine. Laboratory analyses showed: A1c: 11.3% Creatinine: 0.9 mg/dL with TFGe &gt;60 mL/min Aspartate aminotransferase (AST): 17 U/L Alanine aminotransferase (ALT): 14 U/L Beta-hydroxybutyrate: 0.1 mmol/L Bicarbonate: 25 mEq/L Gap anion: 14 mEq/L The protein is also known as the amino acid.</topic><topic number="30">The patient, a 33-year-old woman, complained of fatigue, weight gain, and unusual menstrual urges. There was no sign of hirsutism or nipple discharge. His BMI was 34. Laboratory results include a high TSH level (13 mU/L) and a low free T4 level (0.2 ng/dl). Her anti-TPO levels were very high (120 IU/ml). He was diagnosed with Hashimoto's thyroiditis. My aunt, my brothers, my mother all have the same disease. After starting levothyroxine at 250 mcg daily, symptoms improved markedly and periods are normal. He's still overweight with a BMI of 31. The most recent thyroid profile showed all results to be within normal range, except for the one against TPO: TSH: 2.35 mU/L Free T4: 2.7 ng/dl Anti-TPO: 75 IU/ml</topic><topic number="31">The patient is a 37-year-old woman who came to the clinic for a routine cervical cytology. The test showed stage 1B cervical cancer. The patient tested positive for GPB16. She's had three sexual partners and four children. It was a plug-in. She smokes 30 packs of cigarettes a year and drinks a lot. Otherwise, he's healthy. He was offered a radical hysterectomy.</topic><topic number="32">A young man of 17 years old has complained of vomiting, bloodless diarrhea, abdominal pain, fever, chills and loss of appetite for the past three days. He ate a salad at a restaurant before the diarrhea. During the physical examination, reports of paleness, hives, and vague abdominal pain were noted. Laboratory results were as follows: Hemoglobin: 9.7 g/dL Platelets: 110,000/mm3 Creatinine: 3.6 mg/dL Urea nitrogen (BUN) in the blood: 73 mg/dL Straight bilirubin: 2.4 mg/dL Lactate dehydrogenase (LDH): 881 IU/L (normal: 110-265 IU/L) In the case of peripheral blood frothis showed a moderate number of schistocytes and cells. E. coli bacteria producing a toxin similar to Shiga (STEC) stx1/stx2 were found in the feces. He has no underlying illness or medication.</topic><topic number="33">A healthy 42-year-old woman came to our clinic to get her flu shot in early October. He works in a rehab facility and he has no underlying medical condition. It's his first shot this year. He's been married for five years and he uses barrier methods of contraception. Your menstrual cycle is irregular. He doesn't smoke. He's not on any medication. He exercises 30 minutes a day, at least five days a week. No history of allergies to any food or medication. His surgical history includes one amygdalectomy, and he is otherwise healthy.</topic><topic number="34">The patient is a 47-year-old Asian woman who complains of persistent feelings of sadness. She lost interest in the activities she used to enjoy. He testified that his mood has been depressed for the past three weeks. She also lost her appetite, which caused her to lose about five pounds. Almost every day he complains of a lack of energy and of feeling worthless. She doesn't do drugs or smoke. And I'm not drinking any alcohol. She exercised every day for at least 30 minutes, but she hasn't had enough energy to do it for the last three weeks. And recently, he's had some digestive issues. He is married and has four children. She's in the menopause. Her husband was diagnosed with colon cancer and is beginning chemotherapy. There is nothing remarkable in his past medical history and as a medicine he takes vitamin D3 1000 units a day. The family history is negative for any psychological problems. His HAM-D score is 20.</topic><topic number="35">Patient is 15 years old and has recurrent bilateral migraine. The attacks occur at least twice a week, with each incident lasting a few days or a full day. The pain is throbbing and intense, making it difficult for him to perform regular physical activity. The attacks have been linked to nausea and photophobia. Recently, she's noticed that her attacks are more frequent around the time of her period. He was diagnosed with migraine and is undergoing treatment. She's in high school and lives with her parents. He is a lover of reading and spends his free time in a public library near his home. She is also interested in writing short stories, and has several short stories in English. He rarely exercises. His BMI-CMI is 21, and his blood pressure is 100/60. Nothing unusual was found on your physical examination.</topic><topic number="36">The patient is a 32-year-old obese woman who came to the clinic for weight problems. He is 5'5" and weighs 113 pounds. She's a patient with sleep apnea, polycystic ovary syndrome and self-image anxiety. She's a high school teacher and has been married for five years. She has not used any form of contraception in the past four months, and she has no prior pregnancy. She doesn't smoke or do drugs. She likes to try diets and exercise to lose weight. She completed the Four Square Step Test (FSST) in 14 seconds. His blood pressure is 130/80, his heart rate is 195 beats per minute and his BMI is 41.54. The lab results are as follows: fasting blood glucose: 98 mg/dl TG: 150 mg/dl cholesterol: 180 mg/dl LDL: 90 mg/dl HDL: 35 mg/dl Heart rate is normal. His joints and range of motion are within normal range.</topic><topic number="37">The patient is a 20-year-old Caucasian female, who is admitted to the clinic with unilateral vision loss and facial weakness, diarrhea and stiffness that has lasted for over a day. She went to her doctor, and they did an MRI of her brain, which showed a single plaque in her brain stem. After a few months, she developed weakness in the lower limbs, which led to problems with balance. The second MRI showed another lesion in the left hemisphere of his brain. Recurrent Multiple Sclerosis Remitting (RREM) is confirmed after a second MRI. Her surgical history is significant, she had a caesarean two years ago, and she has a son. He is divorced and currently has no sexual activity. She smokes about 10 cigarettes a day and drinks occasionally. She works as an editor in a publishing house and is happy that she has been able to continue working from home most of the time. She's been on treatment for EAE-EMRD for seven months.</topic><topic number="38">Patient is a 35-year-old female with myasthenia gravis, class II. She suffers from diplopia, fatigue and weakness, which mainly affects the upper limbs. She was tested positive for anti-AChR antibodies and single-fiber electromyography (ZB-EMG-EMG-FU). He takes 60 milligrams of pyridostigmine three times a day. However, he still has symptoms that prevent him from doing his job. She's the lead investigator in the case and the mother of three children. A 70-year-old man with high blood pressure. She doesn't smoke or use any illegal drugs. He drinks alcohol occasionally at social gatherings. Physical examination and laboratory tests did not reveal any other anomalies. The blood pressure is 110/75 hb, 11 g/dL. The leukocytes are 8000/mm3, the platelets are 300000/ml. The creatinine is 0.5 mg/dL. The BUN is 10 mg/dL.</topic><topic number="39">A three-day-old Asian baby breastfed has a rash that started the day before. She was born at 38 weeks and 3 days after an uncomplicated pregnancy. No family history of interest. A baby gets the breastfeeding from its mother. Armpits temperature is 36.3 degrees, heart rate is 154 beats per minute, respiratory rate is 37 breaths per minute, and blood pressure is 65/33 mmHg. It weighs 3.2 kg, measures 53 cm and has a cephalic perimeter of 36 cm. She has scleroderma and hemorrhoids. The heart and lung examination showed no murmur or other abnormalities. Liver growth and placenta are normal. The following laboratory results were obtained from the test: total bilirubin: 21.02 mg/dL Direct bilirubin: 2.04 mg/dL AST: 37 U/L ALT: 20 U/L GGT: 745 U/L Alkaline phosphatase: 531 U/L Creatinine: 0.3 mg/dL Urea: 29 mg/dL Na: 147 mEq/L K: 4.5 mEq/L PCR: 3 mg/L Total blood count within the normal range. Diagnosed as uncomplicated neonatal examination that may require phototherapy.</topic><topic number="40">The patient is a man in his 60s with recurrent headaches, bone pain and complaints of worsening difficulty chewing that began six years ago. The examination shows bilateral swelling around the teeth (molars). The swelling has increased since the last examination. Various extraoral lesions on the head and face. The bumps are painless and are attached to the bone below. A new evaluation shows an increased absorption of the radioactive substance as well as an increase in urinary pyridinoline. Its serum alkaline phosphatase is 300 IU/L (normal range is between 44 and 147 IU/L). Family history is only relevant for the mother's hypertension, and the father's type 2 DM. Paget's diagnosis of bone disease was confirmed and a bisphosphonate will be started as first-line therapy.</topic><topic number="41">A 57-year-old farmer was diagnosed with Parkinson's disease a year ago. He feels the slowness and the trembling of the movements. His medical history is hypertension and hypercholesterolemia. He lives with his wife and has three children. Before she was diagnosed, she was a farmer, a shepherd, a farmer, a farmer, a farmer. The patient complains of tremors and slow movements. He had difficulty walking through a door, because he would become paralyzed and would need help to get through. His handwriting is getting smaller and smaller. She's on levodopa and trihexyphenidyl. She said the medication was helping with the tremors and the slow movements. However, he still has difficulty with stiffness and is somewhat slow in the early stages of movement. He's a cooperative, alert man and shows no signs of dementia. She doesn't smoke or use any illegal drugs.</topic><topic number="42">A 19-year-old Hispanic woman with a pregnancy and childbirth, 32+ 6 weeks of pregnancy, reported to the obstetrics clinic for routine follow-up, complaining of mild headache and swelling of the legs. Primary evaluation showed a blood pressure of 146/99 and a reactive urine stream with 3+ protein. Her blood pressure and urinalysis were normal at the previous visit. A few hours later, the repeat blood pressure is 150/100 mmHg. Laboratory studies showed normal hematocrit, platelet count and liver transaminase levels. He complains of fatigue, but he has no fever or chills. He also has frequent migraines with no visual changes. There were no signs of respiratory distress, cough, chest pain, orthotonia, palpitations, or skin rashes. The physical examination was negative for abdominal pain, intestinal habits, vomiting, diarrhea, dysuria, frequency and also hematuria or foamy urine. Swollen legs were seen, no signs of arthritis or back pain. She has no specific medical history, and is limited to prenatal vitamins. Family history is positive for type 2 diabetes and hypertension. He drinks socially. He doesn't smoke or do drugs. She's had only one sexual partner in the last two years and hasn't used contraception since two years ago. Her BMI was 24 at her first visit, when she was six weeks pregnant. She's gaining normal weight during pregnancy.</topic><topic number="43">The patient is a woman in her 60s who has been admitted to the stroke unit with a history of a second course of intravenous antibiotics for aspiration pneumonia. She has fever and is showing abdominal and lower back pain (eight bowel movements in three hours, each with a lot of liquid faeces and green). The patient has abdominal pain, distention, and hyperactive intestinal noise. He has a high fever (38.4 C), tachycardia (113 beats per minute) and hypotension (80/40 mmHg). The vegetable samples had to be positive for Clostridium difficile toxin.</topic><topic number="44">The patient is a 14-year-old boy with back pain and scoliosis. He has no other medical conditions. He was able to do previously usual activities such as basketball and football; however, recently he has had difficulty doing these activities. The pain is localized in the leg and back and is aggravated by physical activity. He prefers to lie down most of the time. He is not happy with his body language and complains that his shoulders are unbalanced and his head is tilted to the right. The patient is a well-dressed and well-fed adolescent. The patient is a 34-year-old African-American male who was admitted to this clinic with a known history of sickle cell disease. The patient had severe lower back pain, and radiation was applied to both thighs. A score of 9 out of 10. The patient has a positive history of childhood sickle cell crisis. The last two weeks of treatment with oxycodone, he had the same symptoms, which did not help his pain. Her doctor sent her to the emergency department for intravenous pain modulators. The patient's blood pressure is within normal limits. Splenomegaly was not detected on physical examination. He has no positive history of drug allergy. No smoking or use of any illegal drugs. The following is the laboratory test: hb: 8 g/dL Leukocytes: 10000/mm3 Plt: 300000 /ml bCM: 106 fL Hemoglobin electrophoresis: 91% HbS 6% HbF 3% HbA2 AST: 22 U/L ALT: 43 U/L FAL: 53 U/L Ferritin: 1200 ng/ml and is cooperative. Your left shoulder is slightly higher than your right. The scoliosis curvature is measured at 45 degrees. The patient is a candidate for scoliosis surgery based on periodic monitoring of the evoked motor potential (EMP).</topic><topic number="45">The patient is a 34-year-old African-American male who was admitted to this clinic with a known history of sickle cell disease. The patient had severe lower back pain, and radiation was applied to both thighs. A score of 9 out of 10. The patient has a positive history of childhood sickle cell seizures. The last two weeks of treatment with oxycodone, he had the same symptoms, which did not help his pain. Her doctor sent her to the emergency department for intravenous pain modulators. The patient's blood pressure is within normal limits. Splenomegaly was not detected on physical examination. He has no positive history of drug allergy. No smoking or use of any illegal drugs. The laboratory test is as follows: hb: 8 g/dL Leukocytes: 10000/mm3 Plt: 300000 /ml bCM: 106 fL Hemoglobin electrophoresis: 91% HbS 6% HbF 3% HbA2 AST: 22 U/L ALT: 43 U/L FAL: 53 U/L Ferritin: 1200 ng/ml The blood pressure is measured by the blood test and the blood is then analyzed by the blood test.</topic><topic number="46">Patient A is a 30-year-old male who was admitted to hospital after 10 days of coughing, heavy night sweats, and loss of appetite. She traveled to India a month ago and had no positive TB vaccination history. He is a healthy man who works as an engineer in a high-tech company. She doesn't smoke or do illegal drugs. He had fever of 38 degrees Celsius, a heart rate of 115 lpm, a respiratory rate of 22, a PA of 125/75 mmHg and an O2 saturation of 97%. The chest X-ray showed an infiltrate in the middle of the left lung, 1.8 cm in diameter, with signs of cavitation. The sputum smear showed positive sputum culture for Mycobacterium tuberculosis, which is sensitive to first-line anti-tuberculosis drugs (isoniazid, streptomycin, rifanpine and etambutol). The laboratory test is as follows: hb: 13 g/dL Leukocytes: 14000/mm3 Plt: 300000 /ml AST: 13 U/L ALT: 15U/L FAL: 53 U/L Total bilirubin: 0.6 mg/dL Na: 137 mEq/l k: 4 mEq/l Creatinine: 0.5 mg/dL BUN: 10 mg/dL GSV: 120 mm/h The mean blood pressure is the same as that of the blood plasma.</topic><topic number="47">A 62-year-old African-American male with a dark visual spot in the right eye, facial stiffening, facial drooping, and impaired speech was diagnosed with weakness in the upper and lower left limbs. He denied dyspnea, headache, palpitations, chest pain, fever, dizziness, intestinal or urinary incontinence or loss of consciousness. His medical history included hypertension, hyperlipidemia, and hypothyroidism. He smokes a pack of cigarettes a day since he was 40 and drinks five or six beers a week. She doesn't know her family history. He's using levothyroxine, atorbastatin and HTCZ. His vital signs were stable during the primary evaluation. The physical examination revealed a facial rash on the left side, dysarthria, and hemiplegia. The score obtained on the National Institutes of Health Cerebrovascular Accident Scale (NIHSS) was calculated as 7. Early OT-TC angiography of the head and neck revealed no acute discovery within the skull. Tissue activator of the intravenous recombinant plasminogen (t-PA) and high-dose statin therapy were given. The patient was admitted to the intensive care unit for 24-hour monitoring. MRI of the head showed a 1.7 cm acute infarction of the white matter in the right peribentricle and the posterior basal glands.</topic><topic number="48">Fernandez is a 41-year-old professional footballer. She came to the clinic with a foot ache. Physical examination revealed localized scaling and a misalignment between the third and fourth toes of the right foot. It became inflamed and started to hurt, with slight fissures. The back of the foot and the sole were not damaged. There are no signs of any cracking or scratching in the damaged area. She used no topical ointments for the lesion and has no positive history of underlying conditions such as DM. She smokes 15 cigarettes a day and drinks a beer a day. Family history is positive for hyperlipidemia in the mother, myocardial infarction in the father. She has several partners and uses a condom during sex. The physical examination and lab tests were normal. The infection of the foot was confirmed when the fungal hyphae were seen in a microscopic test using wet prepared KOH.</topic><topic number="49">A 12-year-old girl came with her mother to the clinic complaining of short stature, delayed puberty and delayed development. The karyotype test showed 45X and confirmed the diagnosis of Turner syndrome. She's been on GH for the past six months without estrogen therapy to prevent menarche and regain her ideal height. A physical examination has shown that she is obese and suffers from mental retardation. Her breast button was in stage one, pubis and underarm, no thick hair. The last lab test, TSH was at 3, and fasting basal glycemia was 75.</topic><topic number="50">A five-month-old baby was brought to the pediatric surgery clinic with a complaint of empty scrotum on the right side. The baby is the first child born to a healthy mother with a normal vaginal delivery in 38 weeks. Mom had a normal pregnancy with no complications. The baby weighed 3200 grams and measured 50 cm. She's breastfeeding and now weighs five pounds and is two feet tall. Physical evaluation shows no signs of developmental delay. He has a testicle that is visible in the left testicle and a testicle that is invisible in the right testicle. The penis is normal in size and shape and is not circumcised. Diagnostic laparoscopy revealed a testicle that had not been lowered from the abdomen.</topic><topic number="51">The patient is a pregnant (G1 P1) 25-year-old female, gestational age 24 weeks and 3 days, and suddenly had fever and chills, nausea and vomiting. He also complains of dysuria, urges, and frequent bouts of nausea. She also says that she feels a lot of pain on her side. Her vital signs are T 39.7oC, FC 117, R 20 and PA 113/74 mm Hg. Physical examination indicates pain in the growth of two angular costal vertebrae. She has no history of recurrent urinary tract infections prior to pregnancy, nor any other underlying medical conditions. Urine culture showed gram-negative bacterial cells in the form of basil, leukocytes, and leukocyte cylinders. The blood test is negative. A complete blood count shows Hb 12.9 g/dl, Hct 39%, VCM 76 fl and a white blood cell count of 14 120 micral.</topic><topic number="52">A 34-year-old man has been admitted to the clinic complaining of dizziness and a low quality of life since yesterday. She returned a few days ago from an international trip and has been living in a camp in Sudan for a month. She developed stomach upset, followed by swelling and nausea, as well as soft stools. In a short time, she's had a lot of odourless faeces. The carrots are watery and white, but the patient has no fever. Blood pressure is 95/62 lying down and drops to 75/40 standing up. The turbidity of her skin has decreased. His heart rate is 110, and he looks sick with a dry mucous membrane. Under the dark-field microscope of a fresh vegetable sample, V. cholerae was detected. The results of the laboratory tests are as follows: sodium 137 mek/L potassium 2 meq/L chloride 94mek/L CO2 15 mek/L fecal leukocytes are not visible blood hidden in the vegetables negative</topic><topic number="53">The patient is a 34-year-old woman from Jordan, who was admitted to the clinic for general rather than non-specific bone and joint pain. He is married and has three children. The history with the doctor and taking his medication... nothing remarkable. His BMI is 23, his PA is 120/75, his heart rate is 75/min. The laboratory study is noteworthy for its Vit D: 14ng/ml and, otherwise, healthy. The first is that we're not going to be able to get a lot of people to buy our products.</topic><topic number="54">A 57-year-old man was admitted to the clinic for four months of prolonged weight loss and dry cough. CT scan of the chest showed multiple bilateral infiltrates in the upper lobes, as well as a thickened bronchial wall. His clinical history is documented as a positive MPO-ANCA series. Transbronchial biopsy showed necrotic granulomas, which are multinucleated giant cells, and he was diagnosed with Wegener granulomatosis. She's been on a course of corticosteroids and cyclophosphamide for the past four months. The activity score for Birmingham vasculitis (BBAP-BVAS) has been above 4 since the onset of the disease. His final physical examination and laboratory tests were conducted yesterday and the results were these: a healthy, well-fed, uninvestigated, cooperative and alert man. The following table shows the number of deaths by suicide in the United States in the year 2000. The following table shows the number of deaths by suicide in the United States in the year 2000.</topic><topic number="55">A 22-year-old Caucasian man came to the clinic with a history of seizure tremors for over a year. The vibration was in her right hand first, holding something. Then a continuous tremor began, spreading to both hands and legs, including resting. The eye exam showed a Kayser-Fleischer ring. Physical examination revealed the following: hepato-splenomegaly, hypotonia of the upper limbs. She had a constant smile on her face, but an aggressive behavior according to the explanations of her parents. A significant laboratory finding was low serum zeruloplasmin (0.05 g/l) and high copper release in urine within 24 hours (120 g/24 h). Wilson's disease was confirmed due to the high concentration of copper found in the liver (305 &#956;g/g in dry weight of the liver).</topic><topic number="56">The patient is a 41-year-old male with a known case of acromegalia who underwent transesphenoidal surgery four months ago. She came to the clinic to do the follow-up lab work after the primary extraction. Lab results show IGF-1 levels at 4.5 LSN, which is the normal level regardless of sex and age. The random GH level is 4 &#956;g/L. The latest MRI of the brain confirmed a residual pituitary tumor. The medical history is acromegaly, which is caused by a pituitary adenoma, and the recent surgery. He says that after his surgery, he's just taking vitamin D and a multi-vitamin.</topic><topic number="57">The patient is a 41-year-old obese woman who was admitted to the emergency room with abdominal pain and vomiting. The pain started gradually yesterday, and is concentrated in the epigastric and periunbilical regions, radiating to the back. She drinks a lot and doesn't smoke. She has no history of allergies, and she only takes multivitamins every day. Family history is positive for hypertension (mother). She lives with her husband and has three children. When touched, the abdominal area feels painful and soft. Your bowel movements are normal. His heart rate is 115 beats per minute. His arterial pressure is 110/75 mmHg. Laboratory tests are notable for leukocytosis (19.5), water of 8.5, high PCR (145), high amylase (1200) and glucose level of 270. A computed tomography of her abdomen showed acute interstitial pancreatitis edematosa with enlargement of the common cervical canal and intrahepatic canal, which confirms pancreatitis caused by cervical stones. The pregnancy test was negative, and she's not breastfeeding.</topic><topic number="58">The patient is a 17-year-old male who has had an onset of four days ago of severe, migratory pain in the lower right quadrant of the abdomen. The pain is usually accompanied by nausea and vomiting. She had a fever, and palpation, and rebound pain, and defense response. His white blood cell count was high, neutrophils predominant. Computed tomography (CT) showed evidence of acute perforated appendicitis with free fluid in the pelvis. Diagnostic laparoscopy showed phlegm, with no other abdominal abnormalities. At this time, he is a candidate for emergency laparoscopic appendectomy under general anesthesia.</topic><topic number="59">The patient is a 15-year-old male with asthma who was diagnosed about a year ago. She has dyspnea, tightness in the chest, coughing. According to her mother, she wasn't responding to the usual corticosteroid inhaler. She was admitted to the emergency room with a diagnosis of worsening asthma. It's a candidate for treatment with systemic corticosteroids. Spirometry showed that the volume of forced expiration (FEV1) in the first second was at 60% of the expected value. His medical history is irrelevant. My mother and my uncle have a family history of asthma. Treatment was a combination of inhaled corticosteroids and safflower gel.</topic><topic number="60">The patient is a 63-year-old male who has been admitted to the emergency room for two days with acute urinary retention. Abdominopelvic tomography showed an enlarged prostate and a bladder filled with urine. It is a candidate for urethral catheterization and transurethral removal of the prostate (PETU-RTUP). A new evaluation revealed the following: Residue after micturition: 71 ml Prostate volume (direct ultrasound): 63 ml Prostate specific antigen (PSA): 3.5 ng/ml Recent blood biochemistry (3 days ago) was normal: hb: 13.6 g/dL Leukocytes: 133 000/mm3 Platelets: 370 000/ml TP: 12 seconds TTPA: 34 seconds INR: 0.9 Creatinine: 0.5 mg/dL BUN: 10 mg/dL In urine it is Uralysis. Color: yellow Appearance: brownish pH-5.3 Reactive severity: 1.010 gl Nitrite: negative Ceton: none Leukocyte esterase negative gR negative Leukocytes: 2 Leukocytes/high-constitution area u/C: negative</topic><topic number="61">The patient is a 45-year-old postmenopausal woman with cytologically confirmed breast cancer. A thick-needle biopsy showed a two-inch invasive ductal carcinoma in the upper left quadrant. The tumor is HER2 positive and RE/RP negative. The axillary biopsy was positive for five lymph nodes. The chest X-ray showed some metastatic lesions. The patient is on a multivitamin and iron supplement. She doesn't smoke or drink. She is not sexually active and has no children. She's a candidate for a tumor extraction, and she agrees to do this tumor extraction before chemotherapy.</topic><topic number="62">A 46-year-old man with frequent dizziness and migraines. She has a family history of coronary heart disease, but has no other cardiovascular risk factors such as smoking, high blood pressure, and diabetes mellitus, and is physically active. LDL cholesterol and HDL cholesterol were 545 and 53 mg/dl, respectively. Her glucose and triglyceride levels (85 and 158 mg/dl, respectively) were within normal limits. The patient did not use any lipid-lowering medication. Cervical auscultation revealed a 3+/6+ systolic murmur on the neck, radiating from the skull. Ultrasound of the carotid artery showed severe stenosis in the left internal carotid artery (BKA-ACI), and moderate stenosis in the right carotid artery (BKA-ACI), ranging from 40% to 50%. For the left internal carotid artery (BKA-ACI), the cut-off values for maximum systolic velocity (ASM-VMS) and telediastolic velocity (ATD-VTD) were 208.5 cm/s and 54.5 cm/s, respectively; the ASM-VMSa of the right internal carotid artery (BKA-ACI) was 91.72 cm/s, and the VTDa of the BKA-ACI was 37.37 cm/s. Plaque was seen on the anterior and posterior walls of the internal carotid artery and common carotid artery; these were considered to be voluminous plaques, extending up to the middle third of the internal carotid arteries (ICA) and were predominantly ecogenic and hyperecogenic, with less than 50% of the area of the eclucidal area of irregular surface.</topic><topic number="63">A 54-year-old obese woman was admitted to the emergency department, accompanied by vomiting and nausea due to stomach pain that had started four days earlier. Epigastric pain radiates to the upper right quadrant and is exacerbated after eating a fatty food. The patient has had the same pain twice in the last year. Her medical history is marked by hypercholesterolemia and two vaginal births that were abnormal. She's got two kids and she's in menopause. She doesn't smoke, drink or take any illegal drugs. He has a slight fever. Her TA is 150/85, BM is 115, AR is 15, T is 38.2, and SpO2 is 98% at AA, so she's an obese woman with no stress events. Pain in palpation, pain in the epigastrium and pain in the upper right quadrant of palpation, without pain rebound. His bowel movements are normal. Lab tests revealed high VSG and leukoplakia with left-sided deviation. Ultrasound showed multiple sclerosis, scleral softness, and common scleral stones. The smallest pebble is a 14mm.</topic><topic number="64">The patient is a 55-year-old male, diagnosed with HCV two years ago, and recently co-infected with HBV. Past medical history not relevant. She's had the correct IFN, RBV, and antiviral medication for the last six months. The patient is off her other medication. His medical history shows positive enzyme immunoassay for anti-HCV antibodies and positive HCV RNA test. His recent biopsy was negative for hepatocellular carcinoma, and was only notable for chronic swelling consistent with chronic viral hepatitis. There is no evidence of alcoholic liver disease, intestinal varicose hemorrhage, hemochromatosis, autoimmune hepatitis or metabolic liver disease. He's very alert, with no obvious distractions. PA is 130/75, FC is 90/min and BMI is 27. Her tummy is soft, without acidity or growing pains. Lower extremities are normal, no swelling.</topic><topic number="65">The patient is a 25-year-old male with type 1 diabetes, confirmed by molecular analysis seven years ago. She's in the clinic for dyspnea and fatigue from physical activity. After ascending 3 floors she reports mild dysnea, no dysnea at rest and no angina pectoris (New York Heart Association class 2). He's been diagnosed with myocardial disease and will be treated with ACE inhibitors and beta blockers. She's taking 70/30 insulin and vitamin D supplements as well. She had no other significant medical conditions. His medical history is marked with Type 1 DMA in both his uncle and grandfather. The lab results are basal fasting blood glucose 100 mg/dl. The blood glucose at the time of fasting was 100 mg/dl. The HbA1c was 6.5% Cholesterol was 190 mg/dl. The TG was 140 mg/dl. The LDL was 125 mg/dl.</topic><topic number="66">A 16-year-old girl came to the clinic complaining of weight gain and abnormal menstrual cycles. Her body mass index (BMI) was 24, but she gained 5 kg in the last few weeks. She gets tired more and more often, and she doesn't have the energy to go out dancing with her friends. Laboratory tests were notable for high levels of TSH (15 mU/L) and low levels of free T4 (0.18 ng/dl). Her anti-TPO levels were very high (136 IU/ml). He was diagnosed with Hashimoto's disease. He's not a smoker, he's not sexually active.</topic><topic number="67">A cervical cytology of a 54-year-old woman revealed an abnormal intraepithelial/glandular scaly cervical lesion. She tested positive for Human Papillomavirus 16 (HPV 16). She has sex with her husband and has four children. She's in menopause and not using contraception. She's been known to smoke and drink a lot. Otherwise, he's in good health. She was offered a convalescence.</topic><topic number="68">The patient is a 23-year-old male who was admitted to the hospital with arterial hypertension (175/95 mmHg) and signs of sepsis. She subsequently developed respiratory and renal insufficiency, requiring mechanical ventilation and hemodialysis respectively. The blood smear showed microangiopathic hemolytic anemia and thrombocytopenia. Blood tests showed high levels of lactate dehydrogenase (LDH) and low levels of human supplemental C3, with a normal coagulation profile. He was diagnosed with atypical hemolytic uremic syndrome. He was treated with plasmapheresis and corticoids. She had previously been vaccinated with the conjugated meningococcal vaccine of the ACWY group and the meningococcal vaccine of group B. Genetic testing showed ADAMTS13 was &gt;10%.</topic><topic number="69">A healthy 67-year-old woman came to our clinic to get her flu shot in early October. He works in a rehab facility and he has no underlying medical condition. This is the first vaccination this year. She's in menopause and she has four children. And she doesn't have any. He's on a daily multivitamin and antihypertensive. He exercises 30 minutes a day, at least five days a week. She has no allergies to any food or medication.</topic><topic number="70">A 46-year-old Asian woman, a patient with Major Depressive Disorder (MDD-MDD), complains of persistent feelings of sadness and loss of interest in daily activities. She says his mood is usually depressing. He's been experiencing a power outage and loss of availability almost daily. She's been on antidepressants for six months, but her symptoms have not improved. She doesn't drink or smoke. She exercised at least 30 minutes a day, but she had not had enough energy for the last three weeks. He's also been having some digestive problems lately. He is married and has four children. She's in the menopause. My husband was diagnosed with colon cancer a year ago and is undergoing chemotherapy. His medical history is normal. There's nothing in the family history of any psychological problems. On the Ham-D scale, it scored 20.</topic><topic number="71">The patient is a 34-year-old obese woman who came to the clinic for weight problems. She is 165 cm (5 ft 5 in) tall and weighs 113 kg (BMI: 41.5). In the past, it used anti-obesity agents and appetite suppressants without success. She complains of sleep apnea, SOPA, and self-doubt. He's a high school teacher. She's been married for five years. She has not used any method of contraception in the past four months, and she has no prior pregnancy. He rarely exercises, and seems to have difficulty moving. He can't complete the four-square-step test in less than 15 seconds. She doesn't smoke or do drugs. Blood pressure is 130 over 80, heart rate is 195 per minute, and BMI is 41.54. Laboratory results: Fasting serum glucose: 98 mg/dL TG: 150 mg/dL Cholesterol: 180 mg/dL LDL: 90 mg/dL HDL: 35 mg/dL He is currently considering the possibility of laparoscopic gastric bypass.</topic><topic number="72">Our patient is a 16-year-old girl who has recently been diagnosed with myasthenia gravis, grade II. Diplopia and weakness in the upper limbs. He has also tested positive for anti-AChR antibodies and single-fiber electromyography (SFEMG). She is currently undergoing treatment with acetylcholinesterase inhibitors and immunosuppressants. However, it retains some of the symptoms. She doesn't smoke or do illegal drugs. She is not sexually active and her periods are regular. Our physical examination and lab tests have failed to detect any other anomalies. The patient's blood pressure is 110/75 Hb: 11 g/dl. The leukocytes are 8000/mm3 and the platelets are 300000/ml. The creatinine is 0.5 mg/dl. The BUN is 10 mg/dl.</topic><topic number="73">Our patient is a three-day-old female newborn with a day-earlier onset of hiccups. She was born at 34 weeks and was kept in an incubator because of her pregnancy. His vital signs were: arm temperature: 36.3 &#176;C, heart rate: 154 beats/min, respiratory rate: 37 breaths/min and blood pressure: 65/33 mmHg. Its weight is 2.1 kg, its height is 45 cm and the head perimeter is 32 cm. She has a yellow sclerosis and a corpus ictus. Liver and pancreas are normal on palpation. Laboratory results were as follows: Bilirubin, total: 21.02 mg/dL Direct bilirubin: 2.04 mg/dL AST: 37 U/L ALT: 20 U/L GGT: 745 U/L Alkaline phosphatase: 531 U/L Creatinine: 0.3 mg/dL Urea: 29 mg/dL Na: 147 mEq/L K: 4.5 mEq/L PCR: 3 mg/L Total blood count within the normal range. She's diagnosed with infantile hyperkinesia, which requires phototherapy.</topic><topic number="74">The patient is a 53-year-old male with recurrent migraines, bone pain throughout the body, and difficulty chewing, which began six years ago and have been worsening. The scan shows bilateral swelling around the teeth. The swelling has increased since the last examination. We have multiple extraoral lesions on the head and face. The bumps are painless and are attached to the bone below. An additional evaluation showed an increased adherence of radioactive substance and an increase in pyridinoline in the urine. The serum alkaline phosphatase is 300 IU/L (common range: 44147 IU/L). The patient's sister had the same problem. At the age of 52, Paget was diagnosed with osteoporosis. The diagnosis of Paget's bone disease has been confirmed and a bisphosphonate will be started as first-line treatment.</topic><topic number="75">This is a 55-year-old man who was recently diagnosed with Parkinson's disease. Complains of tremors and slowness of movement. His condition is classified as mild, stage I of Hoehn-Yahr's. His medical history is relevant to hypertension and hypercholesterolemia. He lives with his wife. They have three children. He was active in horticulture before his diagnosis. Complains of tremors and slow movements. He had difficulty getting through a door, because he was frozen and needed help to get in. His handwriting is getting smaller and smaller. They're giving her levodopa and trihexyphenidol. He's a cooperative, alert man and shows no signs of dementia. She doesn't smoke or do illegal drugs.</topic></topics>