<topics task="2021 TREC Clinical Trials"><topic number="1">Patient is a 45-year-old male with a history of anaplastic spinal stenosis, complicated by severe weakness of the lower extremities and urinary retention. In the report: hypertension, chronic pain, high-dose steroid therapy, condition after the Foley catheter. Post-radiotherapy condition of an inoperable Th-L-square anaplastic stellation, complicated by progressive lower limb weakness and urinary retention. The patient initially reported weakness in the right lower leg, difficulty walking, and numbness in the front of the right thigh. The MRI showed a tumor in the spinal cord cone, which was removed and found to be anaplastic stellation. The therapy included radiation therapy to the local area of the heart. Th10-Th11, followed by 11 cycles of temozolomide for 7 days and 7 days off. Then, irinotecan (CPT-11) was administered every 4 weeks with Avastin Q2 weeks/2 weeks off and the cycle repeated.</topic><topic number="2">A 48-year-old male with hyperlipidaemia, hypertension, double-flap aortic valve and history of nicotine intolerance reported to the lead cardiologist [**2148-10-1**] with progressive obstructive sleep apnea (OBS) and swelling of the lower extremities. Transcranial echo (TTE) showed severe aortic valve stenosis with worsening left ventricular function. The left ventricular ejection fraction was 25%. Right ventricular pressure was 41 and both atrial enlargements were found. The study was notable for aortic valve obstruction 2+ with mild mitral obstruction. The patient was discharged from the cardiac clinic with the recommendation to use Furosemide (Lasix) and a Beta-blocker BB (which he did not tolerate). Eventually, he came to the clinic for evaluation due to progression of OBS and swelling of the kneecap. On admission, echo-reconfirmed critical aortic valve narrowing with left ventricular hypertrophy with dilation of the lumen and severe generalized hypokinesis, severe aortic valve narrowing at the base of the bicuspid valve, dilated ascending aorta, mild constrictive pulmonary hypertension. The patient underwent preoperative diagnostic tests for valve replacement, including computed tomography of the chest and cervical artery ultrasound (moderate, heterogeneous atherosclerotic plaque with bilateral internal cervical artery (ICA) narrowing 1-39%). The patient also underwent right-sided cardiac catheterization to assess pulmonary arterial pressure, which did not show angiographic coronary artery flow restriction.</topic><topic number="3">A 32-year-old woman came in with a severe, "exploding" headache. According to her and her husband, yesterday, when she got up, she hit her head on the corner of the kitchen cabinet. The next morning, she had a sudden, "exploding" headache. She went to the hospital, where a head CT scan showed a significant amount of blood in the right ventricle. The neurosurgeon examined her for spontaneous intracompartmental hemorrhage against a vascular malformation. They did a brain angiogram, which showed abnormal vascularization with a left temporal vein drainage deep into the white matter, which confirmed an arteriovenous malformation. The painkillers were relieving the headache, which was constant. The patient refused to be subjected to this test, but she was able to move around without difficulty. She was discharged home with her husband on [**2155-12-6**].</topic><topic number="4">A 44-year-old woman with polycystic ovary syndrome (PCOS), obesity, hypertension in the history, who had symptoms of cystitis, was found to have a large cardiac output by chance. Pericardiocentesis was performed, and the fluid analysis confirmed Burkitt's lymphoma. The oocyte fluid contained monotypic CD10+ B cells with FMC-7, CD19, CD20 expression and MYC gene rearrangement, with restriction of the light chain of kappa, which corresponded to a diagnosis of Burkitt' s lymphoma. Subsequent lumbar puncture and bone marrow biopsy showed no changes, indicating primary cardiac lymphoma. The MRI of the heart showed a mass measuring 3 cm x 1 cm on the lateral wall of the right atrium, near the atrioventricular junction. Medical history: Rare migraine 2. What is it? Blood pressure 3. Obesity 4. The following table summarises the data for the following groups of patients: Viral encephalitis/cerebrospinal fluid infection --&gt; intracerebral haemorrhage --&gt; seizure/stroke ([**2137**]) = on the basis of acute sinusitis, which causes mild surviving non-focal lesions. The sixth. Cerebrospinal fluid leakage with meningitis, condition after lumbar drainage 7. Thyroiditis of the right lower extremity, condition after filtering of the main vein 8. Surgery of the knee</topic><topic number="5">74 male, with a history of coronary artery disease, CABG status, EF 60% ejection fraction, previous stroke (no surviving lesions), hypertension, Hodgkin's lymphoma HL, type 2 diabetes, moderate to severe peripheral vascular atherosclerosis, was referred to the cardiology department for evaluation of peripheral arterial atherosclerosis. The scan revealed bruising over the carotid arteries in his neck. After further interview, the patient reported: occasional dizziness, no previous fainting, occasional hypertension, denied chest pain/ obstructive sleep apnea (OBS). No sensory or motor defects. Patient mentions that he may have had a stroke 10-15 years ago with no signs of any abnormalities. Before the CABG, all he had was excessive sweating. During the subsequent interview, the patient denied chest pain, shortness of breath, night-time shortness of breath, orthopnea, palpitations, fainting or a pre-concussion state. He passed a cervical arterial ultrasound, which showed significant bilateral cervical arterial narrowing, L&gt;P. The angiogram showed 80% constriction of the right carotid artery and 90% of the left carotid artery. The cerebral angiography revealed the additional carotid: the right anterior artery (ACA) and the middle cerebral artery (MCA) and the left anterior carotid artery (ACA) and the left median cerebral artery (MCA). Coronary heart disease CABG at [**2154**] ([**Hospital1 112**]) Stroke Surgery Lateral carotid artery atherosclerosis Anaemia Peripheral arterial atherosclerosis Hypertension Diabetes complicated: retinopathy and peripheral neuropathy After surgery Eclipse Thyroid tumour Polyps of the colon After resection Painful lower back Protein After a right elbow fracture in childhood Arthritis</topic><topic number="6">A 55-year-old patient with a history of chronic renal failure, receiving haemodialysis and peritoneal dialysis, presented with watery diarrhoea, no blood in the stool and weakness. Two previous C. difficile infections, most recently last month. She was on antibiotics before the last party. She was then treated for C. difficile for 14 days with oral vancomycin. The patient was initially admitted to the ICU in a sepsis picture with leukocytosis but no fever, where she received pressure amines (noradrenaline) until the morning [**8-26**]. Upon admission, the patient tested positive for C. difficile and was found to have leukocytosis consistent with C. difficile infection. The patient was initially enrolled on oral vancomycin, intravenous metronidazole and oral metronidazole and was switched to oral vancomycin and oral metronidazole on [**8-29**] as her condition improved. The patient was treated with vancomycin for an extended cycle of 6 weeks due to recurrent C. difficile infections. The patient was also advised to take probiotics and disinfect the home after discharge.</topic><topic number="7">A 60-year-old male with cirrhosis of the liver, C-hepatitis, second degree esophageal varices, recently hospitalized for upper gastrointestinal bleeding [**2-9**] induced by nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory drugs (NSAIDs), was referred to the emergency department by the hepatology office for a fresh onset of slurred speech and thinking disorders. The patient also describes a balance disorder that led to a fall in which he may have hit his head. According to the last note from the hepatology office, the patient had not taken ethanol for a year (confirmed by the patient), the result of the test for the presence of alcohol in the body was negative. The CT scan was normal, and the neurological exam ruled out an ischemic stroke. The patient was given a preliminary diagnosis of hepatic encephalopathy and lactulose was switched on. Liver function tests showed a marked increase in total and direct bilirubin since the last visit. Another worrying symptom was an increase in alpha-fetoprotein (AFP). It could be a progression of cirrhosis, because interferon has failed twice. The patient should continue on an outpatient basis for further action. Medical examination: HCV-induced cirrhosis of the liver (interferon x2 treatment not responding) Gastropathy of the throat Gastroesophageal varices Grade II Hypertension Recent hospitalization [**4-/2150**]: upper gastrointestinal bleeding caused by non-steroidal anti-inflammatory drugs [**2-9**]</topic><topic number="8">A 57-year-old male with chronic lymphocytic leukaemia (CLL) and large cell metastasis reported a recurrence of the disease on [**10/2119**] with elevated white blood cell count and LDH. At the time, he had no signs of splenomegaly or cytopenia. But he had extensive lymphadenopathy. Patient completed four FCR cycles, which were completed in 09/[**2119**]. The patient had an excellent response to treatment and was followed for approximately two years after treatment. Then it came back in [**7-/2122**] with an increasing white blood cell count, with about 50% lymphocytes and a moderately elevated LDH. The patient also had mildly severe, detectable lymphadenopathy. The patient received four cycles of PCR, but due to a lack of significant response, the treatment regimen was changed to R-CVP, of which he received two cycles. Again, no response to treatment. However, the patient was in good general condition. Eventually, the patient was prescribed alemtuzumab (trade name Campath). Lymphocytosis was reversed and white blood cell counts were significantly reduced, but no significant improvement in the reduction of extensive lymphadenopathy was observed. Eventually, the left lymph node in his neck was enlarged, and he had a biopsy. He was diagnosed with Richter's transformation.</topic><topic number="9">41-year-old male with a history of severe mental retardation, congestive heart failure, epilepsy with right-sided facial tremor and generalized tremor, in a nursing home, required 20 mg diazepam to stop the seizure. A patient who remained on outpatient treatment developed focal secondary generalized epilepsy, probably due to congenital brain hypoxia and possibly associated with fading changes seen on MRI, particularly in the left temporal lobe. He had his first seizures at the age of 13, which were generalized seizures. He was found by his family. The second robbery occurred two years after the first. The patient was given phenytoin and phenobarbital. For the next 20 years, he never had a seizure. Recently, the patient was gradually weaned off phenytoin, and it was retrospectively concluded that it was probably necessary to keep the patient seizure-free. The patient had no further events during the hospitalization and was in a stable condition at discharge. EEG results are in the works. History of illness: Epilepsy as described above, congestive heart failure, depression</topic><topic number="10">22-year-old female, 5-year history of systemic mast cell disease, with exacerbations usually 3 times a year, manifested by redness and tachycardia, with suspected exacerbation, otherwise healthy. This is the third flare-up in two months for a patient who's still on a gradual dose reduction of steroids, which is new to her. The patient responded well to 125 mg intravenous steroids every 8 hours and to diphenhydromine intravenously, with continued home treatment recommended. Peripheral blood count was at baseline, with normal smear. The serum tryptazoid count was high, 84. The patient failed the aspirin challenge test because of an adverse reaction. She was stabilized with intravenous steroids and intravenous diphenhydramine and then readmitted to the ward. The patient continued with her previous histamine receptor blocker and then switched from intravenous to oral steroids and diphenhydramine. Patient was observed overnight and discharged with recommendations for her current medication, gradual reduction of prednisone dose, IPP as a gastroprotective agent, calcium and vitamin D, and sulfamethoxazole + trimethoprim for pneumonia caused by Pneumocystis jiroveci</topic><topic number="11">75-year-old male, history of metastatic thyroid cancer, standing after 19 sessions of radiation therapy, reported severe dysphagia for 2 days on solid food, difficulty swallowing food, weight loss of 9 kg in the last few weeks and mild sleepiness. Right-sided cervical tumour confirmed metastases of thyroid cancer -- post-neck tumour resection; failure to perform thyroidectomy -- high risk of bleeding, close proximity of the trachea and the dorsal laryngeal nerve and large tumour size -- post-neck radiotherapy -- post-radioiodine treatment -- metastases to lymph nodes and adrenal glands * post-operative hernia * post-tonsillectomy</topic><topic number="12">A 34-year-old woman with Marfan syndrome and severe mitral valve prolapse with impaired permeability, who was scheduled for mitral valve repair, stopped coming in for follow-up visits. Patient is symptomatic and is currently being prepared for mitral valve repair/replacement surgery. The ejection fraction of the EF is 65% in transcranial echocardiography. Medical examination: Marfan syndrome Mitral valve leak with severe mitral insufficiency Esophageal reflux disease Diabetes mellitus in pregnancy reported Pregnant hypertension Obesity Caesarean section x 2 Laser eye surgery Cataract surgery Foot surgery (bone shortening)</topic><topic number="13">62-year-old male with history of stroke, neurogenic blister with a surgical suprapubic catheter, multiple prior hospitalizations for urinary tract infections (UTI), disturbances of consciousness and urosepsis, reported to hospital for urosepsis that resolved following treatment with vancomycin/ meropenem. CT scan showed deposits in the left urethra, no obstruction, no signs of urethral stricture. There was a significant leak near the top of the trachea. Treatment was initiated with oxybutynin and then changed to tolterodine. The leak didn't worry the urologist, who scheduled a follow-up appointment for next week. Stroke-related neurogenic blister, supraorbital catheter-related recurrent urinary tract infections with Klebsiella/ Pseudomonas Non-cerebral lymphoma of the left margin of the occipital lobe diagnosed at 03 (post-R-CHOP x 6 cycles) Bell' s palsy Mild prostate enlargement (BPH) Hypertension Subilus-related with colostomy-like eruption Viral hepatitis Coglobulin-related systemic lupus erythematosus (SLE) with transverse inflammation of the spine, anti-DNA, anti-DNA, insulin-dependent diabetes Mellitus Inflammation of the colon in stage IV? Infections of the urinary tract  Pseudomonas and enterococci</topic><topic number="14">70 year old COPD patient, initially on 2.5 to 3.5 L oxygen, obstructive sleep apnea (OBS) and obese hypo-ventilation syndrome, decompensated chronic heart failure, discharged from hospital [**2132-8-24**] now reports: arousal and mood disturbances, hypoxia and oxygen saturation of 70% on 5 L BipA. Patient was aroused and then asleep on admission. Daughter reported increased arousal and mood disturbances for 2-3 days with oxygen saturation of 60-70% at home. The daughter also noticed an increase in swelling of her lower extremities and weight gain, which prompted her to telephone her GP and increase the dose of Furosemide from 80 mg daily to 100 mg daily, which caused a slight decrease in swelling. Patient experienced decreased appetite, oral medication, decreased energy levels at home, difficulty in performing daily activities. She hasn't had any recent symptoms of fever, cough, chills, sputum distention, chest pain, abdominal pain, or any other ailments other than chronic right hip pain for the past one to two months. The daughter also reports following her doctor's orders and following the BiPap at night. The following are the most commonly reported adverse reactions: &#8226; heart failure, &#8226; coronary heart disease, &#8226; post-caBG with 4 vessels, &#8226; chronic heart failure, &#8226; EF 55%, &#8226; mild aortic stenosis, &#8226; obese hypoventilation syndrome, &#8226; obstructive sleep apnea, &#8226; type 2 diabetes, &#8226; ventricular fibrillation, &#8226; post-ICD, &#8226; hypothyroidism, &#8226; schizophrenia, &#8226; chronic obstructive pulmonary disease, &#8226; pneumonia treated at [**4-7**] in [**Hospital1**]</topic><topic number="15">A 70-year-old woman with a history of coronary artery disease recently noticed a tumor in her abdomen, accompanied by fever/chills and a shift in the white blood cell count to the left. In the last few weeks before the admission, she had pain in the middle of her abdomen, radiating to her left side. The pain is persistent throughout the day, not aggravated by eating, accompanied by vomiting and aggravated by coughing. A non-contrast abdominal CT scan [**4-20**] was performed, which revealed a large, heterogeneous mass in the upper left abdominal cavity measuring 9,5 x 7,5 x 6,0 cm. The patient underwent endoscopic ultrasound (EUS) with a biopsy. The biopsy results were consistent with pancreatic adenocarcinoma, located in the head of the pancreas. A mass was also seen on the CT scan near the splenic flexure/ tail of the pancreas, which was probably pus, considering the recent history of diverticulitis, the mass was considered to be an infected fluid or pus reservoir. The patient has been treated with intravenous antibiotics (piperacillin + azobactam, followed by ceftriaxone and metronidazole) and will continue to receive them until consultation with her doctor, as an outpatient. Medical examination: Coronary artery disease with angioplasty in [**State 108**] one year ago 2. The mitral valve is leaking 3. Aortic Flicker 4. The heart is beating. Hyperlipidemia was 5. Blood pressure 6. The following table summarises the data for the period from 1 January to 31 December 2015: What is it? Thyroid insufficiency? The following table summarises the data for the period from 1 January 2014 to 31 December 2015: The following table summarises the data for the following groups of patients:</topic><topic number="16">A 79-year-old woman with multifactorial chronic hypoxaemia and dyspnoea, probably due to dilated heart failure, pulmonary hypertension, probably secondary to chronic ASD and COPD, treated with 5 litres of home oxygen, was admitted due to increasing dyspnoea. Her consultant cardiologist recommended a right ventricular catheterization to assess the response to sildenafil, but the patient refused. Her pulmonologist recommended an empirical trial of sildenafil, as part of a compassionate use program, because of severe respiratory symptoms that prevented her from living outside the hospital. Patient tolerated the trial in hospital conditions without hypotension. The patient should report to the pulmonologist for a follow-up visit to initiate chronic sildenafil treatment on an outpatient basis after prior consent. - - - Condition after surgery for atrial septal defect [**6-17**] complicated by atrial arrest with implantation of a pacemaker. - Congestive heart failure, estimated dry body weight 94 kg - Pulmonary hypertension (RVSP 75 in [**11-24**]) considered secondary to long-term ASD - COPD at home with O2 (5 l NC) with baseline saturation from high 80 to low 90 during this therapy. - Obstructive sleep apnea OBS not meeting CPAP recommendations - Mild mitral valve obstruction - Microcytic anaemia - Thyroid insufficiency - Condition after appendectomy, condition after cholecystectomy ('[**33**]) - Pancreatitis with biliary stones, condition after ECPW, sphincterotomy - Elevated phosphatase levels secondary to amiodarone alkali</topic><topic number="17">64 years of age, multiple myeloma patient, after allogeneic bone marrow transplantation with relapsed disease and systemic amyloidosis (involving lungs, tongue, bladder, heart), haemodialysed due to chronic renal failure, which is manifested by malaise, weakness and generalized body pain for 2 days. She was admitted last week with hypercalcemia and has been treated with pamidronium 30 mg, calcitonin and dialysis. The patient was initially treated with melphalan and prednisone, followed by VAD and autologous stem cell transplantation. She was given thalidomide (velcade) and thalidomide for a relapse of the spike, but these were also eventually discontinued because of the increased swelling and renal impairment.</topic><topic number="18">78-year-old male with a history of mild prostate hypertrophy, a condition that follows numerous urological procedures, including an epidermal prostatectomy. He was found to have low diuresis, and his bladder examination showed 360 ml of fluid. The staff were unable to put the Foley catheter in. A urologist was consulted, a flexible cystoscope was performed in the OIOM, and a severe 2 cm narrowing of the urethral bladder was found. We were able to insert a small catheter and leave it in place. The patient had a leak around the catheter that eventually fell out, but the patient had good diuresis and a bladder examination was performed every 4 hours after miction to make sure there was no large amount of residual volume. The urologist suggested that once the patient was stable, he would need to be taken to the operating room for surgical removal of the stenosis.</topic><topic number="19">A 65-year-old male with a history of coronary artery disease and a history of heart attack, hyperlipidemia, hypertension, ventricular hypertension and fainting was admitted this morning for evaluation of fainting and ventricular arrhythmia. He was recently discharged from the hospital after testing negative for fainting, which also included wearing a Holter ECG. The patient was examined in an outpatient setting and monitored for 40 seconds of ventricular tachycardia (VT) followed by bradycardia at a rate of 39 beats per minute (39 beats per minute), which was consistent with the symptoms. Last night, the patient had a monomorphic VT, registered on the telemetry. The patient was unresponsive to stimuli. CPR was initiated when it was not certain that the patient had a pulse. Within a minute, the patient's heartbeat was back. The patient reported no symptoms prior to this episode. At this time, the patient is experiencing a state of pre-consciousness and nausea, but denies chest pain. The patient will be transferred to the cardiac intensive care unit for cardiac catheterization and invasive cardiac electrophysiology (EPS).</topic><topic number="20">A 35-year-old woman came in with acne and mild hirsutism. Preliminary tests showed elevated testosterone levels. Recently, she noticed that her hands and feet were gradually getting bigger, and she noticed that the ring was getting too small for her finger. There's irregularity in the menstrual cycle, and there's also nipple discharge. He also has a positive history of snoring and headaches. Physical examination revealed subtle facial features that suggest acromegaly and prognatism. Field of view is normal in the comparative study. Hirsutism, thickening of soft tissues and excessive sweating of the hands and feet were observed. Laboratory studies in the fasted state showed IGF-1 levels of 968 ng/ml and spontaneous growth hormone (GH) secretion of 19.7 ng/ml. Magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) revealed a macrogrucoma without the leak. Since the diagnosis was confirmed, she's been on a steady dose of octreotide. The patient is married with two children. She uses the IUD as a method of contraception</topic><topic number="21">Patient is a 57-year-old male with abdominal pain and vomiting. The pain started gradually about 20 hours ago in the area of the abdomen and the navel, radiating to the back. The patient drinks about 60 units of alcohol a week and smokes 22 cigarettes a day. He's healthy, no allergies on his record, not taking any medication. Family history shows type 2 diabetes (father and sister). He lives alone and has no children. The belly is sticky and soft. Bowel peristalsis is normal. Pulse is 115 over the minute, and blood pressure is 110 over 75 mmHg. In laboratory tests, the following are noted: leukocytosis (19.5), urea 8.5, high CRP (145), high amylase (1200) and glycaemic level 15. The imaging showed no acute pancreatitis with a pancreatic duct obstruction.</topic><topic number="22">31-year-old female complaining of abdominal pain. The pain started last night as a diffuse abdominal discomfort. The patient had a decreased appetite and was in poor health. In the morning, the pain intensified, became severe, and localized in the right lower quadrant of the abdomen. Temperature is within normal limits, vital signs are normal. Local tenderness and muscular defenses were observed during palpation of the right lower abdominal quadrant. Palpation of the left lower quadrant of the abdomen causes pain on the right side. Lab tests show leukocytosis is present. CT scan of the abdominal cavity with contrast shows the presence of a bulging appendix with a thickened wall without perforation, abscesses and tangles. The patient was scheduled for laparoscopic appendectomy under general anesthesia.</topic><topic number="23">A 39-year-old man came into the clinic with a cough and shortness of breath that didn't go away after he replaced his inhaler. These symptoms have persisted for 5 days in the past 2 weeks. He doubled his oral corticosteroid last week. He's a chef and has been suffering from asthma for the past three years, and he suffers from frequent coughing, wheezing, shortness of breath, and chest tightness. Symptoms become more severe within 1 to 2 hours of starting work each day and increase throughout the work week. His symptoms go away in an hour or two outside of work. Spirometry was performed and showed a first second expiratory volume (FEV1) of 63% of the normal value. His medical records show seasonal allergic rhinitis, which occurs in the summer. He doesn't smoke or use drugs. Family history shows asthma in his father and sister. She's currently on an inhaled corticosteroid (ICS) and fluticasone 500 mcg/salmeterol 50 mcg, one inhalation twice a day.</topic><topic number="24">The patient is a 55-year-old male who has been seeing his primary care physician for nine months for symptoms of the lower urinary tract, such as frequent urination, urge to urinate, poor urine flow, incomplete emptying, and interrupted flow. Further diagnostic findings: Results from the IPSS Microscopic Symptoms Questionnaire: 15 Residual urine volume after micturition: 70 ml Prostate volume (TRUS): 60 ml Prostate specific antigen (PSA) concentration: 3.2 ng/ml Maximum urine flow rate: 10 ml/s at a urine volume of 130 ml In addition, he is healthy and receives only 1000 units of vitamin D per day. The most recent biochemical blood test (3 days ago) was normal: Hgb: 13.5 g/dl WBC: 135000/mm3 Plt: 350000/ml PT: 11 seconds PTT: 35 seconds INR: 0.9 Creatinine: 0.5 mg/dl BUN: 10 mg/dl U/A: Colour: yellow Appearance: hazy PH: 5.3 Specific density: 1.010 Glucose: 100 Nitrites: negative Ketones: no Leukocyte Esterase: negative RBC: negative WBC: 2 in the field of view Bacteria: negative</topic><topic number="25">A post-mono-screening ultrasound in a 42-year-old postmenopausal patient showed an abnormality in her right breast. The breast exam showed no detectable tumors. A colonoscopy was performed, which revealed an infiltrating, 1 .8 cm diameter, ductal breast cancer in the left upper outer quadrant. He had a lumpectomy, and the surgical margins were clear. The tumor was HER2-positive and ER/PR-negative. A section of the temporal lobe was taken, where one of the 12 lymph nodes was positive. Chest X-rays showed no abnormalities. She's taking a daily multivitamin called Healthy Women and she's not taking any other medications. He smokes a lot and drinks alcohol occasionally. She's in a relationship with one partner and has three pregnancies and three live births on her record. She breastfed all three of her children.</topic><topic number="26">A 45-year-old female was referred to the emergency department with abdominal pain lasting approximately 4 days, accompanied by nausea and 2 episodes of vomiting. The pain is localized to the abdominal area and radiates to the right upper quadrant. The pain is worse after eating fatty foods. Patient's had similar pain twice in the last year. In the report, hypercholesterolemia and two caesarean sections. She has two kids and she's in menopause. He doesn't smoke, drink or use drugs. She has a slight fever. Her blood pressure is 150/85, HR 115, RR 15, T 38.2, SpO2 98% in the RA exam. During the palpation, she feels tenderness in the abdomen and tenderness in the right upper quadrant, Blumberg negative. Bowel peristalsis is normal. Laboratory studies show elevated OB and leukocytosis with left shift. The ultrasound showed some gallstones and gallstones. The largest gallstone is 0.7 centimeters. Her consulting surgeon recommended a planned cholecystectomy.</topic><topic number="27">A 53-year-old male has been chronically infected with HCV for 2 years. His report only shows his post-op ACL surgery at age 20. She has been on combination therapy with interferon IFN (100 mg/ week) and ribavirin RBV (400 mg/ day) for 9 months. 6 months ago, direct antiviral drugs were added to the treatment. HCV RNA and immuno-enzymatic antibody test results were positive in previous studies. The last biopsy showed no hepatocellular carcinoma, only a chronic inflammatory condition consistent with chronic viral hepatitis. No signs of alcoholic liver disease, bleeding from esophageal veins, haemochromatosis, autoimmune hepatitis or non-alcoholic fatty liver disease were found. Patient is conscious, no acute symptoms. Blood pressure is 130 over 75. Heart rate is 90 over the minute. The abdomen is soft, no abscess or tenderness. The lower extremities are normal, no swelling.</topic><topic number="28">A 60-year-old Spaniard reported with shortness of breath from the previous day. The symptoms started suddenly and gradually worsened. He's had COPD for two years. In FEV1/FVC spirometry after administration of bronchodilator = 60% of the normal value. He smokes 20 cigarettes a day. In the report: benign prostatic hyperplasia (BPH), for which he uses tamsulosin. Family history: brother with high blood pressure. He uses salbutamol and ipratropium every four hours, vitamin D3 at a dose of 1,000 units a day, and tamsulosin for mild prostate hypertrophy. He's a fat man, in serious condition, but he's alert and aware. Life-threatening parameters: Blood pressure is 135/80 Breathing rate is 25/min Heart rate is 75 beats per minute BMI is 40 Blood oxygen saturation is 90%</topic><topic number="29">A 24-year-old male with type 1 diabetes for 11 years came to the emergency room with hyperglycaemia and concern for possible ketoacidosis after 3 days of no insulin. The patient reports that he is currently homeless and has lost his supply of insulin, syringes, a glucometer and a glucose meter. The patient claims that at the time of initial diagnosis of type 1 diabetes, he was hospitalized with a glucose level &gt; 1000 mg/dl. At the time, he was suffering from polygamy, polydipsia and polyphagia. He reports that he has been taking insulin since his diagnosis and has never been prescribed oral antidiabetic medication. He has recently used insulin glargine 55 units once daily and insulin aspart 3 times daily. The patient had a history of ketogenic episodes that led to hospitalization. During this episode of hyperglycaemia, he has no nausea, vomiting, or abdominal discomfort, and he appears healthy. The test chemical is a substance that is not a carcinogen and is not a carcinogen in the same species as the test chemical.</topic><topic number="30">A 33-year-old female patient complained of fatigue, weight gain, and irregular spotting between periods. No hirsutism or nipple discharge. Her BMI was 34. In laboratory studies: high level of TSH (13 mU/l) and low level of free thyroxine (0.2 ng/dl). The anti-TPO antibody level was extremely high (120 IU/ ml). She was diagnosed with Hashimoto's thyroiditis. Her aunt, brother and mother have the same disease. After starting to take 250 mcg of levothyroxine daily, symptoms improved significantly and menstruation returned to normal. She's still overweight, and her BMI is 31. Her last thyroid profile showed all of her scores, except for the anti-TPO antibodies, to be within the normal range: TSH: 2.35 mU/l Free thyroxine: 2.7 ng/dl</topic><topic number="31">Patient is a 37-year-old female who came to the clinic for a routine blood test. The study showed stage 1B cervical cancer. She has three sexual partners and four children. She's going through a fallopian tube. He smokes 30 packs a year and drinks a lot. Besides, she's healthy. She was offered a radical hysterectomy.</topic><topic number="32">A 17-year-old boy complains of vomiting, diarrhea without blood, abdominal pain, fever, chills and loss of appetite for the past three days. He ate a salad at a restaurant before he got diarrhea. The study found pale skin, jaundice and bloated abdominal tenderness. The laboratory results were as follows: Haemoglobin: 9.7 g/dl Blood platelets: 110,000/mm3 Creatinine: 3.6 mg/dl Urinary nitrogen (BUN): 73 mg/dl Direct bilirubin: 2.4 mg/dl Lactic dehydrogenase (LDH): 881 IU/l (standard: 110265 IU/l) Peripheral blood smear was found to have a moderate number of schistocytes. E. coli stx1/stx2 producing Shiga-like toxin (STEC) was detected in faeces. The patient has no other underlying medical conditions and is not taking any medications.</topic><topic number="33">A 42-year-old, healthy woman came to the clinic for a flu shot in early October. She works at a rehab facility and has no co-morbidities. It's her first vaccination this year. She's been married for five years and uses a mechanical contraceptive. She has irregular periods. He doesn't smoke. He's not taking any medication. He exercises regularly for 30 minutes a day, at least 5 days a week. No food or drug allergies on his record. She had tonsillectomy and is otherwise healthy.</topic><topic number="34">A 47-year-old Asian woman complains of persistent feelings of sadness. She has lost interest in activities that once gave her pleasure. She claims that for the past three weeks, her mood has been mostly depressed. She also lost her appetite, which led to a weight loss of about 10 pounds. He complains of loss of energy and feelings of worthlessness almost every day. He doesn't use any drugs and he doesn't smoke. He doesn't drink. Before that, she practiced every day for at least 30 minutes. But there hasn't been enough power for three weeks. He's also been having digestive problems lately. She's married and has four children. She's in the menopause. Her husband has recently been diagnosed with colon cancer and is undergoing chemotherapy. The patient's medical examination is uncomplicated, and she is only taking vitamin D3 at a dose of 1,000 units a day. There's no psychological problems in the family history. Her score on the Hamilton Depression Scale HAM-D is 20.</topic><topic number="35">Patient is a 15-year-old girl with a history of recurrent bilateral headaches. The attacks occur 2 or more times a week, and each episode lasts about a day and a half. The pain is throbbing and intense, making it difficult for her to perform her daily physical activities. The seizures are accompanied by nausea and photophobia. She recently noticed that the attacks are more frequent during menstruation. She's been diagnosed with a migraine and is undergoing treatment. She's a high school student and lives with both her parents. He's a bookworm and spends his free time at the public library near his home. She is also interested in writing short stories and has several short stories in English. He rarely exercises. Her BMI is 21 and her blood pressure is 100/60. Her physical examination showed no sign of any distress.</topic><topic number="36">The patient is a 32-year-old obese woman who came to the clinic with weight problems. He is 5'10" tall and weighs 113 pounds. She's complaining of sleep apnea, PCO, and body dysmorphia. She's a high school teacher, married for five years. She hasn't used any contraception in 4 months and she hasn't been pregnant before. He doesn't smoke or do drugs. She likes to try diets and exercise to lose weight. She completed the four-step quad test in 14 seconds. Her blood pressure is 130 over 80, her heart rate is 195 over the minute, and her BMI is 41.54. The following are the results of the laboratory tests: Glucose: 98 mg/dl TG: 150 mg/dl Cholesterol: 180 mg/dl LDL: 90 mg/dl HDL: 35 mg/dl Heart rate is normal. Her joints and range of motion are normal.</topic><topic number="37">A 20-year-old white female came into the clinic with one-sided vision loss and facial weakness, dysarthria and numbness lasting one day. She went to her family doctor and had an MRI scan of her brain, which revealed a single glow in her brain stem. After a few months, she began to experience weakness in her lower extremities, which led to problems with her balance. The second MRI revealed another change in the left hemisphere of the brain. The second MRI was followed by a diagnosis of relapsing-remitting multiple sclerosis (RRMS). In the C-section report from two years ago, the patient has one child. She's divorced and currently sexually inactive. He smokes 10 cigarettes a day and drinks occasionally. She works as an editor at a publishing house and is happy to be able to work from home most of the time. She's been on RRMS for seven months.</topic><topic number="38">Patient is a 35-year-old female with grade IIa gravis myasthenia. She complains of double vision and fatigue and weakness, which affects mainly the upper extremities. She tested positive for anti-AChR antibodies and also tested positive for single muscle fiber electromyography (SFEMG). He takes 60 mg of pyridostigmine three times a day. But she still has some symptoms that make it difficult for her to work. He's a research coordinator and has three kids. Her 70-year-old father has high blood pressure. He doesn't smoke or do drugs. He occasionally drinks alcohol at social events. Her physical and laboratory examinations have revealed no other abnormalities. Blood pressure: 110/75 Hgb: 11 g/dl WBC: 8000/mm3 Plt: 300000/ml Creatinine: 0.5 mg/dl BUN: 10 mg/dl BhCG: negative result of the pregnancy test</topic><topic number="39">A 3-day-old Asian girl had jaundice that started the day before. She was born at 38+3 weeks of uncomplicated pregnancy. Family interview is easy. The baby is breastfed. Vital signs: core temperature of 36.3&#176;C, heart rate of 154 beats/min, respiratory rate of 37 breaths/min and blood pressure of 65/33 mm Hg. The baby weighs 3.2 kg, body length: 53 cm, head circumference: 36 cm. Yellow solids, yellowish coating. Hearing heart and lungs without deviation. Liver and spleen on palpation without deviation. The results of the laboratory tests are as follows: serum total bilirubin concentration: 21.02 mg/dl direct bilirubin concentration: 2.04 mg/dl AST: 37 U/l ALT: 20 U/l GGT: 745 U/l alkaline phosphatase: 531 U/l creatinine: 0.3 mg/dl urine: 29 mg/dl Na: 147 mEq/l K: 4.5 mEq/l CRP: 3 mg/l Blood morphology is within the normal range. The patient was diagnosed with uncomplicated neonatal jaundice which may require phototherapy.]</topic><topic number="40">A 60-year-old male complains of frequent headaches, generalized bone pain and difficulty chewing that began six years ago and are getting worse. The examination revealed bilateral swelling around the molars. The swelling's gotten worse since the last exam. There were some changes to the head and face. The swelling is painless and adheres to the bone underneath. Further studies showed increased uptake of the radioactive substance, as well as increased urinary concentrations of pyridinoline. The serum alkaline phosphatase activity is 300 IU/ l (norm is 44147 IU/ l). In the family history, only the mother's hypertension and the father's type 2 diabetes are relevant. The diagnosis of Paget' s disease of the bone was confirmed and treatment with bisphosphonates was initiated as first-line treatment.</topic><topic number="41">A 57-year-old farmer was diagnosed with Parkinson's disease a year ago. He's experiencing deceleration and tremor. In the report, hypertension and high cholesterol. He lives with his wife. They have three kids. Before his diagnosis, he was actively farming and raising livestock. Patient complains of tremors and slow movement. He had trouble getting through the door, like he was "frozen" and needed help getting in. His handwriting is getting smaller and smaller. He's taking levodopa and trihexyphenidyl. He's not going to be able to get it. From the patient's account, the medication helps with the tremors and the movement delays. However, he still has difficulty initiating movements, stiffness and general deceleration. He's a conscious, cooperative man who shows no signs of dementia. He doesn't smoke or use drugs.</topic><topic number="42">A 19-year-old Latina woman, Pregnant1Livod1, 32+6 weeks pregnant, reported to the maternity clinic for a routine check-up, complaining of mild headache and leg swelling. Preliminary blood pressure was 146/99 and urine protein was 3+ in the strip test. Her blood pressure and urine tests were normal at the last visit. The blood pressure returned to 150/100 mmHg a few hours later. Lab tests showed normal hematocrit, platelet count and liver transaminase levels. Patient complains of fatigue, but no fever or chills. He also suffers from headaches without visual impairment. No signs of shortness of breath, cough, chest pain, orthopnea, palpitations or skin rash were observed. The physical examination did not reveal abdominal pain, abnormal bowel movements, nausea, vomiting, dysuria, frequent urination, haemorrhage or foamy urine. The swelling of the lower extremities was not accompanied by joint pain or back pain. The patient has no history of any particular health problems and is taking prenatal vitamins only. In the family history, type 2 diabetes and high blood pressure. He drinks alcohol at social gatherings, doesn't smoke, and doesn't do drugs. She's had one partner for two years and no contraception for two years. Her BMI was 24 at her first visit when she was six weeks pregnant. During pregnancy, the weight gain is normal</topic><topic number="43">A 60-year-old woman was admitted to the stroke ward with a history of recent second-cycle intravenous antibiotics for inflammatory pneumonia. Patient has fever and complains of abdominal pain and diarrhoea (ejaculation eight times in 3 hours, each time with large volumes of greenish, liquid stool). The patient's abdomen is generally flaccid and bloated, with increased intestinal peristalsis. He has a fever of 38.4 degrees, a tachycardia of 113/minute, and hypotension of 80/40 mmHg. Faecal samples were positive for Clostridium difficile toxin</topic><topic number="44">A 14-year-old boy complains of scoliosis and back pain. No other medical conditions. He used to be able to do routine activities like basketball and football, but recently he has been having difficulty doing them. The pain that he feels in his lower extremity and back is aggravated by physical activity. He prefers to lie down most of the time. He is not satisfied with his gestures and complains of shoulder imbalance and head tilting to the right. The patient is a well-dressed and well-fed teenager who is alert and cooperative. Left shoulder's a little higher than right. The curve of scoliosis is 45 degrees. The patient is eligible for scoliosis surgery according to the perioperative monitoring of the MEP.</topic><topic number="45">34-year-old African-American male with diagnosed sickle cell anemia, reports to the clinic with severe bone pain. Patient had severe lower back pain radiating to both thighs, rated 9 out of 10. The patient has had episodes of sickle cell anemia since childhood. He's had the same symptoms for the last two weeks, and he's been on oxycodone, which hasn't helped his pain. The emergency room doctor referred him to the emergency room for intravenous pain medication. Patient has no fever and normal blood pressure. The physical examination showed no evidence of splenomegaly. No allergies in the record. He doesn't smoke or use drugs. The following are the results of the laboratory tests: Hb: 8 g/dl WBC: 10000/mm3 Plt: 300000/ml MCV: 106 fL Haemoglobin electrophoresis: 91% HbS 6% HbF 3% HbA2 AST: 22 U/l ALT: 43 U/l AlP: 53 U/l Ferritin: 1200 ng/ml</topic><topic number="46">Patient A is a 30-year-old male who was admitted to the hospital after 10 days of coughing, heavy night sweats and loss of appetite. He traveled to India a month ago. No vaccinations against tuberculosis in his medical history. Before that, he was a healthy man working as an engineer for a high-tech company. He doesn't smoke or use drugs. He had a fever of 38 degrees, a heart rate of 115 beats per minute, a respiratory rate of 22, a blood pressure of 125/75 mmHg, and an oxygen saturation of 97%. Chest X-ray showed a hole in the middle of the left lung, 1.8 cm in diameter, with features of a cavity in the lungs. A sputum smear was positive for Mycobacterium tuberculosis, which is sensitive to first-line anti-tuberculosis drugs (isoniazid, streptomycin, rifampicin and etambutol). The following are the results of the laboratory tests: Hgb: 13 g/dl WBC: 14000/mm3 Plt: 300000/ml AST: 13 U/l ALT: 15 U/l ALP: 53 U/l Total bilirubin: 0.6 mg/dl Na: 137 mEq/l K: 4 mEq/l Creatinine: 0.5 mg/dl BUN: 10 mg/dl OB: 120 mm/h The following are the results of the laboratory tests:</topic><topic number="47">A 62-year-old African-American male reported weakness in his left upper and lower extremities, accompanied by a dark spot in his right eye, numbness in his right face, drooping face, and slurred speech. He denied shortness of breath, headache, palpitations, chest pain, fever, dizziness, failure to urinate or defecate, loss of consciousness. In the report, hypertension, hyperlipidemia and hypothyroidism. He's smoked a pack a day for 40 years and has five to six beers a week. He doesn't know his family's medical history. He's on the left side of the thyroid, the right side of atorvastatin, the right side of hydrochlorothiazide. His vitals were stable in the preliminary examination. The study found left-sided facial droop, dysarthria and left-sided semi-paralysis. His score on the NIHSS was 7. Preliminary angiography of the head and neck CT showed no acute intracranial lesions. The patient was given intravenous recombinant tissue plasminogen activator (t-PA) and a high dose of statin. The patient was admitted to the intensive care unit for 24 hours of follow-up. MRI of the head revealed acute anaemia, 1.7 cm in diameter, pericomporously, of the white matter on the right side and the posterior part of the basal nucleus on the right side.</topic><topic number="48">Fernandez is a 41-year-old man who is a professional soccer player. He went to the clinic because of an itchy foot. The subject examination revealed localized exfoliation and maceration between the third and fourth toes of the right foot. The area occupied was painful, inflamed with mild cracks. The back and the sole of the foot remain intact. There's no oil or cracks in the altered area. The patient was not on topical ointment, and there was no history of co-morbidities, such as diabetes. He smokes 15 cigarettes a day and drinks beer a day. Family history shows the mother has hyperlipidemia and the father has a myocardial infarction. He's involved with multiple partners and uses a condom during sex. Besides, the physical and the lab tests were all normal. Foot-fungal infection was confirmed by microscopic examination of a fungal-clove preparation with potassium hydroxide KOH.</topic><topic number="49">A 12-year-old girl came to the clinic with her mother, complaining of short stature, delayed puberty, and stunted growth. The 45X karyotype test confirmed the diagnosis of Turner syndrome. For 6 months, the girl has been on growth hormone (GH) therapy without estrogen therapy to avoid menarche while achieving her targeted growth. The study identified obesity and mental retardation. The study found no pubic and pubic hair, and her breasts were stage 1. Her last lab test showed her TSH was 3 and her glucose was 75.</topic><topic number="50">A five-month-old boy was admitted to the pediatric surgery clinic because of a hollow on his right side. The boy is the first child of a healthy mother born by natural forces at 38 weeks. The mother's pregnancy was normal, no complications. The boy weighed 3,200 grams and was 50 centimeters tall. The boy is breastfed, currently weighs 6.5 kg and is 62 cm tall. No developmental delay was observed in this study. The nucleus was only detectable on the left side of the scrotum, while the right side of the nucleus was imperceptible. The penis was the right size and shape. The boy was not circumcised. Diagnostic laparoscopy revealed an intact nucleus located in the abdominal cavity.</topic><topic number="51">In a 25-year-old female patient, fever, chills, nausea and vomiting suddenly occurred at 24+3 weeks of first pregnancy (C1P1). In addition, the patient has complained of painful urination, urethral stricture and frequent urination. He also reports severe pain in his side. Her vital signs are T = 39.7oC, heart rate = 117, R = 20 , blood pressure = 113/74 mm Hg. In this study, bilateral palpable tenderness is present in the vertebral-rib area. The patient is in denial of recurrent urinary tract infections before pregnancy and co-morbidities. The urine sample showed Gram-negative bacterial rods, leukocytes and leukocyte spindles. The blood work was negative. The following data are available for the evaluation of the efficacy of the product:</topic><topic number="52">A 34-year-old man has reported to the clinic with dizziness and severe diarrhea, which has been ongoing since yesterday. He just returned from a month-long trip abroad to Sudan. He developed a stomach ache, followed by bloating, nausea, and loose stools. Soon he developed a profuse, watery, odorless diarrhea. The stool is watery and white, but the patient doesn't have a fever. Blood pressure: 95/62 when lying down, drops to 75/40 when standing. Skin tension is down. Pulse rate is 110 beats per minute. The patient seems sick. The napkins are dry. Microscopic examination of a fresh faecal sample in the dark field of vision detected the presence of V. cholerae. The results of the laboratory tests are as follows: Sodium 137 mg/l Potassium 2 mg/l Chlorine 94 mg/l CO2 15 mg/l Leukocytes in the faeces: no Blood dissolved in the faeces: negative</topic><topic number="53">A 34-year-old patient from Jordan came to the clinic with general and non-specific bone and joint pain. She's married with three kids. No significant co-morbidities or medications in the report. BMI is 23, blood pressure is 120/75, heart rate is 75/min. In laboratory studies, the vitamin D level is 14 ng/ml, and is also stable. The test chemical is a substance which is used in the manufacture of a substance.</topic><topic number="54">A 57-year-old male was admitted to the clinic four months ago with weight loss and a persistent dry cough. CT scan of the chest showed bilateral, multiple perforations in the upper lungs and thickening of the bronchial wall. The MPO-ANCA antibody test was positive in the serum. A transglandular biopsy revealed dead granules with giant multi-nucleated cells, and the patient was diagnosed with granulomatosis with vasculitis. He's been on corticosteroids and cyclophosphamide for four months. Since the beginning of the disease, the Birmingham Value Assessment Scale (BVAS) has been above 4. The final physical and laboratory tests were performed yesterday, and the results are as follows: A man in good general condition, well-nourished, free of jaundice, cooperative and conscious. The following table shows the number of patients with a known infection with the virus:</topic><topic number="55">22-year-old Caucasian male reported to the clinic with a concussion for a year. Initially, the tremor was in his right hand when he held an object. Later, the tremors became continuous and affected both arms and lower extremities, even when resting. The eye exam identified the Kayser-Fleischer ring. The study identified: jaundice, hepatosplenomegaly and decreased muscle tension in the upper extremities. The boy was smiling all the time, but according to his parents, he was acting aggressively. Laboratory studies have shown low serum ceruloplasmin concentration (0.05 g/ l) and increased daily copper excretion in the urine (120 &#956;g/24 h). The high copper concentration in the liver confirmed Wilson's disease (305 &#956;g/g of dry liver mass).</topic><topic number="56">A 41-year-old male with diagnosed acromegaly had surgery for a herniated disc four months ago. He checked himself into the clinic for a follow-up lab after the original resection. His lab results show IGF-1 levels of 4.5 in the upper limit of normal, corrected for gender and age. His growth hormone level is 4 ppm. A recent MRI of his brain confirmed the presence of a residual pituitary tumor. The relevant information in his medical history is acromegaly caused by pituitary adenoma and recent surgery. After the surgery, she's on vitamin D and multivitamins.</topic><topic number="57">41-year-old obese woman reported to the emergency room with abdominal pain and vomiting. The pain, which started gradually yesterday, is localized to the abdominal area and the navel area, radiating to the back. He drinks alcohol frequently and doesn't smoke. No allergies in her history, and she only uses multivitamins every day. Family history shows hypertension (from mother). She lives with her husband and has three children. The belly is sticky and soft. Bowel peristalsis is normal. Pulse rate is 115 over the minute, blood pressure is 110 over 75 mmHg. In laboratory tests: leukocytosis (19.5), urea 8.5, high CRP (145), high amylase (1200) and glucose level 15. Abdominal CT showed acute edema of the interstitial pancreatitis with dilated common bile duct and intrahepatic duct, confirming pancreatitis on the gallstone. The pregnancy test came back negative, and the patient is not breastfeeding.</topic><topic number="58">A 17-year-old boy is complaining of severe, wandering pain in the right lower quadrant of his abdomen that began four days ago. The pain is accompanied by nausea and vomiting. Patient has fever, tenderness, positive Blumberg's and increased muscle defenses during palpation. His white blood cells were elevated, with neutrophils. CT scan showed signs of acute appendicitis complicated by perforation, with free fluid in the pelvis. Diagnostic laparoscopy revealed a ropowica without any other abdominal abnormalities. The patient was scheduled for an emergency laparoscopic appendectomy under general anesthesia.</topic><topic number="59">A 15-year-old boy, diagnosed with asthma a year ago, came in with: shortness of breath, chest tightness, and coughing. According to the mother, there was no reaction to the standard corticosteroid inhaler. He was admitted to the emergency room with a severe asthma attack. He's been cleared for general corticosteroid therapy. Spirometry showed a first second exhaled volume (FEV1) of 60% of the normal value. No relevant information in his medical history. With a relevant piece of information in the family history: asthma in the mother and uncle. Patient was previously treated with a combination of inhaled corticosteroids and Zafirlukast</topic><topic number="60">63-year-old male reported SOR due to acute urinary retention in the last 2 days. CT scans of the abdominal cavity and pelvis showed an enlarged prostate and a bladder filled with urine. The patient was qualified for a catheter for bladder and transurethral resection of the prostate (TURP). The following was the result of further analysis: Urine volume after urination: 71 ml Prostate volume (TRUS): 63 ml Concentration of faecal specific antigen (PSA): 3.5 ng/ml The most recent biochemical blood test (three days ago) was normal: Hgb: 13.6 g/dl WBC: 133000/mm3 Plt: 370000/ml PT: 12 seconds PTT: 34 seconds INR: 0.9 Creatinine: 0.5 mg/dl BUN: 10 mg/dl BOM: Colour: yellow Appearance: hazy PH: 5.3 Specific density: 1.010 Glucose: 100 Nitrate: negative: Ketones are absent Leukocyte ester: RBC: WBC: 2 WBC/hp Bacterial: negative</topic><topic number="61">In a 45-year-old postmenopausal patient with breast cancer confirmed by cytology, a colonoscopy revealed a 3-centimeter invasive ductal cancer of the breast in the left upper outer quadrant. The tumour is HER2-positive and ER/PR-negative. The swab from the temporal lobe showed five positive lymph nodes. The chest X-ray showed the presence of metastatic lesions. The patient is taking a multivitamin and iron supplements. He doesn't smoke or drink. She's sexually inactive and has no children. She's qualified to resect the tumor and she's willing to do it before chemotherapy.</topic><topic number="62">46-year-old male reports dizziness and frequent headaches. Family history of coronary artery disease (CAD) but no other cardiovascular risk factors such as nicotine addiction, high blood pressure or diabetes, and is physically active. The patient' s LDL-C and HDL-C levels were 545 and 53 mg/ dl, respectively. His fasting glucose and triglyceride levels (85 and 158 mg/dl, respectively) were within the normal range. The patient did not report the use of lipid-lowering medications. Neck scan revealed a 3+/6+ contractional bruise in the neck radiating to the skull. Ultrasound of the cervical arteries revealed severe left internal carotid artery narrowing (LICA) as well as moderate right internal carotid artery narrowing (RICA) estimated at 40 to 50%. The maximum contraction velocity (PSV) and end-of-year contraction velocity (EDV) limits for LICA were 208,5 cm/ s and 54,5 cm/ s respectively; the RICA PSV was 91,72 cm/ s and the RICA EDV was 37,37 cm/ s. Atrial plaque was observed in the anterior and posterior walls of the internal carotid artery and common carotid artery, characterised by massive plaques extending to the middle third of the internal coronary arteries (ICA) and predominantly echogenic and hyperechogenic, with less than 50% of the area of the echo-transparent surface being irregular.</topic><topic number="63">A 54-year-old obese woman was admitted to the emergency room with abdominal pain that started four days ago and was accompanied by nausea and vomiting. The pain in the abdomen radiates to the right upper quadrant, intensifying after the consumption of fatty foods. Patient's had similar pain twice in the last year. In the report: hypercholesterolemia and the condition after two births by force of nature. She has two children and is in menopause. He doesn't smoke, drink or take drugs. She has a slight fever. Her blood pressure is 150/85, HR 115, RR 15, T 38.2, and her O2 is 98%. She's a fat woman with no acute medical conditions. On palpation, she's experiencing tenderness in the abdomen and tenderness in the right upper quadrant without Blumberg's. Bowel peristalsis is normal. Laboratory studies have shown elevated OB and leukocytosis with left shift. Ultrasound showed several gallstones, gallbladder deposits and gallstones in the common bile duct. The smallest stone is 14mm.</topic><topic number="64">A 55-year-old male who was diagnosed with HCV 2 years ago was recently diagnosed with HBV co-infection. His medical history is irrelevant. She's been on interferon IFN, ribavirin RBV and direct antiviral drugs for six months. The patient is not taking any other medication. His medical records show a previous positive HCV RNA test and a positive HCV antibody immuno-enzymatic test. The last biopsy showed no hepatocellular carcinoma, only a chronic inflammatory condition consistent with chronic viral hepatitis. No signs or symptoms suggestive of alcoholic liver disease, bleeding from esophageal veins, haemochromatosis, autoimmune hepatitis, or metabolic liver disease. He's a conscious male with no acute medical conditions. His blood pressure is 130 over 75. His heart rate is 90 over the minute. His BMI is 27. The abdomen is soft, without the abs and tenderness. The lower extremities are normal, no swelling.</topic><topic number="65">A 25-year-old male with type 1 diabetes, confirmed by molecular testing seven years ago, came to the clinic with shortness of breath and fatigue during physical activity. He reports mild shortness of breath after entering the third floor, no resting shortness of breath, and no painful shortness of breath (class 2 according to the New York Heart Association). He's been diagnosed with cardiomyopathy, and he's being treated with ACE inhibitors and beta-blockers. She's on a 70/30 insulin and vitamin D supplements. His medical history is irrelevant to any other medical problems. My uncle and grandfather both had type 1 diabetes in their family history. The results of his laboratory tests are as follows: Fasting glucose: 100 mg/dl HbA1c: 6.5% Cholesterol: 190 mg/dl TG: 140 mg/dl LDL: 125 mg/dl HDL: 40 mg/dl</topic><topic number="66">A 16-year-old girl came to the clinic complaining of weight gain and menstrual irregularities. Her BMI was 24, but in the last few weeks, she gained five pounds. Patient's more likely to be tired and not have the energy to go out dancing with friends. In laboratory studies, TSH levels were surprisingly high (15 mU/l) and free thyroxine levels were low (0.18 ng/dl). The anti-TPO antibody level was extremely high (136 IU/ ml). She was diagnosed with Hashimoto's disease. She doesn't smoke and she's not sexually active.</topic><topic number="67">A cytological examination in a 54-year-old woman showed abnormal placenta/ cervical mucus. The HPV 16 test was positive. She's sexually active with her husband and has four children. She's in menopause and not using birth control. He smokes cigarettes and drinks alcohol frequently. Besides, she's healthy. She was offered a conization.</topic><topic number="68">A 23-year-old man came to the hospital with high blood pressure (175/95 mmHg) and symptoms of post-concussion syndrome. The patient developed respiratory failure requiring mechanical ventilation and renal failure requiring haemodialysis. The blood smear showed microangiopathic haemolytic anemia and thrombocytopenia. Blood tests showed increased lactate dehydrogenase activity and decreased C3 supplement concentration with a normal clotting profile. He was diagnosed with atypical hemolytic-uremic syndrome. The patient was treated with plasmapheresis and corticosteroids. He has previously been vaccinated with the conjugated vaccine against ACS and with the vaccine against B. The genetic test showed ADAMTS13 &gt; 10%.</topic><topic number="69">A 67-year-old healthy woman came to the clinic for a flu shot in early October. She works at a rehab facility, no co-morbidities. It's her first vaccination this year. She's in menopause and has four kids. There are none. She takes a daily multivitamin and antihypertensive. He exercises regularly for 30 minutes a day, at least 5 days a week. No food allergies or drug sensitivities.</topic><topic number="70">A 46-year-old Asian woman with major depressive disorder (MDD) complains of persistent feelings of sadness and loss of interest in daily activities. She claims her mood is still depressed most days. He complains of loss of energy and feelings of worthlessness almost every day. She's been on antidepressants for six months, but her symptoms are still there. He doesn't drink or smoke. She used to exercise every day for at least 30 minutes, but for the last three weeks, she hasn't had enough energy to do it. He's also been having digestive problems lately. She's married and has four children. She's in the menopause. Her husband was diagnosed with colon cancer a year ago, and he's undergoing chemotherapy. No relevant information in her medical history. Family records show no signs of any psychological problems. Her score on the Hamilton Depression Rating Scale HAM-D is 20.</topic><topic number="71">A 34-year-old obese woman came to the clinic with a weight problem. She is 5'4" tall and weighs 113 pounds. In the past, she's tried anti-obesity and appetite suppressants without success. She's complaining of sleep apnea, PCO, and body dysmorphia. She's a high school teacher. She's been married for five years. She hasn't used any contraception for four months and has never been pregnant. She rarely exercises, and movement makes it difficult. He can't do the four-step quad test in less than 15 seconds. He doesn't smoke or do drugs. Her blood pressure is 130 over 80, her heart rate is 195 over the minute, and her BMI is 41.54. The following laboratory test results were obtained: Fasting glucose: 98 mg/dl TG: 150 mg/dl Cholesterol: 180 mg/dl LDL: 90 mg/dl HDL: 35 mg/dl Laparoscopic gastric bypass surgery is being considered.</topic><topic number="72">A 16-year-old female patient was recently diagnosed with myasthenia gravis, class IIa. Patient complains of double vision and weakness in the upper extremities. The anti-AChR antibodies were positive and the single muscle fiber electromyography (SFEMG) was positive. She's on acetylcholinesterase inhibitors in combination with immunosuppressive drugs, but she's still having symptoms. He doesn't smoke or do drugs. She's sexually inactive, menstruating regularly. No other abnormalities were found in the field and laboratory studies. Blood pressure is 110/75 Hgb, 11 g/dl, CBC is 8000/mm3, Plt is 300000/ml, Creatinine is 0.5 mg/dl, Urinary Nitrogen is 10 mg/dl, and BUN is 10 mg/dl.</topic><topic number="73">Patient is a 3-day-old girl with jaundice that started the day before. She was born at 34 weeks, and because of her gestational age, she was in an incubator. Vital signs: core temperature of 36.3&#176;C, heart rate of 154 beats/min, respiratory rate of 37 breaths/min and blood pressure of 65/33 mm Hg. Weight: 2.1 kg, body length: 45 cm, head circumference: 32 cm. It has yellowish hardness and yellowing of the skin. Liver and spleen are normal on the palpation. The results of the laboratory tests are as follows: serum total bilirubin concentration: 21.02 mg/dl direct bilirubin concentration: 2.04 mg/dl AST: 37 U/l ALT: 20 U/l GGTP: 745 U/l alkaline phosphatase: 531 U/l creatinine: 0.3 mg/dl urea: 29 mg/dl Na: 147 mEq/l K: 4.5 mEq/l CRP: 3 mg/l complete blood count is within the normal range. She was diagnosed with neonatal jaundice, which may require phototherapy.</topic><topic number="74">53-year-old patient complains of: frequent headaches, generalized bone pain and difficulty chewing, which started 6 years ago and is getting worse. The examination revealed bilateral swelling around the molars. The swelling's gotten worse since the last exam. Several lesions were found outside the oral cavity, located in the head and face. The swelling is painless and adheres to the bone underneath. Further evaluation revealed increased uptake of the radioactive substance, as well as increased urinary pyridinoline concentrations. The serum alkaline phosphatase activity is 300 IU/ l (norm is 44147 IU/ l). The patient's sister had the same issues. At the age of 52, she was diagnosed with Paget's disease of the bone. The diagnosis of Paget' s disease of the bone was confirmed and bisphosphonates were included as first-line treatment.</topic><topic number="75">A 55-year-old patient recently diagnosed with Parkinson's disease complains of slow movement and tremors. His disease is mild, stage I on the Hoehn-Yahra scale. In the report, hypertension and high cholesterol. He lives with his wife. They have three kids. He was active in gardening before his diagnosis. She complains of tremors and slow movement. The patient had difficulty getting through the door, as if he was frozen and needed help getting in. His handwriting is getting smaller and smaller. The patient was offered levodopa and trihexyphenidyl. He's a conscious, cooperative man with no signs of dementia. He doesn't smoke or use drugs.</topic></topics>