<topics task="2021 TREC Clinical Trials"><topic number="1">Patient is a 45-year-old male with a history of anaplastic astrocytoma of the spine complicated by severe lower limb weakness and urinary retention with Foley catheter, high-dose steroids, hypertension and chronic pain. The tumor is located in the T-L column, anaplastic astrocytoma, irresectable after radiation. Complicated by progressive weakness of the lower extremities and urinary retention. The patient initially presented with MID (right lower limb) weakness where his right knee gave way with difficulty walking and numbness of the right anterior thigh. MRI showed a mass in the spinal cord cone that was biopsied and found to be an anaplastic astrocytoma. Therapy included radiotherapy of the t10-l1 field followed by 11 cycles of temozolomide 7 days yes and 7 days no. This was followed by CPT-11 Weekly for 4 weeks with Avastin every two weeks / 2 weeks off and repeating the cycle.</topic><topic number="2">48-year-old male with a history of hypertension, hyperlipidemia, bicuspid aortic valve and smoking (severe), who went to the cardiologist on [**2148-10-1**] with progressive dyspnea and oedema of IH. Transthoracic echocardiography (TET) revealed severe aortic stenosis with worsening of left ventricular (VI) function. The ejection fraction (EF) was 25%. Right ventricular pressure (VD) was 41 and she presented with biauricular dilation. Aortic insufficiency of 2+ with mild mitral insufficiency was observed. He was sent home from the cardiology clinic with furosemide and BB (which he didn't tolerate), continued with worsening dyspnea and edema from EI, and finally came in for evaluation. During this admission, repeated echocardiography confirmed critical aortic stenosis showing left ventricular hypertrophy with cavity dilation and severe global hypocinesia, severe aortic valve stenosis with underlying bicuspid aortic valve, dilated ascending aorta, and mild pulmonary artery systolic hypertension. The patient underwent preoperative valve replacement evaluation with preoperative computed tomography of the chest and carotid ultrasound (which showed moderate heterogeneous plaque with bilateral internal carotid artery stenosis (ICA) of 1-39%). He also had a cardiac catheterization with right cardiac catheterization to assess pulmonary arterial pressures, which angiographically showed no flow-limiting coronary artery disease.</topic><topic number="3">A 32-year-old woman who comes in after a severe "explosive" headache. She and her husband report that yesterday she was in the kitchen, got up and hit her head on the corner of a closet. The next morning he developed a sudden "explosive" headache. He arrived at the hospital where the CT scan of his head showed a significant amount of blood in his right ventricle. Neurosurgery evaluated her for spontaneous intraventricular bleeding with concern for an underlying vascular malformation. A cerebral angiogram was performed which showed abnormal vasculature with a left temporal lobe drainage vein penetrating the deep white matter compatible with MAV. Patient continued to have headaches, but they were getting better with painkillers. The patient refused physical therapy evaluation, but was walking independently without difficulty. She was discharged to her home with her husband on [**2155-12-6**].</topic><topic number="4">This is a 44-year-old female with a prior medical history of PCOS, obesity and hypertension. He presented with symptoms of cholecystitis and was incidentally detected with a large pericardial effusion. Pericardiocentesis was performed and pericardial fluid analysis was compatible with Burkitt's lymphoma. The pericardial fluid contained monotypic CD10 positive kappa-restricted light chain B cells expressing FMC-7, CD19, CD20 and myc rearrangement, consistent with Burkitt's lymphoma. A lumbar puncture and a posterior bone marrow biopsy came back negative for any involvement, which identified it as a primary cardiac lymphoma. A cardiac MRI showed a 3 cm x 1 cm mass in the lateral wall of the right atrium, adjacent to the atrioventricular (AV) junction. Medical history: 1. Uncommon migraines 2. High blood pressure 3. Obesity 4. SOP/ infertility 5. Viral encephalitis/meningitis -&gt; HIC -&gt; seizures/stroke ([**2137**]) = due to severe sinus infusion, which caused minor residual non-focal deficits 6. CSF leakage with meningitis secondary to the placement of a lumbar drainage. The seventh. TVP in the lower right secondary limb to the placement of a VCI 8 filter. Surgery of the knee</topic><topic number="5">74-year-old male with a history of coronary artery disease/ ischaemic heart disease (ICD) with a history of bypass surgery, FE 60% previous stroke (no residual deficits), HTA, DLP, DMII, moderate to severe PAD. He was referred to cardiology for PAD evaluation, and on the exam, the patient presented with carotid blows. After further symptom review, the patient reports + occasional dizziness, no previous syncope, occasional headache. He denies chest pain/dyspnea. No sensory or motor defects. Remember, you could have had a stroke 10-15 years ago with no residual deficit. Before the CABG, I only had diaphoresis. In a further review of the systems, the absence of chest pain, exertion dyspnea, paroxysmal nocturnal dyspnea, orthopnea, palpitations, syncope or presyncope is noted. He had a carotid ultrasound which showed significant bilateral carotid stenosis, I&gt;D. The angiography revealed a stenosis of 80% of the right carotid artery (ACI) and 90% of the left carotid artery (ACI). The brain angiography also revealed a permeable right ACA and ACM, as well as a permeable left ACA and ACM. Medical history: CI, with previous history of coronary artery disease (CABG) at [**2154**] ([**Hospital1 112**]) previous stroke Carotid artery disease bilateral PAD anaemia Hypertension Diabetes complicated with retinopathy and peripheral neuropathy Intervened cataracts. Thyroid nodule Colon polyps with resection Intermittent low back pain Proteinuria History of a right elbow fracture in childhood Arthritis</topic><topic number="6">Patient is a 55-year-old female with end-stage chronic kidney disease in HD and peritoneal dialysis who presented with watery, non-bloody diarrhea and weakness. He has a history of two previous C.I.s. diff., the most recent one just a month ago. Recent use of antibiotics in the last month of previous admission. She was also treated for C. diff. at that time for 14 days with oral vancomycin. Patient initially admitted to ICU and was septic on vasopressors (levophed, noradrenaline) until morning of [**8-26**] with leukocytosis but no fever. The C. diff test. was positive on admission and the patient had C. diff compatible leukocytosis. The patient was initially given oral Vancomycin, Flagyl IV and oral Flagyl, and when the patient improved, she was switched to oral Vancomycin and oral Flagyl on [**8-29**]. The patient was treated with oral vancomycin for 6 weeks due to recurrence of C. diff. She was also encouraged to take probiotics and disinfect her home with bleach when she was discharged.</topic><topic number="7">60 year old male with cirrhosis of the liver due to hepatitis C, esophageal varices grade II, recent admission due to HDA [**2-9**], gastritis due to NSAID. He was referred to the emergency room by the hepatology clinic for de novo slurred speech/dysarthria and tangential thinking. The patient also describes de novo instability that caused him to fall in a way that could have hit his head. According to the last entry from the Hepatology consult, she's been ethanol/alcohol free for a year (corroborated with the patient), urine toxics were negative for alcohol. The CT scan was normal and the neurological evaluation determined that it was not an ischemic heart attack. He was diagnosed with a suspected hepatic encephalopathy and started lactulose treatment. Liver function tests showed a marked increase in total and direct bilirubin since the last visit. Another worrying aspect was the increase in FA. This could indicate a progression of cirrhosis, as interferon failed to respond on two occasions. Ambulatory follow-up will be performed to assess this situation. The following are some of the adverse reactions reported in patients with severe gastrointestinal disorders:</topic><topic number="8">This is a 57-year-old male with CLL and transformation into large cells. Reported illness on [**10/2119**] with elevated white blood cell count and elevated LDH. I had no splenomegaly or cytopenias at the time. He had a bulky lymphadenopathy. Completed four cycles of FCR therapy on [09/2119**]. He had an excellent response to treatment and was monitored treatment-free for approximately two years. In [**7-/2122**], he had an increased white blood cell count, approximately 50% lymphocytes and a slightly elevated LDH. He also had palpable lymphadenopathy with mild worsening. He received four cycles of PCR, but the response was poor, so his treatment regimen was changed to R-CVP, of which he received two cycles. Again, he did not show a significant response, although he maintained excellent functional status, and was eventually switched to Campath therapy. Lymphocytosis resolved and his white blood cell count has dropped considerably, but there wasn't much response in terms of reducing his voluminous lymphadenopathy. She subsequently developed an enlarged left cervical ganglion, which was biopsied and a Richter transformation was detected.</topic><topic number="9">41-year-old male with a history of severe intellectual disability, congestive heart failure (CHF) and epilepsy, in the form of facial spasms on the right side and widespread tremors at his nursing home, requiring 20 mg of Valium to stop the seizures. According to an external medical report, the patient was considered to have focal epilepsy with secondary generalization, probably due to anoxic brain injury at birth and possibly related to atrophic changes observed on MRI, particularly in the left temporal lobe. The patient developed his first seizures at age 13, and his family detected a generalized seizure. He had a second seizure two years after the first episode. He was given Dilantin (phenytoin) and phenobarbital. The patient went 20 years without another seizure. Recently his Dilantin dose was gradually reduced, and it was considered that perhaps this medication was necessary to keep him seizure-free. The patient had no further events during his hospital stay and was in baseline condition at discharge. The full EEG reports are pending at the time of the ruling. Medical history: Epilepsy as mentioned above, congestive heart failure, depression.</topic><topic number="10">The patient is a 22-year-old female, otherwise healthy, with a history of systemic mastocytosis of 5 years of evolution, with outbreaks that usually occur 3 times a year. He's showing hot flashes and tachycardia, which suggests a new outbreak. This is the patient's third outbreak in two months, as she continues to taper off steroids, which is new to her. He responded well to 125 mg of intravenous steroids every 8 hours and intravenous diphenhydramine, in addition to his home regimen. The complete blood count was at baseline, with a normal differential. Serum tryptase revealed a high value of 84. Patient failed the aspirin challenge test due to an adverse reaction. She stabilized on IV steroids and IV Benadryl and was moved back to the medicine plant. The patient continued on her home histamine receptor blockers and switched from intravenous to oral steroids and Benadryl and remained on overnight observation and was discharged on her home medications, tapering of prednisone, gastrointestinal prophylaxis with PPIs, calcium and vitamin D, and bactrim ((cotrimoxazole)) at standard doses for PCP.</topic><topic number="11">75-year-old male with metastatic papillary thyroid cancer, after 19 sessions of radiotherapy X-ray, which presented two days of worsening of dysphagia for solids, poor oral intake, weight loss of 9 kg in recent weeks and some lethargy. Dx papillary thyroid cancer with right cervical mass --after resection of cervical mass; inability to perform thyroidectomy --high risk of bleeding, proximity to trachea and recurrent laryngeal nerve, and large tumor --after radiotherapy of the neck --after ablation with radioactive iodine --Metastatic in lymph nodes and adrenal glands *after hernia repair *after amygdalectomy</topic><topic number="12">34-year-old female with Marfan syndrome and severe mitral valve prolapse with regurgitation, who was scheduled for mitral valve repair, but missed follow-up. She remains symptomatic and is ready to undergo mitral valve repair/replacement surgery. The mean FE of 65% in transthoracic echocardiography (TET) was not observed. Medical history: Marfan syndrome Severe mitral valve prolapse with severe mitral regurgitation Gastric reflux disease History of gestational diabetes mellitus Gestational hypertension Obesity Caesarean section x 2 Laser eye surgery Cataract surgery Foot surgery (reduction of bone length) The following are some of the side effects of the drug:</topic><topic number="13">62-year-old male with a history of stroke, neurogenic bladder with permanent suprapubic probe, multiple prior admissions for urinary tract infections, altered mental status and urologic sepsis. You come to the hospital with urological sepsis resolved after treatment with vancomycin/meropenem. CT shows a nonobstructive stone in the left ureter, no evidence of urethral stricture. There are significant leaks around the suprapubic catheter. Treatment was started with Ditropan and changed to Detrol (tolterodine). The urologist isn't worried about leaks and will be seeing the patient next week. History of: Cerebral vascular disorder (CVD) Neurogenic bladder with suprapubic probe Recurrent urinary tract infections with Klebsiella/ Pseudomonas Non-Hodgkin lymphoma of the left marginal area of the orbit, diagnosed at 03 (after R-CHOP x 6 cycles) Bell's palsy HPB Arterial hypertension Partial intestinal obstruction with colostomy Hepatitis C Cryoglobulinemia LES with transverse myelitis, anti-ADN-positive antibodies Diabetic insulin-dependent Is this stage IV fungal esophagitis? Urinary tract infections: Pseudomonas and enterococci</topic><topic number="14">70 year old patient with COPD with 2.5-3.5 L O2 basal, OSAS and hypoventilation syndrome-obesity, decompensated CCI, discharged [**2132-8-24**] now presents agitation and altered mental state with hypoxia and 70 s O2 saturation with BipAp at 5 L. Patient agitated and then somnolent in initial presentation. Your daughter reported increased agitation and altered mental status x 2-3 days with O2 saturation of 60-70s at home. Her daughter has also noticed an increase in IBD oedema and weight gain, prompting a phone call to her GP and an increase in the dose of FUROSEMIDA from 80 to 100 mg daily with a slight improvement in the oedema. She's had decreased appetite, oral intake, energy level at home with difficulty for the AVD. No recent history of fever, cough, chills, sputum production, chest pain, abdominal pain or other discomfort other than chronic pain in the right thigh in the last 1-2 months. Daughter also reports compliance with medication and BiPap at night. - coronary heart disease; treated with coronary bypass of 4 vessels at [**2119**] - CHF; FE 55%, mild EA - obesity hypoventilation syndrome - obstructive sleep apnea - T2DM - ventricular tachycardia, with AID provided at [**2127**]</topic><topic number="15">7Female aged 70 years with a history of coronary heart disease who recently experienced an abdominal mass and presented with fever, thyrotonia and increased peripheral blood pressure. During the last weeks before admission, she developed a medium abdominal pain that radiated to the left flank. It persisted throughout the day and did not increase with food, although it was associated with vomiting and worsened with coughing. A CT scan of the abdomen without contrast was performed at [**4-20**], which showed a large heterogeneous mass in the left upper abdomen of 9,5 x 7,5 x 6,0 cm. Echo-endoscopy with biopsy was performed. The biopsy results were consistent with pancreatic adenocarcinoma in the head of the pancreas. A mass was also observed in the splenic flexure/pancreatic collar on CT, likely a diverticular abscess given the patient's recent history of diverticulitis; thought to be an infected fluid accumulation or abscess. She received treatment with intravenous antibiotics (Zosyn (piperacillin tazobactam), then ceftriaxone and Flagyl) and will continue with them until the infectious disease specialist sees her as an outpatient. Medical history: 1. Coronary heart disease with history of angioplasty in [**State 108**] one year ago 2. Prolapse of the mitral valve 3. Atrial fibrillation 4. Hyperlipidemia was 5. Blood pressure 6. The following table summarises the data for the following groups of patients: Is that hypothyroidism? (TSH 10 at [**3-17**]) 8. The Commission has not yet received any comments from the applicant. The following table summarises the data for the following groups of patients:</topic><topic number="16">79-year-old woman with chronic multifactorial hypoxemia and dyspnea, presumably due to diastolic heart failure (DHI), pulmonary hypertension (presumably secondary to chronic AIC) and COPD with 5 litres of home oxygen, admitted for complaints of worsening dyspnea. The cardiology office recommended a right cardiac catheterization to assess the response to sildenafil, but the patient refused. The pulmonary office recommended an empirical and compassionate clinical trial with sildenafil due to severe dysneic symptomatology that impeded ambulatory life, and the patient tolerated the clinical trial without hypotension. The patient should be seen by pulmonology to initiate sildenafil on a chronic and outpatient basis, provided prior authorisation is obtained. - Repair of interatrial communication [**6-17**] complicated with sinus paralysis with placement of a permanent pacemaker). - Pulmonary hypertension (RSVP 75 at [**11-24**]) considered secondary to long-term AIC - COPD with home O2 (5 L per nasal cannula) with basal saturation between 80 and 90% with this therapy. - SAOS, not compatible with CPAP - Mild mitral insufficiency - Microcytic anaemia - Hypothyroidism - Appendicectomy and cholecystectomy - Biliary pancreatitis treated with ERCP and sphincterotomy - Elevated alkaline phosphatase secondary to amiodarone</topic><topic number="17">64 year old woman with multiple myeloma treated with secondary allogeneic transplantation with recurrent disease and systemic amyloidosis (lung, lingual, bladder and heart disease), on haemodialysis for terminal chronic kidney disease, with general malaise, weakness and widespread body pain for two days. She came in last week with hypercalcemia and was treated with pamidronate 30 mg, calcitonin and dialysis. Initially, he received melphalan and prednisone, followed by a VAD regimen (vincristine, adriamycin and dexamethasone) and an autologous stem cell transplant. When myeloma recurred, she was given thalidomide and velcade and thalidomide, which were eventually also discontinued due to worsening edema and renal function.</topic><topic number="18">This is a 78-year-old male with a history of BPH after multiple urological procedures, including suprapubic prostatectomy. He was observed to have low urine output and the bladder ultrasound showed 360 cc residual. The staff found it impossible to pass a Foley probe. Urology was consulted, a flexible cystoscopy was performed in the ICU and a severe 2 cm bulbar urethral stenosis was found. They were able to get a small catheter through and put it in place. The patient had leaks around the catheter, the catheter eventually came out, but continued to have good urine output and post-mixation bladder ultrasounds were performed every 4 hours to ensure that he did not have a high residual volume. Urology suggested that when the patient is stable, he should be taken to the operating room to have the stenosis surgically resolved.</topic><topic number="19">A 65-year-old male with a history of coronary heart disease and previous myocardial infarction, Hodgkin's disease, hypertension, ventricular tachycardia and syncope was admitted earlier today for evaluation of syncope and ventricular arrhythmias. Recently discharged after a negative evaluation for syncope that included implantation of a cardiac monitoring device. He was questioned at another hospital and, according to yesterday's monitor report, readings were: 40 seconds of TV and then bradycardia with a frequency of 39 shortly after corresponding to his symptoms. During the night, the patient entered monomorphic TV in the telemetry. The patient was found to be unresponsive. CPR was started, but it's unclear if the patient had a pulse. Within a minute, the patient was back to a sinus rhythm. The patient reports no symptoms prior to this episode. Currently, the patient is experiencing presyncope and nausea, but denies chest pain. The patient will be transferred to the coronary care unit for catheterization and EFE.</topic><topic number="20">A 35-year-old woman has a history of acne and mild hirsutism. The primary evaluation revealed elevated levels of testosterone. Recently she noticed a gradual enlargement of her hands and feet and recognized that her ring was getting too small for her finger. There's some irregularity in her menstrual cycle, as well as some nipple discharge. He also has a history of snoring and headaches. Physical examination revealed subtle facial features of acromegaly and prognatism. Visual fields are normal by comparison. Hirsutism, thickening of soft tissues and diaphoresis of the hands and feet are observed. Laboratory evaluation in the fasted state reveals IGF-1 of 968 ng/mL and random GH of 19.7 ng/mL. The MRI shows a noninvasive macroadenoma. She's been on stable doses of extended-release octreotide since her diagnosis was confirmed. She's married with two kids. She's using an IUD as a contraceptive.</topic><topic number="21">Patient is a 57-year-old male with abdominal pain and vomiting. The pain started gradually about 20 hours ago in the epigastric and periumbilical regions, radiating to his back. He drinks about 60 units of alcohol a week and smokes 22 cigarettes a day. He's healthy with no history of allergies or medication use. His family history is positive for type 2 diabetes (his father and sister). He lives alone and has no children. The abdomen is painful and soft. His bowel sounds are normal. His heart rate is 115/min and blood pressure is 110/75 mmHg. Laboratory results are notable for leukocytosis (19.5), urea of 8.5, high PCR (145), high amylase (1200) and Glc level of 15. The CT was negative for obstructive pancreatitis.</topic><topic number="22">Patient is a 31-year-old female who complains of abdominal pain. The pain started last night as a diffuse abdominal discomfort. He had a poor appetite and was also unwell. The pain increased in intensity and became more acute in the morning. The pain was localized to the lower right quadrant in the morning. Temperature is within normal limits with normal vital signs. Focal pain and defense were observed during palpation of the right lower quadrant. Palpation of the lower left quadrant causes pain on the right side. His lab tests are highlighting his leukocytosis. The contrasted CT abdomen shows the presence of a distended appendix with thickened appendicular wall without perforation, abscess or gangrene. She's a candidate for laparoscopic appendectomy under general anesthesia.</topic><topic number="23">A 39-year-old man came to the clinic with a cough and difficulty breathing that was not relieved by his inhaler. He's had these symptoms for five days over the last two weeks. He doubled his oral corticosteroids last week. He's a chef with a history of asthma for the past 3 years, who suffers from frequent coughing, wheezing, shortness of breath and chest tightness. Symptoms become more bothersome within 1 to 2 hours after starting work each day and worsen throughout the working week. His symptoms improve after 1 or 2 hours away from the workplace. Spirometry was performed and revealed a forced expiratory volume in the first second (FEV1) of 63% of the predicted. His medical history is significant for seasonal allergic rhinitis in the summer. He doesn't smoke or use illegal drugs. Among his family history are a history of asthma in his father and his sister. He currently uses inhaled corticosteroids (IC) and fluticasone 500 mcg/salmeterol 50 mcg, one inhalation twice a day.</topic><topic number="24">The patient is a 55-year-old male who has been seeing his GP for symptoms of the lower urinary tract, including frequency, urgency, weak flow, incomplete emptying and intermittent flow, for the past 9 months. A subsequent evaluation revealed: IPSS score: 15 Post-microgram residues: 70 ml Prostate volume (transrectal ultrasound): 60 ml Prostate specific antigen (PSA): 3.2 ng/ml Maximum flow: 10 ml/s when urinary volume is 130 ml Otherwise, he is healthy and only takes 1000 units daily of vitamin D. His recent blood biochemistry (3 days ago) was normal: Hb: 13.5 g/dL Leukocytes: 135000 /mm3 Platelets: 350000 /ml TP: 11 seconds TPT: 35 seconds INR: 0.9 Creatinine: 0.5 mg/dL BUN: 10 mg/dL Urianalysis: Yellow Color: Turbid appearance: PH: 5.3 Specific gravity: 1.010 Gluc 100: Nitrogenase negative: Leukocytes: no Leukocytes: negative: Leukocytes: negative: 2 UROC: increased</topic><topic number="25">The patient is a 42-year-old postmenopausal woman who underwent a screening ultrasound that revealed an abnormality in her right breast. She had no palpable masses on the breast exam. A thick needle biopsy was performed which revealed a 1.8 cm infiltrating ductal carcinoma of the breast in the upper left external quadrant. He had a tumorectomy and the surgical margins were clear. The tumor was HER2 positive and estrogen receptor/progesterone receptor negative. The axillary sampling revealed 1 positive lymph node from the 12 sampled. The chest X-ray showed no remarkable findings. She takes multivitamins from "healthy women" daily and doesn't take any other medications. He smokes frequently and drinks alcohol occasionally. She has a single partner and a history of three pregnancies and live births. She breastfed her three children.</topic><topic number="26">A 45-year-old woman was referred to the emergency department with abdominal pain lasting approximately 4 days, accompanied by nausea and 2 episodes of vomiting. The pain is localized to the epigastric region and radiates to the upper right quadrant. The pain gets worse after eating fatty foods. The patient experienced similar pain twice in the last year. In his medical history, he's noted for hypercholesterolemia and two cesarean sections. She has two children and is menopausal. He does not smoke, drink alcohol, or use illegal drugs. She has a slight fever. His blood pressure is 150/85, heart rate 115, respiratory rate 15, T 38.2, SpO2 98% in ambient air. On palpation, he experiences pain on epigastric palpation and in the upper right quadrant without rebound. The bowel sounds are normal. The laboratory analysis is notable for elevated VSG and leukocytosis with left deviation. Ultrasound revealed several gallstones and bile mud. The largest gallstone is 0.7 cm. The surgery consult recommends an elective cholecystectomy.</topic><topic number="27">A 53-year-old male has chronic HCV infection for the past 2 years. His medical history is only significant because of an inguinal hernia surgery at age 20. He's been on combined IFN (100 mg/week) plus RBV (400 mg/day) for the past 9 months. Direct antiviral drugs were added to his treatment 6 months ago. His medical history shows previous positive HCV RNA testing as well as a positive enzyme immunoassay for anti-HCV antibodies. The recent biopsy was negative for hepatocellular carcinoma and was only notable for chronic inflammation consistent with chronic viral hepatitis. There is no evidence of alcoholic liver disease, bleeding from esophageal varices, hemochromatosis, autoimmune hepatitis or metabolic liver disease. He's a man of alertness without acute distress. His blood pressure is 130 over 75, heart rate is 90 over the minute, and his BMI is 27. Her abdomen is soft with no ascites or pain. Lower extremities are normal with no edema.</topic><topic number="28">The patient is a 60-year-old Spanish man who presented with dyspnea approximately one day earlier. The symptoms started acutely and got progressively worse. She's had known COPD for two years. Spirometry revealed a postbronchodilator FEV1/FVC of 60% of the expected values. He smokes 20 cigarettes a day. Among his medical history, he has HBP, for which he uses Flomax (tamsulosin). His family history includes a brother with high blood pressure . Your medication includes Duo-Neb (salbutamol and ipratropio) inhaled every 4 hours as needed, 1000 units of vitamin D3 daily and Flomax for your BPH. He's an obese man, acutely ill, but oriented and aware. The following are the vital signs: PA: 135/80 FR: 25 lpm FC: 75 lpm BMI: 40 Oxygen saturation: 90%</topic><topic number="29">The patient is a 24-year-old man who has had type 1 diabetes for 11 years. You show up in the emergency room with hyperglycaemia and concern for possible diabetic ketoacidosis after not taking your insulin for 3 days. The patient reports that he is currently homeless and has lost his insulin supply, syringes, blood glucose meter and glucose testing supplies. The patient claims that at the time of his initial diagnosis with type 1 diabetes he was hospitalized with a glucose value &gt; 1000 mg/dL. At that time, I had polyuria, polydipsia and polyphagia. You state that you have been on insulin treatment since the time of your diagnosis and have never been prescribed oral agents for the management of diabetes. More recently, he has been using insulin glargine 55 units once daily and insulin aspart movable scale/ variable dose 3 times daily. The patient has had previous episodes of diabetic ketoacidosis, for which he was hospitalized. With this episode of hyperglycemia, she has no nausea, vomiting, or abdominal discomfort, and she is doing well. The following laboratory analyses were performed: A1c: 11.3% Creatinine: 0.9 mg/dL with TFGe &gt; 60 mL/min Aspartate aminotransferase (AST): 17 U/L Alanine aminotransferase (ALT): 14 U/L Beta-hydroxybutyrate: 0.1 mmol/L Bicarbonate: 25 mEq/L Anion gap: 14 mEq/L The following are the results of the laboratory analyses:</topic><topic number="30">The patient, a 33-year-old woman, complained of fatigue, weight gain, and abnormal spotting between periods. No hirsutism or nipple discharge was detected. His BMI was 34. His laboratory results were high in TSH (13 mU/L) and low in free T4 (0.2 ng/dl). Their anti-TPO levels were extremely high (120 IU/ml). He was diagnosed with Hashimoto's thyroiditis. His aunt, brother and mother all suffer from the same disease. After starting levothyroxine at 250 mcg a day, her symptoms improved significantly and her periods are normal. She's still overweight with a BMI of 31. His most recent thyroid profile revealed all but anti-TPO results within the normal range: TSH: 2.35 mU/L free T4: 2.7 ng/dl Anti-TPO: 75 IU/ml</topic><topic number="31">The patient is a 37-year-old woman who came to the clinic for a routine cervical cytology. The test revealed stage 1B cervical cancer. The patient tested positive for HPV 16. He has three sexual partners and four children. He underwent a tubal ligation. He smokes 30 packs a year and drinks alcohol frequently. Otherwise, she's healthy. She was offered a radical hysterectomy.</topic><topic number="32">A 17-year-old complains of vomiting, bloodless diarrhea, abdominal pain, fever, chills and loss of appetite for the past 3 days. He ate a salad at a restaurant before the diarrhea. On physical examination, he was marked for pallor, jaundice, and diffuse abdominal pain. Laboratory results were as follows: Hemoglobin: 9.7 g/dL Platelets: 110,000/mm3 Creatinine: 3.6 mg/dL Blood urea nitrogen (BUN): 73 mg/dL Direct bilirubin: 2.4 mg/dL Lactate dehydrogenase (LDH): 881 IU/L (normal: 110-265 IU/L) The peripheral blood smear showed a moderate amount of schistocytes and helmet cells. Shiga-like toxin (STEC) producing E. coli bacteria stx1/stx2 were found in faeces. He has no other underlying medical conditions and is not taking any medications.</topic><topic number="33">A healthy 42-year-old woman came to the clinic for a flu shot in early October. She works in a rehab facility and has no underlying medical condition. It's the first time he's been vaccinated this year. She's been married for five years and uses barrier methods of contraception. Her menstrual cycle is irregular. He doesn't smoke. He's not on any medication. Exercise regularly for 30 minutes a day, at least 5 days a week. He has no history of allergies to any food or medication. Her surgical history includes a tonsillectomy, and otherwise, she's healthy.</topic><topic number="34">Patient is a 47-year-old Asian woman who complains of persistent feelings of sadness. He lost interest in activities he used to enjoy. He claims his mood has been mostly depressed for the past 3 weeks. He also lost his appetite, which resulted in a weight loss of approximately 5 kg. He complains of loss of energy and feelings of worthlessness almost daily. He doesn't do drugs or smoke. He doesn't drink alcohol. He used to exercise every day for at least 30 minutes, but he doesn't have enough energy to do it for the last 3 weeks. He's also had some digestive problems recently. She's married with four children. She's in the menopause. Your husband was recently diagnosed with colon cancer and is beginning his chemotherapy. There's nothing remarkable in his past medical history and his drug history is only positive for 1,000 units of vitamin D3 a day. His family history is negative for any psychological problems. His HAM-D score is 20.</topic><topic number="35">Patient is a 15-year-old female with a history of bilateral recurrent headache. The attacks occur two or more times a week and each episode lasts about a day or a half. The pain is throbbing and intense, making it difficult for you to perform your usual physical activity. The attacks are associated with nausea and photophobia. Recently, she's noticed that she has more attacks near her menstrual period. He's been diagnosed with a migraine and is undergoing treatment. She's in high school and lives with her parents. She is a voracious reader and spends her free time in a public library near her home. She is also interested in writing short stories and has several in English. He rarely exercises. His BMI is 21 and his blood pressure is 100/60. There's nothing remarkable about her physical.</topic><topic number="36">The patient is a 32-year-old obese woman who came to the clinic with weight problems. He is 5'5" and weighs 113 pounds. She has sleep apnea, polycystic ovarian syndrome, and dissatisfaction with her figure. She's a high school teacher and has been married for five years. You have not used any contraceptive method in the last 4 months and you have not had a previous pregnancy. He doesn't smoke or do drugs. She likes to try diets and exercise to lose weight. He completed the four-square-step test (FSST) in 14 seconds. His blood pressure is 130/80, his heart rate is 195 beats per minute, and his BMI is 41.54. His lab results are: Glucose in the fasted state: 98 mg/dl TG: 150 mg/dl Cholesterol: 180 mg/dl LDL: 90 mg/dl HDL: 35 mg/dl His cardiac evaluation is normal. His joints and range of motion are within normal limits.</topic><topic number="37">Patient is a 20-year-old Caucasian female who comes to the clinic with unilateral vision loss and facial weakness, dysarthria, and numbness lasting 1 day. She went to her GP and underwent an MRI scan of her brain that revealed a single plaque in her brain stem. After a few months, he experienced weakness in his lower extremities that caused balance problems. The second MRI revealed another lesion in the left cerebral hemisphere. The diagnosis of relapsing-remitting multiple sclerosis (RRMS) is confirmed after the second MRI. His surgical history is significant past a C-section two years ago and he has a son. She's divorced and currently has no sexual relationship. He smokes 10 cigarettes a day and drinks alcohol occasionally. She works as an editor at a publishing house and is happy to be able to continue working from home most of the time. He's been on treatment for RRMS for the past seven months.</topic><topic number="38">Patient is a 35-year-old female with myasthenia gravis class IIa. She has diplopia, fatigue and weakness affecting mainly the upper extremities. He tested positive for anti-AChR antibodies and single-fiber electromyography (EMG-FU). Take 60 mg of pyridostigmine three times a day. However, he still has some symptoms that interfere with his work. She's a research coordinator and has three kids. Her 70-year-old father has high blood pressure. He doesn't smoke or use illegal drugs. He drinks alcohol occasionally at social events. His physical examination and lab tests showed no other abnormalities. The test chemical is a substance which is used in the manufacture of a substance or mixture.</topic><topic number="39">A three-day-old Asian infant has jaundice that started a day ago. She was born at 38 weeks and 3 days of gestation, after a pregnancy without complications. He has no family history of interest. The baby is breastfed. His vital signs are: axillary temperature: 36.3 &#176;C, heart rate: 154 beats/min, respiratory rate: 37 breaths/min and blood pressure: 65/33 mmHg. It weighs 3.2 kg, measures 53 cm and its head circumference is 36 cm. He has yellow sclerosis and jaundice. No murmurs or other abnormalities are detected in the cardiac and pulmonary auscultation. Liver and spleen palpations are normal. The laboratory results are as follows: Total serum bilirubin: 21.02 mg/dL Direct bilirubin: 2.04 mg/dL AST: 37 U/L ALT: 20 U/L GGT: 745 U/L Alkaline phosphatase: 531 U/L Creatinine: 0.3 mg/dL Urea: 29 mg/dL Na: 147 mEq/L K: 4.5 mEq/L PCR: 3 mg/L Complete blood count within the normal range. He's diagnosed with uncomplicated neonatal jaundice that might require phototherapy.</topic><topic number="40">The patient is a 60-year-old male who complains of frequent headaches, widespread bone pain, and difficulty chewing that began six years ago and is getting worse. Examination shows bilateral swelling around the molars. The swelling's increased since your last exam. Multiple extraoral lesions are detected on the head and face. The swelling is not painful and is attached to the underlying bone. Further evaluation shows increased uptake of radioactive substance as well as increased urinary pyridinoline. Its serum alkaline phosphatase is 300 IU/ L (the normal range is 44 to 147 IU/ L). Her family history is only significant for hypertension in her mother and type 2 DM in her father. Paget's bone disease diagnosis was confirmed and a bisphosphonate will be started as first-line therapy.</topic><topic number="41">A 57-year-old farmer was diagnosed with Parkinson's disease a year ago. He experiences slowness of movement and tremors. His medical history includes hypertension and hypercholesterolemia. He lives with his wife and they have three children. Before the diagnosis, he used to be a farmer and a rancher. The patient complains of tremors and slow movement. He had difficulty getting through a door, since he would become paralyzed and needed help to do so. His handwriting is getting smaller and smaller. He's on levodopa and trihexyphenidyl. He said his medication helps with the tremors and the slowness of movement. However, he still has difficulty initiating movements, stiffness and general slowness. He's an alert, cooperative man who shows no signs of dementia. He doesn't smoke or use illegal drugs.</topic><topic number="42">19-year-old Hispanic woman, one pregnancy and one delivery, 32+6 weeks gestational age, reported to the obstetrics clinic for routine follow-up complaining of mild headache and leg swelling. Primary evaluation revealed a blood pressure of 146/99 and a urine test strip with 3+ proteins. Your blood pressure and urinalysis were normal at the last visit. A few hours later, the repeat blood pressure is 150/100 mmHg. Laboratory studies showed normal haematocrit, platelet count and liver transaminase levels. She complains of fatigue, but she has no fever or chills. He also suffers from headaches without changes in vision. No breathing difficulties, cough, chest pain, orthopnea, palpitations or rash were observed. His physical examination was negative for abdominal pain, changes in bowel habits, nausea, vomiting, dysuria, frequency, hematuria or foamy urine. Swelling of the legs was observed without arthralgia or back pain. She has no specific medical history and only takes prenatal vitamins. His family history is positive for type 2 diabetes and hypertension. He drinks socially and has not smoked or used drugs. She's only had one partner in the last two years and hasn't used any contraception in two years. Her BMI was 24 at the first visit, when she was six weeks pregnant. She's gaining weight normally during her pregnancies.</topic><topic number="43">Patient is a 60-year-old female admitted to the stroke unit with a recent history of a second course of intravenous antibiotics for aspiration pneumonia. Fever, abdominal pain, and diarrhea (eight bowel movements in three hours, with abundant greenish liquid stools in each). The patient's abdomen is experiencing pain on palpation and distention, with hyperactive bowel sounds. He has a fever (38.4 &#176;C), tachycardia (113 beats per minute) and hypotension (80/40 mmHg). The stool samples must have tested positive for Clostridium difficile toxin.</topic><topic number="44">The patient is a 14-year-old boy who suffers from scoliosis and back pain. He has no other medical condition. He used to be able to do routine activities like basketball and soccer, but recently he has had difficulty doing them. The pain is localized to the leg and back, and it gets worse with physical activity. He prefers to lie down most of the time. He is not satisfied with his body gestures and complains of imbalance in the balance of the shoulders and deflecting the head to the right. The patient is a well-dressed, well-fed, alert adolescent. The patient is a 34-year-old African-American male with a known history of sickle cell disease who comes to the clinic with severe bone pain. The patient had severe lower back pain radiating to both thighs with a score of 9 out of 10. The patient has a positive history of sickle cell crisis since childhood. He also had the same symptoms in the last two weeks, treated with oxycodone, which was not beneficial for his pain. His primary care physician sent him to the emergency department for intravenous pain modulators. The patient is afebrile within normal blood pressure. No splenomegaly was detected on physical examination. He has no positive history of drug allergy. He doesn't smoke or use any illegal drugs. The laboratory study is as follows: Hb: 8 g/dl Leukocytes: 10000/mm3 Plt: 300000 /ml VCM: 106 fL Haemoglobin electrophoresis: 91% HbS 6% HbF 3% HbA2 AST: 22 U/L ALT: 43 U/L FAL: 53 U/L Ferritin: 1200 ng/ml and cooperative. The results of the study were as follows: The left shoulder is slightly higher than the right. The scoliosis curvature is measured at 45 degrees. The patient is a candidate for scoliosis surgery based on perioperative motor evoked potential (EMP) monitoring.</topic><topic number="45">Patient is a 34-year-old African-American male with a known history of sickle cell disease who comes to the clinic with severe bone pain. The patient had severe lower back pain radiating to both thighs with a score of 9 out of 10. The patient has a positive history of sickle cell crisis since childhood. He also had the same symptoms in the last two weeks, treated with oxycodone, which was not beneficial for his pain. His primary care physician sent him to the emergency department for intravenous pain modulators. The patient is afebrile within normal blood pressure. No splenomegaly was detected on physical examination. He has no positive history of drug allergy. He will not smoke or use any illicit drugs. The laboratory study is as follows: Hb: 8 g/dl Leukocytes: 10000/mm3 Plt: 300000 /ml VCM: 106 fL Haemoglobin electrophoresis: 91% HbS 6% HbF 3% HbA2 AST: 22 U/L ALT: 43 U/L FAL: 53 U/L Ferritin: 1200 ng/ml The following is the laboratory study:</topic><topic number="46">Patient A is a 30-year-old male who was admitted to the hospital after 10 days of coughing, profuse night sweats and loss of appetite. He had traveled to India a month earlier and had no positive TB vaccination history. He's a formerly healthy man, working as an engineer for a high-tech company. He doesn't smoke or use any illegal drugs. He was feverish (38&#176;C) with a heart rate of 115 lpm, respiratory rate of 22, BP of 125/75 mmHg and O2 saturation of 97%. Chest X-ray showed a mid-level infiltrate in the left lung, 1.8 cm in diameter with signs of cavitation. The sputum swab revealed a sputum culture positive for Mycobacterium tuberculosis, which is sensitive to the first-line anti-tuberculosis drugs (isoniazid, streptomycin, rifampicin and etambutol). The following is the laboratory study: Hb: 13 g/dl Leukocytes: 14000/mm3 Plt: 300000 /ml AST: 13 U/L ALT: 15U/L FAL: 53 U/L Total bilirubin: 0.6 mg/dl Na: 137 mEq/l K: 4 mEq/l Creatinine: 0.5 mg/dl BUN: 10 mg/dl VSG: 120 mm/h</topic><topic number="47">A 62-year-old African American male presented with weakness in the upper and lower left extremities, associated with a dark visual spot in the right eye, right facial numbness, facial drooping, and difficulty speaking. Dyspnoea, headache, palpitations, chest pain, fever, dizziness, bowel or urinary incontinence, loss of consciousness were reported. His medical history included high blood pressure, hyperlipidemia, and hypothyroidism. He's smoked a pack of cigarettes a day for 40 years and consumes five to six beers a week. He has no knowledge of your family history. He's on levothyroxine, atorvastatin and the HTCZ. His vitals were stable at the primary evaluation. On physical examination, facial droop on the left side, left-sided dysarthria and hemiplegia were observed. His score on the National Institutes of Health Stroke Scale (NIHSS) was calculated as 7. Initial head and neck CT angiography did not reveal any acute intracranial findings. Intravenous recombinant plasminogen activator (t-PA) and high dose statin therapy were administered. The patient was admitted to the intensive care unit to be monitored for 24 hours. MRI of the head revealed a 1.7 cm acute infarction of the right periventricular white matter and the right posterior basal ganglia.</topic><topic number="48">Fern&#225;ndez is a 41-year-old man who is a professional footballer. She came to the clinic with an itchy foot. Physical examination revealed localized peeling and maceration between the third and fourth toes of the right foot. It became inflamed and started to hurt, with slight fissures. The back and the sole of the foot were unaffected. No pus or tears in the affected area. He didn't use any topical ointment on the lesion and he has no positive history of any underlying disease such as DM. He smokes 15 cigarettes a day and drinks a beer a day. Her family history is positive for hyperlipidemia in her mother and myocardial infarction in her father. He has a relationship with several partners and uses a condom during sex. His physical examination and lab tests were otherwise normal. Foot ringworm infection was confirmed as his diagnosis by observation of segmented fungal hyphae during a wet preparation microscopic examination with KOH.</topic><topic number="49">A 12-year-old girl came to the clinic with her mother complaining of short stature, delayed puberty, and stunted development. His karyotype study revealed 45X and confirmed the diagnosis of Turner syndrome. She's been on GH for the past six months without estrogen therapy to avoid menarche and achieve her ideal height. The physical examination shows that she is an obese and mentally retarded child. Her breast bud was stage one with no thick hair on the pubic or axillary areas. In the last lab study, his TSH was 3 and his basal fasting glucose was 75.</topic><topic number="50">A 5-month-old boy was taken to the pediatric surgery clinic with the complaint of an empty scrotum on the right side. The baby is the first child born at 38 weeks with normal vaginal delivery from a healthy mother. The mother had a normal pregnancy with no complications. The baby weighed 3,200 grams and was 50 cm long. He's being breastfed and now weighs 6.5 kg and is 62 cm tall. No developmental delay on the physical. There's a palpable testicle in the left scrotum and an imperceptible testicle in the right scrotum. The penis is normal in shape and size and uncircumcised. Diagnostic laparoscopy showed an undescended abdominal testicle.</topic><topic number="51">Patient is a 25-year-old pregnant female G1 P1 with a gestational age of 24 weeks and 3 days who presented with a sudden onset of fever and chills, accompanied by nausea and vomiting. He also complains of dysuria, urgency and frequency. He also refers to having a severe pain in his side. The vital signs are: T = 39.7oC, FC = 117, R = 20 and PA = 113/74 mm Hg. Physical examination reveals pain on palpation from both costovertebral angles. You have no history of recurrent urinary tract infections prior to your pregnancy or any other underlying illness. Urine culture showed gram-negative bacterial cells in the form of bacillus, leukocytes and leukocyte cylinders. The blood culture is negative. A complete blood count shows Hb 12.9 g/dl, Hct 39%, VCM 76 fl and white blood cell count 14 120/&#956;l.</topic><topic number="52">A 34-year-old man comes to the clinic complaining of dizziness and severe diarrhea since yesterday. He returned from an international trip a few days ago and has been living in a camp in Sudan for a month. She developed abdominal pain followed by swelling and nausea, as well as soft stools. Soon she began to have profuse, odorless watery diarrhea. The stool is watery and white, but the patient has no fever. Blood pressure is 95/62 lying down and drops to 75/40 standing up. The skin turgor has reduced. Heart rate is 110 and he looks sick with dry mucus. V. cholerae was observed in dark field microscopy of a fresh faeces sample. The laboratory test is as follows: Sodium 137 meq/L Potassium 2 meq/L Chloride 94 meq/L CO2 15 meq/L Fecal leukocytes None Blood occulted in faeces Negative</topic><topic number="53">The patient is a 34-year-old woman from Jordan who comes to the clinic with general and non-specific bone and joint pain. She's married with three kids. His medical history and drug history are nothing remarkable. His BMI is 23, PA: 120/75, FC: 75/min. His lab study is remarkable for Vit D: 14ng/ml and otherwise healthy. The test chemical is a solvent and the test chemical is a carrier of the test chemical.</topic><topic number="54">A 57-year-old man was admitted to the clinic due to weight loss and persistent dry cough 4 months ago. CT scan of the chest showed multiple bilateral infiltrations in the upper lobes and thickened bronchial walls. There's a positive serum MPO-ANCA documented in his medical history. Transbronchial biopsy revealed necrotic granulomas with multinucleated giant cells and he was diagnosed with Wegener's granulomatosis. He's been on corticosteroids and cyclophosphamides for the past four months. His Birmingham vasculitis activity score (BVAS) is above 4 since the beginning of his illness. His last physical examination and laboratory study was performed yesterday and yielded the following results: A healthy, well-nourished, non-icteric, cooperative and alert man. The following table shows the number of samples of the test chemical used in the manufacture of the test chemical:</topic><topic number="55">A 22-year-old Caucasian man came to the clinic with a history of tremors for a year. The tremor was first in his right hand as he was holding something. Subsequently the tremor became continuous and spread to both hands and legs and even at rest. The ophthalmological examination showed the presence of the Kayser-Fleischer ring. Physical examination revealed jaundice, hepato-splenomegaly and hypotonia of the upper limbs. He had a constant smile on his face, however, he has an aggressive behavior according to his parents' explanation. Its laboratory study was significant for low serum ceruloplasmin (0.05 g/ l) and elevated copper excretion in 24-hour urine (120 &#956;g/24 h). Wilson's disease was confirmed by a high concentration of copper in the liver (305 &#956;g/g of dry weight of the liver).</topic><topic number="56">Patient is a 41-year-old male known case of acromegaly who underwent transesphenoidal surgery 4 months ago. He went to the clinic for follow-up lab studies after his primary resection surgery. His lab study shows a gender- and age-adjusted IGF-1 level of 4.5 LSN. His random GH level is 4 ug/L. Recent MRI confirmed residual pituitary tumor. Among his medical history, only acromegaly due to pituitary adenoma and recent surgery stand out. After the surgery, she only takes vitamin D and multivitamins.</topic><topic number="57">Patient is a 41-year-old obese woman who comes to the emergency room with abdominal pain and vomiting. The pain, which started gradually yesterday, is localized to the epigastric and periumbilical regions, radiating to the back. He drinks alcohol frequently and doesn't smoke. She has no history of allergies and only takes a daily multivitamin. Her family history is positive for hypertension (her mother). She lives with her husband and has 3 children. The abdomen is painful to the touch and soft. His bowel sounds are normal. His heart rate is 115 beats per minute and his blood pressure is 110/75 mmHg. Laboratory studies are notable for leucocytosis (19.5), urea of 8.5, high PCR (145), high amylase (1200) and glucose level of 270. His abdominal CT scan revealed acute interstitial edema pancreatitis with enlargement of the common bile duct and intrahepatic duct, which confirms pancreatitis by gallstones. Her pregnancy test is negative and she's not breastfeeding.</topic><topic number="58">The patient is a 17-year-old male with severe migratory pain in the lower right quadrant of his abdomen, which began four days ago. The pain is accompanied by nausea and vomiting. Fever with pain on palpation, rebound pain and defense on palpation. His white blood cell count was elevated, with neutrophils predominant. CT showed evidence of acute appendicitis perforated with free fluid in the pelvis. Diagnostic laparoscopy revealed phlegm without any other abdominal abnormalities. He's currently a candidate for an emergency laparoscopic appendectomy under general anesthesia.</topic><topic number="59">Patient is a 15-year-old with asthma diagnosed a year ago. She has dyspnea, tightness in the chest and coughing. According to his mother, he didn't respond to the usual corticosteroid inhaler. She was admitted to the emergency room with a diagnosis of severe asthma exacerbation. It is a candidate for treatment with systemic corticosteroids. Spirometry revealed a forced expiratory volume in the first second (FEV1) of 60% of the expected value. His medical history is insignificant. His mother and uncle have a family history of asthma. He was being treated with a combination of inhaled corticosteroids and zafirlukast.</topic><topic number="60">Patient is a 63-year-old male coming into the E.R. with a history of acute urinary retention in the last two days. Abdominopelvic CT revealed an enlarged prostate and a bladder filled with urine. It is a candidate for urethral catheterization and transurethral resection of the prostate (TURP). Further evaluation revealed: Post-migration residues: 71 ml Prostate volume (transrectal ultrasound): 63 ml Prostate specific antigen (PSA): 3.5 ng/ml Your recent blood biochemistry (3 days ago) was normal: Hb: 13.6 g/dl Leukocytes: 133 000/mm3 Plaquetast: 370 000/ml TP: 12 seconds PTT: 34 seconds INR: 0.9 Creatinine: 0.5 mg/dl BUN: 10 mg/dl Urinalysis was performed and the results were as follows: The following table shows the number of cases of the disease in the European Union:</topic><topic number="61">Patient is a postmenopausal woman, 45 years old, with cytologically confirmed breast cancer. A thick needle biopsy revealed a 3 cm invasive ductal carcinoma in the left upper outer quadrant. The tumor is HER2 positive and RE/RP negative. The axillary biopsy revealed five positive lymph nodes. The chest X-ray showed metastatic lesions. The patient is taking multivitamins and iron supplements. He doesn't smoke or drink. She's not sexually active or has any children. She's a candidate for a tumor resection and agrees to undergo it before chemotherapy.</topic><topic number="62">A 46-year-old man has frequent dizziness and headaches. He has a family history of coronary heart disease, but has no other cardiovascular risk factors such as smoking, high blood pressure and diabetes mellitus, and is physically active. Their LDL cholesterol and HDL cholesterol levels were 545 and 53 mg/dl, respectively. His fasting glucose and triglyceride levels (85 and 158 mg/dl, respectively) were within normal limits. The patient did not report any lipid-lowering medication. Cervical auscultation revealed a 3+/6+ systolic blow to the neck, radiating to the skull. Ultrasound of the carotid arteries revealed severe stenosis in the left internal carotid artery (LCA) as well as moderate stenosis in the right internal carotid artery (RCA), estimated to be between 40% and 50%. For the left internal carotid artery (LCA), the cut-off values for the maximum systolic velocity (MSV) and the telediastolic velocity (MTD) were 208.5 cm/ s and 54.5 cm/ s, respectively; the MSV of the right internal carotid artery (ICA) was 91.72 cm/ s and the MTD of the ACI was 37.37 cm/ s. Plaque was observed on the anterior and posterior walls of the internal carotid artery and common carotid artery, characterized as voluminous plaques extending to the middle third of the internal coronary arteries (ACI) and were predominantly ecogenic and hyperechoic, with less than 50% of the ecolocus area having irregular surfaces.</topic><topic number="63">A 54-year-old obese woman entered the emergency room with abdominal pain that started 4 days ago with nausea and vomiting. The epigastric pain radiates to the upper right quadrant, worsening after eating fatty foods. The patient experienced similar pain twice in the last year. Her past medical history is notable for hypercholesterolemia and 2 normal vaginal deliveries. She has two children and is menopausal. He does not smoke, drink alcohol, or use illegal drugs. She has a slight fever. The pH of the test chemical is 150/85, FC 115, FR 15, T 38.2, SpO2 98% in AR. She's an obese woman with no acute distress. On palpation, he experiences pain at epigastric palpation and pain at palpation in the upper right quadrant without rebound. The bowel sounds are normal. Laboratory analysis is notable for elevated VSG and leukocytosis with a left deviation. Ultrasound revealed several gallstones, bile mud and stones in the common bile duct. The smallest stone is 14 millimeters.</topic><topic number="64">Patient is a 55-year-old male diagnosed with HCV 2 years ago and recent co-infection with HBV. His past medical history is not significant. She's on IFN, RBV and direct antiviral medication for the last 6 months. The patient is not taking any other medications. Your medical history shows previous positive HCV RNA testing and a positive enzyme immunoassay for anti-HCV antibodies. The recent biopsy was negative for hepatocellular carcinoma and was only notable for chronic inflammation consistent with chronic viral hepatitis. There is no evidence of alcoholic liver disease, bleeding from esophageal varices, hemochromatosis, autoimmune hepatitis or metabolic liver disease. He's a man of alertness without acute distress. The test chemical is a substance with a low pH, a low pH, and a low pH. Her abdomen is soft with no ascites or pain on palpation. Lower extremities are normal with no edema.</topic><topic number="65">The patient is a 25-year-old male with type 1 diabetes, confirmed by molecular analysis seven years ago. Go to the clinic for dyspnea and fatigue during activities. Refers to mild dyspnea after climbing 3 floors, with no resting dyspnea or angina pectoris (New York Heart Association class 2). You're diagnosed with myocardial infarction, which will be treated with ACE inhibitors and beta blockers. She's on insulin 70/30 and vitamin D supplements. She has no other relevant medical problems. His medical history is positive for type 1 DM in his uncle and grandfather. His lab tests are as follows: Basal fasting glucose: 100 mg/dl HbA1c: 6.5 % Cholesterol: 190 mg/dl TG: 140 mg/dl LDL: 125 mg/dl HDL: 40 mg/dl</topic><topic number="66">A 16-year-old girl came to the clinic complaining of weight gain and abnormal menstrual cycles. Her BMI was 24, but she'd gained five kilos in the last few weeks. She gets tired more often and doesn't have the energy to go out dancing with her friends. His laboratory tests were remarkable: high levels of TSH (15 mU/L) and low levels of free T4 (0.18 ng/dl). Their anti-TPO levels were extremely high (136 IU/ml). He was diagnosed with Hashimoto's disease. She doesn't smoke or have sex.</topic><topic number="67">A cervical cytology on a 54-year-old woman revealed an abnormal intraepithelial/glandular scaly cervical lesion. He tested positive for HPV 16. She has sexual relations with her husband and has four children. She's in menopause and not using birth control. He smokes and drinks alcohol frequently. Otherwise, he is in good health. He was offered a conization.</topic><topic number="68">The patient is a 23-year-old male who was admitted to hospital with high blood pressure (175/95 mmHg) and signs of septicemia. He developed respiratory failure that required mechanical ventilation and renal failure that required hemodialysis. His blood smear showed microangiopathic hemolytic anemia and thrombocytopenia. Their blood tests revealed elevated levels of lactate dehydrogenase and reduced levels of human C3 complement with a normal clotting profile. He was diagnosed with atypical hemolytic uremic syndrome. He was treated with plasmapheresis and corticosteroids. He had previously been vaccinated with the meningococcal conjugate vaccine of group ACWY and the meningococcal vaccine of group B. The genetic study showed ADAMTS13 to be &gt; 10%.</topic><topic number="69">A healthy 67-year-old woman came to the clinic for a flu shot in early October. She works at a rehab facility and has no underlying medical condition. It's his first shot this year. She's in menopause and has four children. He doesn't have any. She takes multivitamins and antihypertensives every day. Exercise regularly for 30 minutes a day, at least 5 days a week. He's not allergic to any food or medication.</topic><topic number="70">A 46-year-old Asian woman with MDD complains of persistent feelings of sadness and loss of interest in daily activities. He claims that his mood remains depressed most of the time. He complains of loss of energy and feelings of worthlessness almost daily. She's been on antidepressants for six months, but the symptoms persist. He doesn't drink alcohol or smoke. He used to exercise every day for at least 30 minutes, but he hasn't had enough energy to do it for three weeks. He's also had some digestive problems recently. She's married with four children. She's in the menopause. Your husband was diagnosed with colon cancer a year ago and is undergoing chemotherapy. His medical history is normal. His family history is negative for any psychological problems. His score on the Ham-D scale is 20.</topic><topic number="71">The patient is a 34-year-old obese woman who comes to the clinic for weight problems. She is 5'5" and weighs 113 kg (BMI: 41.5). In the past, he's used anti-obesity agents and appetite suppressants without success. She complains of sleep apnea, PCOS, and dissatisfaction with her figure. She's a high school teacher. She's been married for five years. You have not used any contraceptive method in the last 4 months and you have not been pregnant before. He rarely exercises and movement seems difficult. You can't complete the four-square-step test in less than 15 seconds. He doesn't smoke or do drugs. Your blood pressure is 130/80, your heart rate is 195/min and your BMI is 41.54. Laboratory results: Fasting serum glucose: 98 mg/dl TG: 150 mg/dl Cholesterol: 180 mg/dl LDL: 90 mg/dl HDL: 35 mg/dl Laparoscopic gastric bypass is being considered.</topic><topic number="72">Patient is a 16-year-old female with a recent diagnosis of myasthenia gravis, class IIa. She has diplopia and weakness in the upper extremities. He tested positive for anti-AChR antibodies and for single-fiber electromyography (SFEMG). You are treated with acetylcholinesterase inhibitors and immunosuppressants. However, it persists with some symptoms. He doesn't smoke or use illegal drugs. She's not sexually active and her periods are regular. Your physical examination and lab tests show no other abnormalities. The following table shows the number of samples of the test chemical used in the manufacture of the test chemical:</topic><topic number="73">Patient is a 3-day-old infant with jaundice that started a day ago. She was born at 34 weeks gestation and kept in incubator due to her gestational age. His vital signs were: axillary temperature: 36.3 &#176;C, heart rate: 154 beats/min, respiratory rate: 37 breaths/min and blood pressure: 65/33 mmHg. Its weight is 2.1 kg, its height is 45 cm and its head circumference is 32 cm. He has yellow sclerosis and jaundice. Liver and spleen are normal to the touch. The laboratory results are as follows: Total serum bilirubin: 21.02 mg/dL Direct bilirubin: 2.04 mg/dL AST: 37 U/L ALT: 20 U/L GGT: 745 U/L Alkaline phosphatase: 531 U/L Creatinine: 0.3 mg/dL Urea: 29 mg/dL Na: 147 mEq/L K: 4.5 mEq/L PCR: 3 mg/L Complete blood count within the normal range. He's diagnosed with neonatal jaundice that may require phototherapy.</topic><topic number="74">The patient is a 53-year-old male who complains of frequent headaches, widespread bone pain and difficulty chewing that began 6 years ago and is getting worse. Examination shows bilateral swelling around the molars. The swelling's increased since your last exam. Several extraoral lesions are detected on the head and face. The swelling is not painful and is attached to the underlying bone. Further evaluation shows increased uptake of radioactive substance as well as increased urinary pyridinoline. The serum alkaline phosphatase is 300 IU/ L (the normal range is 44 to 147 IU/ L). The patient's sister had the same problems. She was diagnosed with Paget's disease of bone when she was 52. Diagnosis of Paget's bone disease is confirmed and a bisphosphonate will be initiated as first-line therapy.</topic><topic number="75">The patient is a 55-year-old man who was recently diagnosed with Parkinson's disease. He complains of slow movements and tremors. His disease is classified as mild, stage I of Hoehn-Yahr. His medical history is significant for hypertension and hypercholesterolemia. He lives with his wife. They have three children. He used to be active with gardening before his diagnosis. He complains of tremors and slow movement. He had difficulty getting through a door, as he was frozen and needed help to get in. His handwriting is getting smaller and smaller. You're offered levodopa and trihexyphenidyl. He's an alert, cooperative man who shows no signs of dementia. He doesn't smoke or use illegal drugs.</topic></topics>