<topics task="2021 TREC Clinical Trials"><topic number="1">Patient is a 45-year-old male with a history of anaplastic astrocytoma of the spine complicated by severe lower limb weakness and urinary retention treated with Foley catheter placement, high-dose steroid therapy, hypertension and chronic pain. The tumor is localized to the thoracolumbar spine, classified as an anaplastic non-resectable astrocytoma, undergoing radiation therapy. Complicated by progressive weakness of the lower extremities and urinary retention. The patient initially presented with weakness in the right lower limb, with right knee collapse, difficulty walking, and dysesthesia of the front of the right thigh. MRI showed a cone-shaped mass in the spinal cord which, when biopsied, turned out to be an anaplastic astrocytoma. Treatment included: radiotherapy of the T10-L1 tract followed by 11 cycles of temozolomide 7 days yes and 7 days no. This was followed by treatment with CPT-11 weekly x 4 weeks, plus treatment with Avastin with 2 weeks of treatment and 2 weeks off, repeated.</topic><topic number="2">48-year-old male, with a positive history of hypertension, hyperlipidemia, bicuspid aortic valve, and smoking, presents to the cardiologist on [**2148-10-1**] with aggravated dyspnea and edema of the lower extremities. Transthoracic echocardiography (TTE) revealed severe aortic stenosis with worsening of the function of the left ventricle. The ejection fraction was 25%. Right ventricular pressure was 41 and presenting with bi-atrial dilation. Grade 2+ aortic insufficiency with mild mitral insufficiency was observed. He was discharged from the cardiology clinic with Lasix and beta-blockers (which he couldn't tolerate), continued to have worsening dyspnea and edema in his lower extremities, and finally came in here for an evaluation. During this hospitalization, a further echocardiogram confirmed a critical aortic stenosis showing left ventricular hypertrophy with cavity dilation and severe global hypotension, severe aortic valve stenosis with underlying bicuspid aortic valve, dilated ascending aorta, mild pulmonary artery systolic hypertension. The patient underwent preoperative valve replacement examination with chest CT and preoperative carotid ultrasound (showing moderate heterogeneous plaque with bilateral carotid artery stenosis of 1-39%). He also underwent right-sided cardiac catheterization to assess pulmonary pressures, which showed no angiographically evident flow-limiting coronary artery disease.</topic><topic number="3">A 32-year-old woman presents after a severe "explosive" headache. She and her husband report that yesterday, while she was in the kitchen, she got up and hit her head on the corner of a piece of furniture. The next morning he developed a sudden "explosive" headache. She went to the hospital where a cranial CT showed a significant amount of blood in her right ventricle. The neurosurgeon requested an evaluation for spontaneous intraventricular hemorrhage with the suspicion of an underlying vascular malformation. A cerebral angiogram was performed which showed abnormal vascularisation with a draining vein from the left temporal lobe penetrating the deep white matter consistent with AVM. The patient was still having headaches, but the situation was improving with the painkillers. The patient refused physiotherapy evaluation, but walked independently without difficulty. She was discharged and returned home with her husband on [**2155-12-6**].</topic><topic number="4">This is a 44-year-old woman with a long history of polycystic ovary syndrome (PCOS), obesity and hypertension, who presented with symptoms of cholecystitis and who was incidentally found to have a large pericardial effusion. Pericardiocentesis was performed and the pericardial fluid was found to be compatible with Burkitt's lymphoma. The pericardial fluid contained CD10-positive monotypic B cells with pathological kappa light chain enlargement, which expressed FMC-7, CD19, CD20 and myc rearrangement, compatible with Burkitt's lymphoma. A subsequent lumbar puncture and a bone marrow biopsy were negative for any involvement, which led to the identification of a primary cardiac lymphoma. A cardiac MRI showed a 3 cm x 1 cm mass on the lateral wall of the right atrium adjacent to the atrioventricular junction. Patient has a history of: 1. Blood pressure 3. Obesity 4. The following table summarises the data for the year 2000: Viral encephalitis/meningitis -&gt; intracranial haemorrhage -&gt; convulsions/stroke ([**2137**]) =- from severe infectious sinusitis, which has residual mild nonfocal deficits 6. Cerebrospinal fluid leakage with meningitis treated with lumbar drainage placement 7. The right lower limb TVP treated with IVC 8 filter placement. Surgery of the knee</topic><topic number="5">74-year-old male, with a history of coronary artery disease treated with coronary artery bypass grafting (CABG), 60% FE, previous thrombocytopenia (no residual deficiency), hypertension, type II diabetic lymphoadenopathy, moderate to severe left ventricular dysfunction (LVD), was referred to cardiology for evaluation of LVD and, on objective examination, carotid blocks were found. After further symptom evaluation, the patient reports: + occasional dizziness, no previous syncope, occasional carotid hypertrophy, denial of CP/ SOB. No sensory or motor impairments. He remembers having a stroke 10 or 15 years ago with no residual deficit. Before the CABG, she only had diaphoresis. Further system evaluation is noteworthy for the absence of chest pain, stress dyspnea, paroxysmal nocturnal dyspnea, orthopnea, palpitations, syncope or presyncope. He underwent carotid ultrasound which showed significant bilateral carotid stenosis, SX&gt;DX. The angiogram revealed a stenosis of 80% of the right internal carotid and 90% of the left internal carotid. The cerebral angiography also revealed permeability of the right coronary artery and the left left middle cerebral artery, as well as permeability of the left coronary artery and the left middle cerebral artery. In the absence of a clinical history, the patient is considered to have a history of cardiovascular disease (CVD) or cardiovascular disease (CVD) if the patient has a history of cardiovascular disease (CVD) or cardiovascular disease (CVD).</topic><topic number="6">The patient is a 55-year-old female with end-stage renal failure on hemodialysis and peritoneal dialysis, who presented with watery, non-blood diarrhoea and weakness. He has a history of two previous Clostridium difficile infections, the last of which was a month ago. She took antibiotics in the last month before she was admitted. The last C. difficile infection was treated with a 14-day course of oral vancomycin. Patient was initially admitted to intensive care and remained septic on vasopressor therapy with pressure medication (noradrenaline) until morning of [**8-26**], with leukocytosis but no fever. The C. difficile test was positive at admission and the patient had leukocytosis compatible with C. difficile infection. The patient was initially treated with oral vancomycin, oral Flagyl EV and oral Flagyl and, upon improvement, was reduced to oral vancomycin and oral Flagyl on [**8-29**]. The patient was treated with Vancomivins for a prolonged course of 6 weeks due to her recurrent C. difficile infection. The patient was also advised to take probiotics and to disinfect her home with bleach once discharged.</topic><topic number="7">60-year-old male with cirrhosis of hepatitis C, second degree esophageal varices, recent upper gastrointestinal bleeding for SNAF gastritis [**2-9**], referred to the emergency room from the hepatology clinic for a new speech disorder and tangential thinking. The patient also describes a new episode of imbalance that led to a fall, during which he may have hit his head. According to the latest note from the hepatology department, he's been off alcohol (ETOH) for a year (confirmed by the patient), the tox screen came back negative for alcohol. CT was within normal limits, and the neurological evaluation determined that it wasn't an ischemic event. The patient was diagnosed with suspected hepatic encephalopathy and started lactulose therapy. Liver function tests showed a significant increase in total and direct bilirubin since the last visit. Another concern was the increase in the patient's alkaline phosphatase (AFP). This could indicate a progression of cirrhosis, as he failed to respond to interferon twice. You'll need to undergo an outpatient follow-up to further investigate. Patient has a history of: HCV cirrhosis (treatment with interferon x2 without response); portal gastropathy; esophageal varices of the second degree; recent hospitalization with hypertension [**4-/2150**]: nonsteroidal drug-induced gastritis [**2-9**]</topic><topic number="8">This is a 57-year-old male with CLL and large cell metamorphosis. He presented with the disease on [**10/2119**] with an elevated white blood cell count and LDH. At the time, she had no splenomegaly or cytopenias. He had a bulky lymphadenopathy. He then completed four courses of Fludarabine+Cyclophosphamide+Rituximab (FCR) completed on [**2119**] 2009. He had an excellent response to the therapy and was followed for about two years. Then [**7-/2122**] was presented with an increased leukocyte count, approximately 50% lymphocytes and a slightly elevated LDH. He also had palpable lymphadenopathy that was getting worse. He then received four cycles of the PCR regimen, but did not achieve a significant response and his treatment regimen was changed to R-CVP (rituximab cyclophosphamide, vincristine and prednisone), of which he received two cycles. Again, he had no significant response, although he maintained a very good performance status, and he was eventually put on Campath therapy. Lymphocytosis resolved and the white blood cell count decreased, but it did not achieve great results in terms of reducing the voluminous lymphoadenopathy. Subsequently, she developed an enlarged left cervical lymph node, which was biopsied and found to have Richter's transformation.</topic><topic number="9">41-year-old male with a history of severe intellectual disability, congestive heart failure (CHF), epilepsy, while admitted to his residential care facility presented with right-sided facial spasms and generalized tremors, which ceased after administration of 20 mg of valium. According to an external medical report, the patient was considered to have focal epilepsy with secondary generalisation, probably due to anostic brain injury at birth and probably related to atrophic changes observed on MRI, particularly in the left temporal lobe. The patient developed his first seizures at the age of 13, when his family diagnosed him with a generalized seizure. She had a second seizure two years after the first episode. He was maintained on Dilantin and phenobarbital. The patient went 20 years without another seizure. Recently Dilantin has been gradually reduced and it was felt that perhaps this medicine was needed to keep him seizure-free. The patient had no further events during the hospital stay and was back to his baseline condition by the time of discharge. The full EEG records are awaiting delivery at the time of discharge. Medical history at a distance: epilepsy as above, CHF, depression</topic><topic number="10">Patient is a 22-year-old female, otherwise healthy, with a 5-year history of systemic mastocytosis, with relapses normally 3 times per year, presenting with hot flashes and tachycardia, indicative of another relapse. This is the third flare-up in two months for the patient, while she's still on steroids, which is new to her. He responded well to 125 mg EV steroids every 8 hours and diphenhydramine EV, in addition to continuous home therapy. Her blood count was baseline, with a normal differential. The serum tryptase was elevated to 84. The patient failed the aspirin challenge test due to an adverse reaction. She was stabilized with EV steroids and Benadryl EV and transferred back to the med bay. She continued her histamine receptor blockers and switched from intravenous to oral steroids and Benadryl, was kept under observation overnight and discharged with her home medication, prednisone to scalar, gastrointestinal prophylaxis with PPI, calcium and vitamin D, and Bactrim SS for PCP.</topic><topic number="11">75-year-old male with metastatic papillary thyroid cancer, treated with 19 sessions of radiation therapy, who had 2 days of worsening solids dysphagia, poor oral intake, weight loss of 9 kg in the last few weeks and some lethargy. Diagnosis of papillary thyroid cancer with mass in the right neck, previous resection of the mass in the neck; inability to perform thyroidectomy - high risk of bleeding, proximity to the trachea and recurrent laryngeal nerve and large tumor - previous radiotherapy to the neck - previous radioiodine ablation - metastases to the lymph nodes and adrenal glands *progressive repair of the hernia *progressive tonsillectomy</topic><topic number="12">34-year-old female with Marfan syndrome and known severe mitral valve prolapse with regurgitation, who was scheduled for mitral valve repair but missed at follow-up. She remains symptomatic and is now ready to undergo surgery to repair/replace her mitral valve. The ECx should be performed at a frequency of 65% on trans-thoracic echocardiography (TET). Patient has a history of: Marfan syndrome; mitral valve prolapse (MVP) with severe mitral regurgitation Gastric reflux disease History of gestational diabetes mellitus Hypertension in pregnancy Obesity 2 cesarean sections Laser eye surgery Cataract surgery Foot surgery (shortening of bone length)</topic><topic number="13">62-year-old male with history of cerebrovascular event (CVA), neurogenic bladder with permanent suprapubic catheter, with prior multiple admissions for urinary tract infections, altered mental status and urosepsis, presents to hospital with urosepsis resolved after treatment with vancomycin/meropenem. CT shows a nonobstructive stone in the left ureter, no evidence of urethral stricture. There's significant leakage around the suprapubic catheterization site. He was treated with Ditropan, then replaced with Detrusitol. The urologist isn't worried about the leakage and will be visiting the patient next week. Cerebrovascular event, neurological bladder treated with vesicular suprapubic catheterization s/p; Recurrent urinary tract infections with Klebsiella/ Pseudomonas Non-Hodgkin lymphoma of the left marginal orbital area diagnosed in 03 (R-CHOP s/p x 6 cycles) Bell' s IPB paralysis Hypertension Partial intestinal obstruction colostomy s/p Hepatitis C Cryoglobulinemia with LES transverse myelitis, anti-dsDNA antibodies Ab+ Diabetic insulin-dependent Fungal exophagitis Stage IV? Urinary tract infections - Pseudomonas and enterococcus</topic><topic number="14">70 year old patient with COPD in O2 home therapy with 2.5-3.5 L of O2 at baseline, OSA and obesity hypoventilation syndrome, dCHF, discharged [**2132-8-24**] now presents agitation and altered mental state with hypoxia and O2 saturation of 70 seconds with BipAp with 5 L. Patient agitated and then sleepy at initial presentation. Her daughter reported increased agitation and altered mental status for 2-3 days with O2 saturation of 60-70 seconds at home. The daughter also noticed an increase in lumbar oedema and weight gain, which prompted her to call her GP and increase the dose of Lasix from 80 mg per day to 100 mg per day with a slight improvement in the oedema. She had decreased appetite, O.P. intake, energy levels at home with difficulty in daily activities. You haven't had fever, cough, chills, sputum production, cerebral palsy, abdominal pain or any recent disorders other than chronic right thigh pain in the last 1-2 months. The daughter also reports adherence to drug therapy and night-time BiPap. Patient has a history of: - CAD; CABG s/p at 4 vessels in [**2119**]; - CHF; FE 55%, mild SA - obesity hypoventilation syndrome - obstructive sleep apnea - type 2 diabetes mellitus - ventricular tachycardia; ICD s/p in [**2127**] - hypothyroidism - schizophrenia - COPD - pneumonia treated in [**4-7**] at [**Hospital 1**] - had a history of: - severe hypothyroidism - severe hypothyroidism - severe hypothyroidism - severe hypothyroidism - severe hypothyroidism - severe hypothyroidism - severe hypothyroidism - severe hypothyroidism - severe hypothyroidism - severe hypothyroidism - severe hypothyroidism - severe hypothyroidism - severe hypothyroidism - severe hypothyroidism - severe hypothyroidism - severe hypothyroidism - severe hypothyroidism - severe hypothyroidism - severe hypothyroidism - severe hypothyroidism - severe hypothyroidism - severe hypothyroidism - severe hypothyroidism - severe hypothyroidism - severe hypothyroidism - severe hypothyroidism - severe hypothyroidism - severe hypothyroidism - severe hypothyroidism - severe depression - severe depression - severe depression - severe depression - severe depression - severe depression</topic><topic number="15">A 70-year-old woman with a history of coronary artery disease recently noticed an abdominal mass that presents with fever/chills and neutrophilia. In the weeks before admission, he had a mild abdominal pain, radiating to his left side. The pain lasts all day and does not increase with meals, although it is associated with vomiting, and it gets worse with coughing. A CT scan of the abdomen without contrast was then performed on [**4-20**] showing a large heterogeneous mass of 9,5 x 7,5 x 6,0 cm in the left upper abdomen. The patient underwent ultrasound (EUS) with biopsy. The biopsy results were consistent with pancreatic adenocarcinoma at the head of the pancreas. A mass between the splenic flexure and the pancreatic cauda was also observed on CT, probably a diverticular abscess, given the likely recent history of diverticulitis in the patient. It was thought to be a collection of infected fluid or an abscess. She has been treated with intravenous antibiotics (tazocin, then ceftriaxone and flagyl) and will continue to take them until the visit to the clinic by her doctor. Patient has a history of: Coronary artery disease with a history of angioplasty in [**State 108**] one year ago; 2. Prolapse of the mitral valve 3. Atrial fibrillation 4. Hyperlipidemia is not known to occur in patients with hyperlipidemia. Blood pressure 6. Chronic renal disease (SCr 2.1 in [**3-17**]) 7. What is it? Hypothyroidism? (TSH 10 in [**3-17**]) 8. The Commission has not yet received any comments from the applicant. The following table summarises the data for the following groups of patients:</topic><topic number="16">79-year-old patient with multifactorial chronic hypoxemia and dyspnea, presumably due to cardiac failure diastolic congestion, pulmonary hypertension, presumably secondary to chronic interatrial septal disorder and COPD, on home therapy with 5-litre oxygen therapy, hospitalized for worsening dyspnea. The cardiologist recommended a right-sided cardiac catheterization to assess the response to sildenafil, but the patient refused. The pulmonary examination recommended empirical and compassionate treatment with sildenafil due to severe dyspnoea symptoms that prevented outpatient admission, and the patient tolerated in-patient treatment without hypotension. Patients should undergo a pulmonary examination prior to initiating chronic, outpatient sildenafil therapy, if authorised. - Repair of the interatrial defect [**6-17**] complicated by sinus arrest with placement of a peripheral peace maker. - Pulmonary hypertension (RSVP 75 in [**11-24**]) thought to be secondary to a long-term interatrial septal defect - COPD with home oxygen therapy (5L NC nasal cannula) with basal saturation between 80 and 90 with this therapy. - OSAS, not compatible with CPAP - Mild mitral insufficiency - Microcytic anaemia - Hypothyroidism - APPY s/p, CCY s/p ('[**33**]) - Biliary pancreatitis treated with ERCP and sphincterotomy - Elevated levels of alkaline phosphatase secondary to amiodarone</topic><topic number="17">64 year old female with multiple myeloma, allogeneic transplant history with disease recurrence and systemic amyloidosis (involvement of lungs, tongue, bladder, heart), on haemodialysis for end-stage renal disease (ESRD), which is manifested by malaise, weakness and generalized muscle pain for 2 days. She was hospitalized last week for hypercalcemia and has been treated with pamidronate 30 mg, calcitonin and dialysis. The patient was initially treated with melphalan and prednisone, followed by chemotherapy with VAD and autologous stem cell transplantation. Following a recurrence of myeloma, he received thalidomide velcade and thalidomide, which were then discontinued due to worsening of the oedema and renal function.</topic><topic number="18">This is a 78-year-old man with severe benign prostatic hyperplasia (BPH) who underwent multiple urological procedures, including an over-the-counter prostatectomy. A contraction of diuresis was found and bladder scintigraphy showed a residual of 360 cc. It was impossible for the staff to insert a Foley catheter. A urologist was consulted, who performed a flexible cystoscopy in intensive care and found severe 2 cm bulbar urethral stenosis. They were able to insert a small catheter and leave it in place. The patient had leakage around the catheter, which eventually moved, but continued to have good diuresis and had post-mination bladder scans every 4 hours to make sure he didn't have a high residual volume. The urologist suggested that when the patient is stable, he should be taken to the operating room for surgical correction of the stenosis.</topic><topic number="19">A 65-year-old man with a history of coronary artery disease and a history of myocardial infarction, erectile dysfunction, hypertension, ventricular tachycardia and syncope was admitted today for evaluation of syncope and ventricular arrhythmias. He was recently discharged after testing negative for syncope, where he was fitted with a heart monitoring device. He was questioned at OSH, and according to the report, the monitor recorded 40 seconds of TV yesterday, followed by a 39-degree brisk heart rate, which matched his symptoms shortly after. During the night, the patient went into monomorphic TV via telemetry. The patient was found unconscious. CPR has been initiated, but it's unclear if the patient has a pulse. Within a minute, the patient's sinus rhythm was back. The patient reports no symptoms prior to this episode. At this time, the patient is experiencing presyncope and nausea, but denies chest pain. The patient should be transferred to intensive care for catheterization and electrophysiological study (EPS).</topic><topic number="20">A 35-year-old woman comes in with a history of acne and mild rash. The primary evaluation revealed elevated levels of testosterone. Recently she noticed a gradual swelling of her hands and feet and noticed that her ring was shrinking. She has some irregularity in her menstrual cycle and nipple discharge. He also has a positive history of snoring and headaches. Objective examination revealed mild facial features of acromegaly and prognatism. Visual fields are normal. There is irsutism, thickening of the soft tissues and diaphoresis of the hands and feet. Laboratory tests on an empty stomach revealed IGF-1 levels of 968 ng/mL and GH random of 19.7 ng/mL. MRI shows a noninvasive macroadenoma. He's been on steady doses of slow-release octreotide since his diagnosis was confirmed. She is married and has two children. She uses the IUD as a contraceptive.</topic><topic number="21">Patient is a 57-year-old male with abdominal pain and vomiting. The pain started gradually about 20 hours ago in the epigastric and peri-umbilical region, radiating to the back. He drinks about 60 units of alcohol a week and smokes 22 cigarettes a day. He's healthy, has no history of allergies, and he's not on any medication. His family history is positive for type 2 diabetes (father and sister). He lives alone and has no children. The abdomen is sore and soft. His peristalsis is normal on auscultation. His heart rate is 115 beats per minute and his blood pressure is 110/75 mmHg. Laboratory tests are significant for leukocytosis (19.5), urea of 8.5, high PCR (145), high amylase (1200) and Glc level of 15. CT came back negative for obstructive pancreatitis.</topic><topic number="22">Patient is a 31-year-old female with abdominal pain. The pain started last night as a pervasive abdominal discomfort. He had poor appetite and was unwell. The pain got worse and worse and became acute in the morning. The pain was localized to the lower right quadrant in the morning. Temperature is within normal limits with normal vital signs. Focal pain and defensive reaction were observed during palpation of the right lower quadrant. Palpation of the lower left quadrant causes pain on the right. Lab tests show a leukocytosis. CT scan of the abdomen with contrast shows a distended appendix with thickened appendicular wall, no perforation, abscess or gangrene. He's a candidate for laparoscopic appendectomy under general anesthesia.</topic><topic number="23">A 39-year-old man showed up at the clinic with a cough and dyspnea that were not relieved by the inhaler. She's had these symptoms for five days in the last two weeks. He doubled his dosage of oral corticosteroids last week. He's a chef with a three-year history of asthma, suffers from frequent coughing, wheezing, dyspnea and chest tightness. Symptoms become more bothersome within 1-2 hours of starting work each day and worsen during the work week. His symptoms improve within 1-2 hours of being out of the workplace. Spirometry was performed and revealed a forced expiratory volume in the first second (FEV1) of 63% of the above. His history is significant for seasonal allergic rhinitis in the summer. He does not smoke or use illegal drugs. His family history is significant for asthma in his father and sister. She is currently on inhaled corticosteroids (ICS) and fluticasone 500 mcg/salmeterol 50 mcg, once twice daily.</topic><topic number="24">The patient is a 55-year-old male who has visited his primary care physician for symptoms of a low urinary tract, including frequency, urgency, weak flow, incomplete emptying, and intermittent flow, in the past 9 months. Further investigations revealed: IPSS score: 15 Post-minal residue: 70 mL Prostate volume (TRUS): 60 mL Prostate specific antigen (PSA) level: 3.2 ng/mL 10 mL/sec maximum flow with a urinary volume of 130 mL Otherwise, the patient is in good health and takes only 1000 units of vitamin D per day. The most recent (3 days ago) haematological examinations were normal: Hgb: 13.5 g/dl WBC: 135000 /mm3 Plt: 350000 /ml PT: 11 seconds PTT: 35 seconds INR: 0.9 Creatinine: 0.5 mg/dl BUN: 10 mg/dl U/A: Color: yellow Appearance: turbid PH: 5.3 Specific weight: 1.010 Glc: 100 Nitrite: negative Ketones: absent Leukocyte esterase: negative RBC: negative</topic><topic number="25">The patient is a 42-year-old postmenopausal woman who underwent a screening ultrasound that revealed an abnormality in her right breast. She had no palpable masses on her breast exam. A needle biopsy was performed on the heart, revealing a 1.8 cm infiltrating ductal breast cancer in the left upper outer quadrant. A lumpectomy was performed and the surgical margins were clear. The tumor was HER2-positive and ER/PR negative. The axillary swab revealed 1 positive lymph node in 12 samples. The chest X-ray showed no abnormalities. She takes a daily multivitamin "for healthy women" and no other medications. He smokes frequently and drinks occasionally. She's in a one-partner relationship and has a history of three pregnancies and three live births. She breastfed all three of her children.</topic><topic number="26">A 45-year-old woman was referred to the emergency room with abdominal pain lasting approximately 4 days, accompanied by nausea and 2 episodes of vomiting. The pain is localized to the epigastric region and radiates to the upper right quadrant. The pain gets worse after eating fatty foods. The patient has experienced similar pain twice in the last year. Her remote history is significant for hypercholesterolemia and two caesarean sections. She has two kids and is in menopause. He does not smoke, drink alcohol, or use illicit drugs. She's slightly feverish. His blood pressure is 150 over 85, heart rate 115, respiratory rate 15, temperature 38.2 degrees, SpO2 98% in the air. On palpation, she's experiencing epigastric pain and pain in the upper right quadrant with no Bloomberg mark. The bowel sounds are normal. Lab tests show an elevated ESV and left-sided leukocytosis. Ultrasound revealed several gallstones and bile sludge. The largest calculation is 0.7 cm. The surgical consult recommends an elective cholecystectomy.</topic><topic number="27">A 53-year-old man has had a chronic HCV infection for 2 years. His history is only significant for an inguinal hernia surgery performed at the age of 20. He has been on combination therapy with IFN (100 mg/ week) plus RBV (400 mg/ day) for 9 months. 6 months ago, they added directed antiviral drugs to his treatment. His medical records show previous positive tests for HCV RNA and positive for HCV antibody enzyme immunoassays. The recent biopsy was negative for hepatocellular carcinoma and found only chronic inflammation consistent with chronic viral hepatitis. There is no evidence of alcoholic hepatopathy, bleeding from esophageal varices, haemochromatosis, autoimmune hepatitis or metabolic hepatopathy. He's a vigilant man, without acute suffering. Blood pressure is 130 over 75, heart rate is 90 over a minute, and BMI is 27. The abdomen is soft, no ascites or soreness. Lower extremities are normal, no swelling.</topic><topic number="28">The patient is a 60-year-old Spanish man who has been presenting with dyspnea for about a day. The symptoms started acutely and have progressively worsened. He's a known case of COPD for two years. Spirometry revealed a post-bronchodilator FEV1/FVC = 60% of the expected value. He smokes 20 cigarettes a day. His history is positive for benign prostatic hypertrophy (BPH) and he's using Flomax for it. His family history is positive for high blood pressure in his brother. His drug therapy includes Duo-Neb inhaled every 4 hours as needed, Vit D3 1000 units a day and Flomax for his BPH. He's an obese man, seriously ill but oriented and conscious. The vital signs are as follows: PA: 135/80 FR: 25/min FC: 75 bpm BMI: 40 Oxygen saturation: 90%</topic><topic number="29">The patient is a 24-year-old man who has had type 1 diabetes for 11 years. He presents to the emergency room with hyperglycaemia and concern for possible diabetic ketoacidosis after discontinuing insulin for 3 days. The patient reports that he is currently homeless and has lost his supply of insulin, syringes, blood glucose meter and blood glucose monitoring kit. The patient states that at the time of initial diagnosis of type 1 diabetes he was admitted to hospital with a blood glucose &gt; 1000 mg/dL. At the time, she had polyuria, polydipsia and polyphagia. He says he has been taking insulin since his diagnosis and has never been prescribed oral medication for diabetes management. More recently, he has taken insulin glargine 55 units once a day and insulin aspart as needed 3 times a day. The patient had previous episodes of diabetic ketoacidosis, for which he was hospitalized. Despite this episode of hyperglycemia, she's not experiencing nausea, vomiting, or abdominal disturbances, and she seems to be doing well. The following laboratory tests were performed: A1c: 11.3% Creatinine: 0.9 mg/dL with eGFR &gt; 60 mL/min Aspartate aminotransferase (AST): 17 U/L Alanine aminotransferase (ALT): 14 U/L Beta-hydroxybutyrate: 0.1 mmol/L Bicarbonate: 25 mEq/L Anionic gap: 14 mEq/L</topic><topic number="30">The patient is a 33-year-old woman who complained of fatigue, weight gain, and abnormal menstrual bleeding. No irsutism or nipple discharge was detected. Her BMI was 34. Its laboratory results were significant for a high level of TSH (13 mU/L) and a low level of free T4 (0.2 ng/dL). Its anti-TPO levels were extremely high (120 IU/ ml). She was diagnosed with Hashimoto's thyroiditis. His aunt, his brother and his mother all suffer from the same disease. After starting therapy with 250 mcg of Levothyroxine per day, her symptoms improved significantly and her menstrual periods were normal. She's still overweight with a BMI of 31. His most recent thyroid profile revealed all but anti-TPO results within the normal range: TSH: 2.35 mU/L free T4: 2.7 ng/dL anti-TPO: 75 IU/ml</topic><topic number="31">The patient is a 37-year-old woman who came to the clinic for a routine Pap test. The test revealed a stage 1B cervical cancer. The patient tested positive for HPV 16. She has three sexual partners and four children. She's been tubed. He smokes 30 packs of cigarettes a year and drinks alcohol frequently. Otherwise, he's in good health. She was offered a radical hysterectomy.</topic><topic number="32">A 17-year-old boy has been complaining of vomiting, non-blood diarrhea, abdominal pain, fever, chills, and loss of appetite for the past three days. She ate a salad at the restaurant before the diarrhea flared up. Objective examination revealed paleness, jaundice and widespread abdominal pain. The results of the laboratory tests were as follows: Haemoglobin: 9.7 g/dL Platelets: 110,000/mm3 Creatinine: 3.6 mg/dL Blood urea nitrogen (BUN): 73 mg/dL Direct bilirubin: 2.4 mg/dL Lactic dehydrogenase (LDH): 881 IU/L (normal: 110-265 IU/L) The peripheral blood strip showed a moderate number of schistocytes and keratocytes. Shiga-like toxin-producing Escherichia coli (STEC) stx1/stx2 were found in the faeces. He has no other medical history and is not taking any medication.</topic><topic number="33">A healthy 42-year-old woman came to the clinic to get her flu shot in early October. She works at a rehab facility and has no history of illness. It's the first time he's had it this year. She's been married for five years and uses barrier methods of contraception. Her menstrual cycle is irregular. He doesn't smoke. He's not on any medication. Regularly exercise for 30 minutes a day, at least 5 days a week. No history of food or drug allergies. His prior surgical history is significant for tonsillectomy and otherwise he's in good health.</topic><topic number="34">The patient is a 47-year-old Asian woman who complains of persistent feelings of sadness. She has lost interest in activities that she once enjoyed. She claims to be mostly depressed for the last three weeks. He also lost his appetite, which led to a weight loss of about 10 pounds. He laments loss of energy and a sense of uselessness almost every day. He doesn't use drugs or smoke. He doesn't drink alcohol. He exercised every day for at least 30 minutes, but for the last three weeks he hasn't had enough energy to do it. He's also been having some digestive problems lately. She's married with four children. She's going through menopause. Your husband has recently been diagnosed with colon cancer and is beginning chemotherapy. There's nothing relevant in his medical history, and his drug history is only positive for 1,000 units of vitamin D3 a day. His family history is negative for any psychological problems. His HAM-D score is 20.</topic><topic number="35">Patient is a 15-year-old girl with a history of recurrent bilateral headaches. The attacks occur 2 or more times a week and each episode lasts about a day or a half. The pain is throbbing and intense, causing difficulty in his usual physical activity. The seizures are associated with nausea and photophobia. She recently noticed that the attacks intensify during the menstrual cycle. She's been diagnosed with a migraine and is being treated. She's a high school student and lives with both parents. She is a book eater and spends her free time in a public library near her home. She is also interested in short story writing and has written several short stories in English. He rarely exercises. Her BMI is 21 with a blood pressure of 100/60. There's nothing remarkable about his objective examination.</topic><topic number="36">The patient is a 32-year-old obese woman who came to the clinic with weight problems. She is 5'5" tall and weighs 113 pounds. She complains of sleep apnea, polycystic ovarian syndrome (PCOS), and dissatisfaction with her physical condition. She's a high school teacher who's been married for five years. She hasn't used any contraceptive method for 4 months and she hasn't had a pregnancy before. He doesn't smoke or do drugs. She would like to try losing weight with diet and exercise. He completed the four-step test in 14 seconds. His blood pressure is 130/80, his heart rate is 195/min and his BMI is 41.54. Laboratory tests: FBS: 98 mg/dl TG: 150 mg/dl Cholesterol: 180 mg/dl LDL: 90 mg/dl HDL: 35 mg/dl His cardiac evaluation is normal. He has a high blood pressure. His joints and range of motion (ROM) are within the norm.</topic><topic number="37">Patient is a 20-year-old Caucasian female who comes to the clinic with one-sided vision loss and facial weakness, dysarthria, and numbness lasting one day. She went to her primary care physician and had an MRI scan of her brain that revealed a single plaque in her brain stem. After a few months, she developed weakness in her lower extremities that led to balance problems. The second MRI revealed another lesion in the left cerebral hemisphere. The diagnosis of relapsing-remitting multiple sclerosis (RRMS) was confirmed after the second MRI. Her prior surgical history is significant for a cesarean delivery that occurred two years ago and she has a son. She's divorced and currently not having sex. He smokes 10 cigarettes a day and drinks alcohol occasionally. She works as an editor in a publishing house and is happy to continue working from home most of the time. He's been on treatment for RRMS for seven months.</topic><topic number="38">Patient is a 35-year-old female with severe myasthenia gravis, class IIa. She complains of diplopia, fatigue, and weakness affecting mainly the upper limbs. The anti-AChR antibody test was positive and the single-fiber electromyography (SFEMG) was positive. Take 60 mg of pyridostigmine three times a day. However, he still has some symptoms that interfere with his work. She's a research coordinator and has three kids. Her father, 70, suffers from hypertension. He does not smoke or use illegal drugs. He drinks alcohol occasionally at social events. Objective and laboratory examinations have revealed no other abnormalities. The following table shows the number of samples of the test chemical in the blood:</topic><topic number="39">A three-day-old Asian baby shows up with jaundice that started the day before. She was born at 38 weeks and 3 days of gestation, after a pregnancy without complications. Family history is negative. The newborn is breastfed. The vital signs are: armpit temperature: 36.3 &#176;C, heart rate: 154 beats/min, respiratory rate 37 breaths/min and blood pressure: 65/33 mm Hg. The weight is 3.2 kg, the length is 53 cm and the skull circumference is 36 cm. The sclera is yellow and the body is jaundiced. No breathing or other abnormalities on the cardiac and pulmonary auscultation. Liver and spleen are normal to the touch. The laboratory results are as follows: Total serum bilirubin: 21,02 mg/dL Direct bilirubin 2,04 mg/dL AST: 37 U/L ALT: 20 U/L GGT: 745 U/L Alkaline phosphatase: 531 U/L Creatinine: 0.3 mg/dL Urea: 29 mg/dL Na: 147 mEq/L K: 4.5 mEq/L PCR: 3 mg/L Hemochrome is complete as normal and is not known to cause any adverse effects to the liver. She was diagnosed with uncomplicated neonatal jaundice that may require phototherapy.</topic><topic number="40">The patient is a 60-year-old male with frequent headaches, generalized bone pain, and difficulty chewing, which began six years ago and is getting worse. Objective examination shows bilateral swelling around the molars. The swelling's increased since the last exam. Several extraoral lesions were found on the head and face. The swelling is not painful and is adherent to the bone underneath. Further investigations show an increase in the absorption of radioactive substances and an increase in urinary pyridinoline. The serum alkaline phosphatase is 300 IU/L (the range of normal is 44-147 IU/L). Her family history is only significant for hypertension in the mother and type 2 diabetes mellitus in the father. Paget's bone disease diagnosis has been confirmed and bisphosphonates will be started as first-line therapy.</topic><topic number="41">A 57-year-old farmer was diagnosed with Parkinson's disease a year ago. He suffers from sluggish movement and tremors. His history is significant for hypertension and high cholesterol. He lives with his wife and has three children. Before his diagnosis, he was engaged in planting and caring for farm animals. The patient complains of tremors and slowness of movement. He had difficulty getting through a door because he was paralyzed and needed help to get in. His handwriting is getting smaller. He's on Levodopa and Trioxyphenyl. He said his medication helps him manage the tremors and the slowness of movement. However, it still presents with difficulty in initiating movements, stiffness and slowness in general. He's a vigilant, cooperative man who shows no signs of dementia. He does not smoke or use illegal drugs.</topic><topic number="42">A 19-year-old Hispanic woman, G1P1, 32 weeks plus 6 weeks gestational age, presented herself to the gynecologist for a routine checkup complaining of a mild headache and swollen legs. Initial evaluation found a blood pressure of 146/99 and a urine test with protein 3+. Blood pressure and urine tests were normal at the last visit. The repeated blood pressure a few hours later is 150/100 mmHg. Lab tests showed normal blood count, platelet count and hepatic transaminases. She's complaining of fatigue, but no fever or chills. He also suffers from headaches, without any visual impairment. Shortness of breath, cough, chest pain, orthopaedics, palpitations or skin rash were not observed. The objective examination was negative for abdominal pain, altered bowel habits, nausea, vomiting, dysuria, frequency, haematuria or cloudy urine. Leg swelling was observed, without arthralgia or back pain. She has no history of any health problems and only takes prenatal vitamins. His family history is positive for type 2 diabetes mellitus and hypertension. She is a socially active alcoholic with a history of smoking or drug use. You've had one partner in the last two years and you haven't used any contraceptive methods in two years. Her BMI was 24 at her first visit, when she was six weeks pregnant. Her weight is increasing normally during pregnancy.</topic><topic number="43">Patient is a 60-year-old female admitted to the stroke unit with a recent history of a second course of intravenous antibiotics for ab ingestied pneumonia. She is feverish and complains of abdominal pain and diarrhea (eight bowel movements in 3 hours, with copious amounts of liquid, greenish stool each time). The patient's abdomen is generally painful and distended, with overactive intestinal peristalsis. It is febrile (38.4 &#176;C), tachycardiac (113/min) and hypotensive (80/40 mmHg). The stool samples tested positive for Clostridium difficile toxin.</topic><topic number="44">The patient is a 14-year-old boy with scoliosis and back pain. He has no other medical conditions. In the past, he was able to perform routine activities such as basketball and soccer, but recently he has had difficulty performing them. The pain is localized to the leg and back and is aggravated by physical activity. He prefers to lie down most of the time. He is not satisfied with his gestures and complains of an imbalance of the shoulders and a shift of the head to the right. The patient is a well-dressed and well-fed adolescent, alert and cooperative. The left shoulder is slightly higher than the right shoulder. The scoliosis curve is 45 degrees. The patient is a candidate for surgery for scoliosis according to perioperative evoked potential (EPM) monitoring.</topic><topic number="45">The patient is a 34-year-old African-American male with a known history of sickle cell anemia who shows up at the clinic with severe bone pain. Patient had severe lower back pain radiating to both thighs, scoring 9 out of 10. The patient has a history of sickle cell seizures since childhood. He also exhibited the same symptoms in the last two weeks after being treated with oxycodone, which had no effect on pain. His primary care physician sent him to the emergency room to receive intravenous pain modulators. Patient is aperetic and blood pressure is normal. No splenomegaly was detected on objective examination. He doesn't have a positive history of drug allergy. He does not smoke or use illegal drugs. The laboratory test is as follows: Hb: 8 g/dl WBC: 10000 /mm3 Plt: 300000 /ml MCV: 106 fL Haemoglobin electrophoresis: 91% HbS 6% HbF 3% HbA2 AST: 22 U/L ALT: 43 U/L Alcohol P: 53 U/L Ferritin: 1200 ng/ml The test is carried out in the following way:</topic><topic number="46">Patient A is a 30-year-old male, hospitalized after 10 days of coughing, heavy night sweats and loss of appetite. He had traveled to India a month earlier and has no history of positive TB vaccination. He's a healthy man, working as an engineer in a high-tech company. He does not smoke or use illegal drugs. He had a fever of 38 degrees, a heart rate of 115 beats per minute, a respiratory rate of 22, a blood pressure of 125/75 mmHg, and an O2 saturation of 97%. Chest X-ray revealed an infiltrate in the center of the left lung with a diameter of 1.8 cm and signs of cavitation. The examination of the sputum culture revealed a positive for Mycobacterium tuberculosis, which is sensitive to first-line anti-tuberculosis drugs (isoniazid, streptomycin, rifampicin and etambutol). The results of the laboratory tests are as follows: Hgb: 13 g/dl WBC: 14000 /mm3 Plt: 300000 /ml AST: 13 U/l ALT: 15 U/l Alk P: 53 U/l Total bill: 0.6 mg/dl Na: 137 mEq/l K: 4 mEq/l Creatinine: 0.5 mg/dl BUN: 10 mg/dl VES: 120 mm/h</topic><topic number="47">A 62-year-old African-American male presented with weakness of the left upper and lower extremities, associated with dark visual spot in the right eye, right facial numbness, facial ptosis and speech difficulty. He denied breathlessness, headache, palpitations, chest pain, fever, dizziness, bowel or urinary incontinence, loss of consciousness. His history was significant for hypertension, hyperlipidemia and hypothyroidism. He's been smoking a pack of cigarettes a day for 40 years and drinking five to six beers a week. You don't know anything about his family history. You are taking levothyroxine, atorvastatin and hydrochlorothiazide (HTCZ). His vitals were stable at the primary assessment. Objective examination revealed left facial ptosis, dysarthria and left hemiplegia. His score on the National Institutes of Health Stroke Scale (NIHSS) was calculated as 7. Initial CT angiography of the head and neck showed no acute intracranial marks. Tissue-activated recombinant plasminogen (t-PA) was administered intravenously, as well as high-dose statin therapy. The patient was admitted to the intensive care unit for 24 hours of observation. Cranial MRI revealed an acute infarction of 1.7 cm of the right periventricular white matter and the right posterior basal ganglia.</topic><topic number="48">Fernandez is a 41-year-old professional soccer player. He came to the clinic with an itchy foot. Objective examination revealed a localized peeling and maceration between the third and fourth toes of the right foot. The area is inflamed and sore, with slight fissures. The back and the sole of the foot were not affected. There's no pus or lacerations in the affected area. He didn't use topical ointments on the lesion and he doesn't have a positive history of any underlying conditions, like diabetes mellitus. He smokes 15 cigarettes a day and drinks a beer a day. His family history is positive for hyperlipidemia in the mother and myocardial infarction in the father. She has multiple partners and uses a condom during sex. The objective examination and laboratory tests were otherwise normal. Tinea pedis infection was confirmed as a diagnosis by observation of segmented fungal hyphae during a microscopic examination with KOH.</topic><topic number="49">A 12-year-old girl came to the clinic with her mother, complaining of short stature, delayed puberty, and stunted growth. The karyotype revealed a 45X value and confirmed the diagnosis of Turner syndrome. She's been on GH for six months, no estrogen therapy, to avoid menopause and achieve her ideal height. On objective examination, the child was found to be obese and mentally retarded. Her breast lump was stage 1, no pubic or axillary hair. His TSH was 3 and his FBS was 75 on the last lab test.</topic><topic number="50">A 5-month-old baby was taken to the pediatric surgery room for evaluation of a hollow scrotum on the right side. The baby is the first born, born at 38 weeks with NVD from a healthy mother. The mother had a normal pregnancy with no complications. The baby weighed 3,200 grams and was 50 centimeters tall. He is breastfed and now weighs 6.5 kg and is 62 cm tall. It has no developmental delays on objective examination. There is a palpable testicle in the left scrotum, but it is not palpable in the right scrotum. The penis is normal in shape and size and the boy is not circumcised. Diagnostic laparoscopy showed a retained abdominal testicle.</topic><topic number="51">Patient is a 25-year-old pregnant female, G1 P1, gestational age 24 weeks and 3 days, who developed a sudden onset of fever and chills, accompanied by nausea and vomiting. He also complains of dizziness, urgency and urinary frequency. He also reports a sharp pain in his side. The following are the vital parameters: T = 39,7 &#176;C, FC = 117, R = 20 and PA = 113/74 mm Hg. Objective examination reveals pain on palpation of both costovertebral angles. You have no history of recurrent urinary tract infections before pregnancy or other underlying conditions. Urine culture showed Gram-negative bacterial rod cells, white blood cells and white blood cell cylinders. The blood culture is negative. The blood count shows Hb 12.9 g/dL, Hct 39%, MCV 76 fL, white count 14.120/&#956;L.</topic><topic number="52">A 34-year-old man shows up at the clinic complaining of dizziness and severe diarrhea from yesterday. He returned from an international trip a few days ago and lived in a camp in Sudan for a month. She developed abdominal pain followed by swelling and nausea, as well as liquid diarrhea. Soon she began to have profuse, odorless watery diarrhea. The stool is watery and white, but the patient has no fever. Blood pressure is 95/62 lying down and drops to 75/40 standing up. The skin turgor has subsided. Heart rate is 110 and the patient appears to be suffering from dry mucous membranes. V. cholerae was observed under a dark-field microscope in a fresh stool sample. The laboratory test is as follows: Sodium 137 meq/L Potassium 2 meq/L Chloride 94 meq/L CO2 15 meq/L Faecal leukocytes None observed Occult blood in the faeces Negative</topic><topic number="53">The patient is a 34-year-old woman from Jordan who comes to the clinic for general and non-specific bone and joint pain. She's married with three kids. His medical and pharmacological history is normal. His BMI is 23, BP is 120/75, and his heart rate is 75/min. Lab tests show vitamin D at 14 ng/ml and otherwise healthy. The test chemical is a substance which is a constituent of a food additive.</topic><topic number="54">A 57-year-old man was admitted to the clinic four months ago for weight loss and persistent dry cough. Axial CT scan of the chest showed bilateral multiple infiltrates in the upper lobes and thickened bronchial walls. He has a documented positive serum MPO-ANCA in his medical record. Transbronchial biopsy revealed necrotic granulomas with multinucleated giant cells and he was diagnosed with Wegener's granulomatosis. He's been on corticosteroids and cyclophosphamide for four months. His Birmingham vasculitis activity score (BVAS) is above 4 from the onset of the disease. The latest physical and laboratory examinations were performed yesterday and showed the following results: The following table shows the number of samples of the substance in the sample:</topic><topic number="55">A 22-year-old Caucasian man showed up at the clinic with a history of tremors for a year. The tremor initially manifested itself in the right hand while holding something in his hand. Afterward, the tremor became continuous and spread to both hands and legs, even at rest. The ophthalmic examination showed the ring of Kayser-Fleischer. Objective examination revealed jaundice, hepatosplenomegaly and hypotonia of the upper limbs. He had a constant smile on his face, but, according to his parents' explanation, he had aggressive behavior. Laboratory tests showed low serum ceruloplasmin (0.05 g/ l) and high urinary excretion of copper over 24 hours (120 &#956;g/24 h). Wilson' s disease was confirmed by the high hepatic copper concentration (305 &#956;g/g dry weight of liver).</topic><topic number="56">Patient is a 41-year-old male, diagnosed with acromegaly, underwent transphenoid surgery four months ago. He showed up at the clinic for follow-up lab tests after the primary resection. Laboratory tests show a gender and age-corrected IGF-1 level of 4.5 ULN. His GH level is 4 &#956;g/L. Recent MRI of the brain confirmed a residual pituitary tumor. His remote medical history is only significant for acromegaly due to pituitary adenoma and recent surgery. After surgery, she's on vitamin D and multivitamins.</topic><topic number="57">Patient is a 41-year-old obese woman who shows up at the emergency room with abdominal pain and vomiting. The pain, which started gradually yesterday, is localized to the epigastric and peri-umbilical region, radiating to the back. He drinks alcohol frequently and does not smoke. She has no history of allergies and only takes a daily multivitamin. Her family history is positive for hypertension (the mother). She lives with her husband and has three children. The abdomen is sore and soft. His bowel sounds are normal. His heart rate is 115 beats per minute and his blood pressure is 110/75 mmHg. Laboratory tests show a leukocytosis of 19.5, a urea of 8.5, a high PCR of 145, a high amylase of 1200 and a glucose of 15. Abdominal CT shows an acute interstitial pancreatitis with dilation of the common bile duct and intrahepatic duct, consistent with the diagnosis of pancreatitis from gallstones. Her pregnancy test is negative and she's not breastfeeding.</topic><topic number="58">Patient is a 17-year-old boy who is complaining of severe, migratory pain in the right lower quadrant of his abdomen, which began four days ago. The pain is accompanied by nausea and vomiting. She was feverish with tenderness, positive Bloomberg sign and defense reaction to palpation. His white blood cells were elevated with neutrophilia. CT showed signs of acute perforated appendicitis with free-flowing into the pelvis. Diagnostic laparoscopy revealed a phlegm in the absence of other abdominal abnormalities. He's now a candidate for emergency laparoscopic appendectomy under general anesthesia.</topic><topic number="59">Patient is a 15-year-old boy with asthma diagnosed a year ago. She's experiencing shortness of breath, chest tightness and coughing. According to the mother, she didn't respond to the usual corticosteroid inhaler. He was admitted to the emergency room with a diagnosis of severe asthma exacerbation. He was a candidate for systemic corticosteroid therapy. Spirometry revealed a forced expiratory volume in the first second (FEV1) of 60% of the above. His distant medical history is not significant. His family history is positive for asthma in his mother and uncle. He was previously treated with a combination of inhaled corticosteroids and Zafirlukast.</topic><topic number="60">Patient is a 63-year-old male who came to the emergency room with a history of acute urinary retention in the last two days. Abdominal CT revealed an enlarged prostate and a bladder full of urine. He's a candidate for urethral catheterization and TURP. Further evaluations revealed: Post-minal residue: 71 mL Prostate volume (TRUS): 63 mL Prostate specific antigen (PSA) level: 3.5 ng/mL Recent (3 days ago) haematological examination normal: Hgb: 13.6 g/dl WBC: 133000 /mm3 Plt: 370000 /ml PT: 12 seconds PTT: 34 seconds INR: 0.9 Creatinine: 0.5 mg/dl BUN: 10 mg/dl U/A: Colour: yellow Appearance: turbid PH: 5.3 Specific weight: 1.010 Glc: 100 Nitrite: Negative Chetones: absent Leukocyte esterase: RBC negative: WBC negative: 2 WBC/hBC/pfC negative: U/C was found to be positive for the following:</topic><topic number="61">Patient is a 45-year-old postmenopausal female with cytologically confirmed breast cancer. An agobopsy revealed a 3 cm invasive ductal breast cancer in the left upper outer quadrant. The tumor is HER2-positive and ER/PR negative. The axillary swab revealed five positive lymph nodes. The chest X-ray showed metastatic lesions. The patient is taking multivitamins and iron supplements. He doesn't smoke or drink. She's not sexually active and has no children. She's a candidate for resection of the tumor and she's willing to do it before chemotherapy.</topic><topic number="62">A 46-year-old man comes in with dizziness and frequent headaches. He has a family history of coronary artery disease, but no other cardiovascular risk factors like smoking, high blood pressure and diabetes mellitus, and he's physically active. The patient' s LDL-C and HDL-C levels were 545 and 53 mg/dL, respectively. Fasting blood glucose and triglyceride levels (85 and 158 mg/ dL respectively) were within the normal range. The patient reported no lipid-lowering drugs. Auscultation of the neck revealed a 3/6 systolic blow to the neck, irradiated to the head. Ultrasound of the carotid arteries revealed severe stenosis in the left internal carotid artery (LICA) as well as moderate stenosis in the right internal carotid artery (RICA), estimated to be between 40% and 50%. For LICA, the systolic peak velocity (PSV) and the telediastolic peak velocity (EDV) limit values were 208,5 cm/s and 54,5 cm/s respectively; the PSV of RICA was 91,72 cm/s and the EDV of RICA was 37,37 cm/s. In the anterior and posterior walls of the internal carotid artery and common carotid artery, large plaques extending to the middle third of the internal coronary arteries (ICA) were detected, predominantly ecogenic and hyperogenic, with less than 50% of the ecolocating area having irregular surfaces.</topic><topic number="63">A 54-year-old obese woman was admitted to the emergency room with abdominal pain that had started four days earlier, along with nausea and vomiting. The epigastric pain radiates to the right upper quadrant, worsening after ingestion of fatty foods. The patient has experienced similar pain twice in the last year. Her history is significant for hypercholesterolaemia and natural 2-part (NVD). She has two kids and is in menopause. He does not smoke, drink alcohol, or use illicit drugs. She has a slight fever. His blood pressure is 150/85, heart rate is 115, respiratory rate is 15, body temperature is 38.2&#176;C, SpO2 98% in ambient air (RA). She's an obese woman with no acute pain. On palpation, she's experiencing epigastric pain and pain in the right upper quadrant with a negative Bloomberg mark. The bowel sounds are normal. Laboratory tests indicate elevated VES and leukocytosis with increased immature neutrophil component. Ultrasound revealed several gallstones, bile sludge and stones of CBD. The smallest calculation is 14 mm.</topic><topic number="64">The patient is a 55-year-old male who was diagnosed two years ago with HCV and, more recently, a co-infection with HBV. His remote history is not significant. He has been on interferon (IFN), ribavirin (RBV) and antiviral medicines for 6 months. The patient is not taking any other medication. His medical records show a previous positive test for HCV RNA and a positive immuno-enzyme test for anti-HCV antibodies. The recent biopsy was negative for hepatocellular carcinoma and only showed chronic inflammation consistent with chronic viral hepatitis. There is no evidence of alcoholic hepatopathy, bleeding from esophageal varices, haemochromatosis, autoimmune hepatitis or metabolic hepatopathy. He's a vigilant man, with no signs of acute distress. His blood pressure is 130/75, his heart rate is 90/min and his BMI is 27. The abdomen is soft, no ascites or soreness. Lower extremities are normal, no swelling.</topic><topic number="65">The patient is a 25-year-old male with type 1 diabetes confirmed by molecular analysis seven years ago. He shows up at the clinic with breathing difficulties and fatigue during activities. He reports mild dyspnea after climbing 3 floors, no dyspnea at rest and no angina (New York Heart Association class 2). He's been diagnosed with cardiomyopathy, which will be treated with ACE inhibitors and beta-blockers. He's on insulin 70/30 and vitamin D supplements. His history is not significant for other medical problems. His family history is positive for type 1 diabetes in his uncle and grandfather. The following are his laboratory tests: FBS: 100 mg/dl HbA1c: 6.5% Cholesterol: 190 mg/dl TG: 140 mg/dl LDL: 125 mg/dl HDL: 40 mg/dl</topic><topic number="66">A 16-year-old girl came to the clinic complaining of weight gain and irregular menstrual cycles. Her BMI was 24, but in the last few weeks she's gained 10 pounds. She gets tired more often and doesn't have the energy to go dancing with her friends. Its laboratory results were significant for high TSH levels (15 mU/ L) and low free T4 levels (0.18 ng/ dL). Its anti-TPO levels were extremely high (136 IU/ml). She was diagnosed with Hashimoto's thyroiditis. She doesn't smoke and she's not sexually active.</topic><topic number="67">A Pap test on a 54-year-old woman revealed an abnormal intraepithelial/cervical scaly gland lesion. The patient tested positive for HPV 16. She has a husband, with whom she has a sexually active life, and she has four children. She's in menopause and not using any form of contraception. He smokes and drinks alcohol frequently. Otherwise, he's in good health. You've been offered conization.</topic><topic number="68">The patient is a 23-year-old male who was admitted to hospital with high blood pressure (175/95 mmHg) and signs of septicaemia. He developed respiratory failure that required mechanical ventilation and renal failure that required hemodialysis. The blood smear showed microangiopathic haemolytic anemia and thrombocytopenia. Blood tests revealed an increase in lactate dehydrogenase and a decrease in complement factor C3 levels, with a normal clotting profile. He was diagnosed with atypical hemolytic uremic syndrome. He was treated with plasmapheresis and corticosteroids. You have previously been vaccinated with the conjugated meningococcal vaccine of group ACWY and the meningococcal vaccine of group B. The genetic survey revealed a value of ADAMTS13 of &gt; 10%.</topic><topic number="69">A healthy 67-year-old woman came to the clinic to get her flu vaccine in early October. She works at a rehab facility and has no history of illness. It's his first vaccination this year. She's menopausal and has four children. (Doesn't he?) She takes a daily multivitamin and antihypertensive medication. He exercises regularly for 30 minutes a day, at least 5 days a week. He's not allergic to any food or medication.</topic><topic number="70">A 46-year-old Asian woman with major depressive disorder complains of persistent feelings of sadness and loss of interest in daily activities. She claims to be depressed most of the day. He laments loss of energy and a sense of uselessness almost every day. She's been on antidepressants for six months, but her symptoms are still present. He doesn't drink alcohol or smoke. He exercised every day for at least 30 minutes, but for the last three weeks he hasn't had enough energy to do it. He's also had digestive problems recently. She's married with four children. She's going through menopause. Your husband was diagnosed with colon cancer a year ago and is undergoing chemotherapy. His distant medical history shows no significant symptoms. His family history is negative for psychological problems. His HAM-D score is 20.</topic><topic number="71">The patient is a 34-year-old obese woman who comes to the clinic for weight problems. She is 5'5" tall and weighs 113 kg (BMI: 41.5). In the past, he's tried anti-obesity drugs and appetite suppressants without success. She complains of sleep apnea, polycystic ovarian syndrome (PCOS), and dissatisfaction with her physical condition. He's a high school teacher. She's been married for five years. You have not used any contraceptive method in the last 4 months and you have not had a previous pregnancy. She rarely exercises and movement seems to be difficult for her. He can't complete the four-square test in less than 15 seconds. He doesn't smoke or do drugs. His blood pressure is 130/80, his heart rate is 195/min and his BMI is 41.54. The following are the results of the laboratory tests: FBS: 98 mg/dl TG: 150 mg/dl Cholesterol: 180 mg/dl LDL: 90 mg/dl HDL: 35 mg/dl She is considering a laparoscopic gastric bypass.</topic><topic number="72">The patient is a 16-year-old girl who was recently diagnosed with severe myasthenia gravis class iia. He's complaining of diplopia and weakness in his upper extremities. The anti-AChR antibody test was positive and the single-fiber electromyography (SFEMG) was positive. You are being treated with acetylcholinesterase inhibitors in combination with immunosuppressants. However, he still has some symptoms. He does not smoke or use illegal drugs. She's not sexually active and her periods are regular. Objective examination and laboratory tests show no other abnormalities. Blood pressure: Blood pressure: 110/75 Hgb: 11 g/dl WBC: 8000 /mm3 Plt: 300000 /ml Creatinine: 0.5 mg/dl BUN: 10 mg/dl Beta hCG: negative for pregnancy The following data are not available for the following patients:</topic><topic number="73">Patient is a 3-day-old infant with jaundice that started the day before. She was born at 34 weeks gestation and was kept in an incubator due to her gestational age. The vital signs were as follows: armpit temperature: 36.3 &#176;C, heart rate: 154 beats/min, respiratory rate: 37 breaths/min and blood pressure: 65/33 mm Hg. Its weight is 2.1 kg, its length is 45 cm and its skull circumference is 32 cm. He has yellow sclerosis and jaundice. Liver and spleen are normal to the touch. The laboratory results are as follows: Total serum bilirubin: 21,02 mg/dL Direct bilirubin 2,04 mg/dL AST: 37 U/L ALT: 20 U/L GGT: 745 U/L Alkaline phosphatase: 531 U/L Creatinine: 0.3 mg/dL Urea: 29 mg/dL Na: 147 mEq/L K: 4.5 mEq/L PCR: 3 mg/L Hemochrome is complete as normal and is not known to cause any adverse effects to the liver. She's been diagnosed with neonatal jaundice that may require phototherapy.</topic><topic number="74">The patient is a 53-year-old male who complains of frequent headaches, generalized bone pain, and difficulty chewing, which began six years ago and is getting worse. Objective examination shows bilateral swelling around the molars. The swelling's increased since the last exam. Several extraoral lesions are detected on the head and face. The swelling is painless and adheres to the bone underneath. Further investigations show an increase in the absorption of radioactive substances and an increase in urinary pyridinoline. The serum alkaline phosphatase is 300 IU/L (the range of normal is 44-147 IU/L). The patient's sister had the same problems. She was diagnosed with Paget's disease of bone at the age of 52. Paget's bone disease diagnosis is confirmed and bisphosphonates will be started as first-line therapy.</topic><topic number="75">The patient is a 55-year-old man who was recently diagnosed with Parkinson's disease. He complains of slow movement and tremors. His disease is classified as mild, stage Hoehn-Yahr I. His history is positive for hypertension and high cholesterol. He lives with his wife. They have three children. Before he was diagnosed, he was a gardener. He complains of tremors and slow movement. He had difficulty getting through a door because he was paralyzed and needed help to get in. His handwriting is getting smaller. He's being prescribed Levodopa and Triexiphenidyl. He's a vigilant, cooperative man who shows no signs of dementia. He does not smoke or use illegal drugs.</topic></topics>